<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList>
  <provider>
    <System>Sega Saturn</System>
    <software>Skraper</software>
    <database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
    <web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
  </provider>
  <game id="13260" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./3D Lemmings (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>3D Lemmings </name>
    <desc>You, as in all other Lemmings games, are responsible for helping hoards of lemmings through hazardous environments to safety. However, this lemmings game goes just that little bit further by introducing the lemmings to 80 new 3-dimensional levels!</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19960705T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Clockworks Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/3D Lemmings (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/3D Lemmings (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/3D Lemmings (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13173" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Albert Odyssey - Legend of Eldean (USA) (RE).chd</path>
    <name>Albert Odyssey - Legend of Eldean  </name>
    <desc>The game follows the adventure of Pike, a young boy whose family was murdered by a horde of monsters while still an infant, and is raised by a family of winged humanoids known as Harpies. Ten years later, his adoptive sister is turned to stone by an evil mage. Together with Cirrus, a talking sword housing the spirit of one of the legendary Eldean siblings, Pike travels the world to search for a cure, and discovers a plot by a group of evil magicians to turn the world's races against each other and revive the ancient god Vlag. Together with the help of friends he meets along his journey, Pike must prevent the evil's resurrection.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970731T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Working Designs</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Albert Odyssey - Legend of Eldean (USA) (RE).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Albert Odyssey - Legend of Eldean (USA) (RE).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Albert Odyssey - Legend of Eldean (USA) (RE).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13102" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Alien Trilogy (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Alien Trilogy </name>
    <desc>Alien Trilogy is a first-person shooter based on the first three Alien movies. You control Lt. Ripley in three sections, each based on one film: The colony complex on LV426 (from Aliens), the prison planet (from Alien³) and the derelict spaceship (from Alien). Each section consists of about 10 missions. In every mission, certain goals must be accomplished to continue. These include killing a certain number of enemies, finding items or activating switches.

Enemies include everything the Alien life cycle provides: facehuggers, chestbursters, warrior aliens, dog aliens (from Alien³) and Alien queens, one of which waits in the final mission of every section. In addition to the Aliens, you also have to fight employees of the Company, who have either been infected by the Aliens and are beyond saving or who actively want to obstruct your mission.

Weapons to be used include pistol, shotgun, pulse rifle, flame thrower and smart gun. Ammunition, health upgrades and other useful items are scattered throughout the levels. Hidden areas may be uncovered by using explosives like grenades and seismic charges. An auto mapping system helps in not getting lost, night goggles and shoulder lamps (running on battery power) allow you to see in the dark and the motion tracker tells you where your enemies are - but only if they are moving.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19960904T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Acclaim</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Alien Trilogy (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Alien Trilogy (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Alien Trilogy (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13109" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Alone in the Dark - Jack Is Back (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Alone in the Dark - Jack Is Back  </name>
    <desc>It is Christmas of 1924, three months after Alone in the Dark. "Supernatural Private Eye" Edward Carnby and his partner Ted Stryker are investigating the kidnapping of young Grace Saunders. The trail of clues leads to an old mansion named "Hell's Kitchen" - the home of an infamous gangster boss and his gang. Edward decides to pick up the trail when he learns of Ted's disappearance in the mansion. Unfortunately, Edward soon finds out that Ted has been murdered.nnCarnby eventually finds out that the mobsters are the corporeal forms of the spirits of pirates that plundered the sea hundreds of years ago, the lot having sold their souls in exchange for eternal life through voodoo magic. Fighting his way into the house and ultimately onto a pirate ship hidden in the cliff on which Jack's house is built, Edward must survive, discover the secret of the pirates' apparent immortality, rescue little Grace, and find out why the pirates are so interested in her.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960501T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Alone in the Dark - Jack Is Back (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Alone in the Dark - Jack Is Back (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Alone in the Dark - Jack Is Back (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13109" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Alone in the Dark - One-Eyed Jack's Revenge (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Alone in the Dark - One-Eyed Jack's Revenge </name>
    <desc>It is Christmas of 1924, three months after Alone in the Dark. "Supernatural Private Eye" Edward Carnby and his partner Ted Stryker are investigating the kidnapping of young Grace Saunders. The trail of clues leads to an old mansion named "Hell's Kitchen" - the home of an infamous gangster boss and his gang. Edward decides to pick up the trail when he learns of Ted's disappearance in the mansion. Unfortunately, Edward soon finds out that Ted has been murdered.nnCarnby eventually finds out that the mobsters are the corporeal forms of the spirits of pirates that plundered the sea hundreds of years ago, the lot having sold their souls in exchange for eternal life through voodoo magic. Fighting his way into the house and ultimately onto a pirate ship hidden in the cliff on which Jack's house is built, Edward must survive, discover the secret of the pirates' apparent immortality, rescue little Grace, and find out why the pirates are so interested in her.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Alone in the Dark - One-Eyed Jack's Revenge (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Alone in the Dark - One-Eyed Jack's Revenge (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Alone in the Dark - One-Eyed Jack's Revenge (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13255" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Amok (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Amok </name>
    <desc>Amok portrays a futuristic storyline on a planet which is identified in the manual as having the same name. There, two gigantic corporations, referred to by the acronyms NONLUN and AZTK, had previously been having an all-out war between them for forty-seven years. The war had involved all possible fronts and theaters, including operations in the air, on the surface of the land and sea, and beneath the water. Very recently, a weak peace accord had only just been reached. In the manual, the peace accord is described as being much like "a blanket covering the fire that smolders in the hearts of the people." The agreement is sufficiently unsteady that an influential mercenary company, known only as "the Bureau," has now decided to hire a capable battle walker pilot named Gert Staun to restart the war so they can continue to make large amounts of money by taking lucrative contracts from both sides. The player takes the role of Gert Staun.

Naturally "the Bureau" has placed a high priority on this, and they are funding it entirely on their own. Indeed, Gert Staun's battle walker, called the "Slambird" is explicitly said to be custom-modified. In particular, the Slambird can not only survive either on land or underwater, but it can transition between the two -- it can move, fight, and safely control its vertical position in either environment. These abilities are portrayed as costly and not standard to such vehicles in the universe where Amok takes place. The transformation of the Slambird between an underwater vehicle and a land vehicle is automatically scripted, however. The player  has no power to control this transformation or alter the time when it happens. Instead, the player must get to the point when Staun will automatically bring the Slambird ashore to continue his attacks.

The object of this arcade-type game is to meet a series of objectives, and to do so in such a way that each side will blame the other. The game has a linear structure, based on levels that present tasks of increasing difficulty, and all sorts of hazards and targets are encountered. These include military bases, power generators, land mines, infantry, tanks, submarines -- even sharks and huge, aggressive birds. Infantry elements are poorly armored, so they can be killed by being run over. In one mission, the only way that the player will be able to get enough time to escape is to open with a surprise attack, slowing pursuit by destroying a parking facility full of unattended troop transport vehicles. Power-ups are scattered throughout the levels. The Slambird carries a variety of explosive devices and line-of-sight weapons. Some of the explosive weapons can bounce in a parabolic trajectory, and in addition there are two laser cannons that can fire rapidly an unlimited number of times. These cannons are useful in case no other weapons remain, and they can be used to create complex ripple fire, which can be used to cover an area that is surprisingly wide. When underwater, propellers are used, while torpedoes are automatically used instead of missiles.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Scavenger</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Amok (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Amok (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Amok (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13157" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Area 51 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Area 51 </name>
    <desc>This is the home port of the popular arcade light gun game. This home version has special bonuses and additional secret levels not found in the arcade. Using a light gun (or a mouse, if available) you blast your way through the secret base, Area 51, which has been taken over by mutant aliens.

As you work your way to the secrets at the heart of Area 51, you'll need to destroy an increasingly dangerous line of aliens, upgrade your firearm, and cause as much collateral damage as possible. The game rewards the player for destroying windows, light fixtures, computers, explosive barrels, and even fire extinguishers. Each consecutive hit increases your streak rating (which adds to your score) and certain combinations of these collateral hits will open up secret bonus rooms.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19970314T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mesa Logic</developer>
    <publisher>Midway</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Area 51 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Area 51 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Area 51 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13116" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Astal (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Astal </name>
    <desc>Antowas has created a land of striking beauty and magic, with Astal and his beloved Leda among its happy inhabitants. However, Jerado has set out to destroy it, capturing Leda and forcing Astal to set off to save her.

Astal is a side-scrolling platform game with lots of Anime-esque background detail. You have birds helping you if you can rescue them. Special moves such as a smart bomb can be collected.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19950427T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Astal (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Astal (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Astal (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13194" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Athlete Kings (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Athlete Kings </name>
    <desc>Athlete Kings is a conversion of the 1995 Sega coin-op Decathlete in which you get to compete in all 10 events involved in a Decathlon. The game is split into two modes. First is the Decathlon mode itself in which you can play through all 10 events in standard order. 

Points are awarded for your performance in each event and, when completed, you will be rewarded with your final decathlon score. There is also Arcade Mode which, unsurprisingly, is a straight port of the arcade game. 
In this you can select which of 5 events you want to play from day one but must achieve a qualifying mark on that event in order to progress. Once you've qualified from all five events you then move on to the next five in day 2.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Athlete Kings (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Athlete Kings (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Athlete Kings (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1536</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13098" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Atlantis - The Lost Tales (Europe) (En,De,Es).m3u</path>
    <name>Atlantis - The Lost Tales  </name>
    <desc>Atlantis: The Lost Tales is a 1997 fantasy adventure video game developed and published by Cryo Interactive. Interplay Productions published the game in North America, where it released on September 30, 1997. The game is named after its initial and most important setting, Atlantis. It is the first in a Myst-like series, and was followed by Atlantis II (Beyond Atlantis outside Europe), Atlantis III: The New World (Beyond Atlantis II), Atlantis Evolution and The Secrets of Atlantis: The Sacred Legacy.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Cryo Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Cryo Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Atlantis - The Lost Tales (Europe) (En,De,Es).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Atlantis - The Lost Tales (Europe) (En,De,Es).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Atlantis - The Lost Tales (Europe) (En,De,Es).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13286" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Baku Baku Animal - World Zookeeper Contest (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Baku Baku Animal - World Zookeeper Contest </name>
    <desc>The Minister approaches the King to tell him that his only daughter, the Princess, wants a new pet. But the King says she already has too many, and she can't take care of so many animals. Thus the Minister purposes a contest of skill and daring to select the Royal Zookeeper. Master Piggy then sends his pupil, Polly, to participate in the contest.

Baku Baku Animal is a variation on the very often copied Tetris type of game. The game has three different play modes: practice, normal and hard. It also can be played by two players against each other (except for the Master System version).

The objective is to pair animal heads with their respective food. If a rabbit head comes falling, you must make it fall on a pile of carrot tiles, dog heads with bones, panda heads with bamboos and monkey heads with bananas. There is a bonus item, the "BB coin", which will appear from times to times, and remove piled tiles from the playfield. Removed tiles will be sent to the opponent's playfield all at once, increasing the difficulty of the task. Polly will face several contestants, and she'll win when her opponents get their playfield piled to the top.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960501T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Baku Baku Animal - World Zookeeper Contest (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Baku Baku Animal - World Zookeeper Contest (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Baku Baku Animal - World Zookeeper Contest (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13180" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Batman Forever - The Arcade Game (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Batman Forever - The Arcade Game </name>
    <desc>It's a fight to the finish as Batman and Robin take on the dark side of Gotham City's underworld! Power-Up with devastating special moves and gadgets, then master the unique combo system which allows up to 400 hits! Batman Forever the Arcade Game - 100% computer-rendered street brawling arcade action!</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19961116T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Acclaim</developer>
    <publisher>Iguana Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Batman Forever - The Arcade Game (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Batman Forever - The Arcade Game (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Batman Forever - The Arcade Game (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13267" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Arena Toshinden Remix (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Battle Arena Toshinden Remix </name>
    <desc>Toshinden Remix or Toshinden S as it was called in Japan is a port of Takara's Playstation fighting game Battle Arena Toshinden to the Sega Saturn by Sega.

It adds an additional secret character as well as a story mode for each character. These additions also hint at some of the plot twists in the game's sequel Battle Arena Toshinden 2.

The games graphics took a huge hit in the port; the Playstation version really does look considerably better. Though the character model and arena for the afore mentioned port exclusive character looks notably better than the ported graphics.

Toshinden Remix also redubs all the games voice samples with more light-hearted samples with over the top and arguably outrageous accents.

Like the graphics, the game speed also takes a huge hit in this port running considerably slower than the Playstation original.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19960327T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tamsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Takara</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Battle Arena Toshinden Remix (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Battle Arena Toshinden Remix (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Battle Arena Toshinden Remix (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13308" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Arena Toshinden URA - Ultimate Revenge Attack (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Battle Arena Toshinden URA - Ultimate Revenge Attack </name>
    <desc>The Toshinden Tournament is over. Through the battles some of the fighters have uncovered much about the shadowy events surrounding their lives. But the others now head home with little more than a few bruises and unfulfilled dreams. None of them, however, are aware that a new battle is about to begin. 
 
Throughout the world, martial arts experts are disappearing. Police from various nations are cooperating in an international manhunt to find the criminal responsible for the murders. Yet no motive has been established, and there is little evidence available. A wave of terror has struck the world, and now even the strongest and bravest of fighters are not safe. 
 
The former contestants of the Toshinden Tournament find themselves in a world gone mad. It is not inconceivable that one of them is responsible for the current chaos. But who is behind the disappearances, and for what purpose? All of the fighters came to the Toshinden Tournament for different reasons, but they are all fighting for the same reason now: SURVIVAL.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19970206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Takara</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Fight-Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Battle Arena Toshinden URA - Ultimate Revenge Attack (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Battle Arena Toshinden URA - Ultimate Revenge Attack (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Battle Arena Toshinden URA - Ultimate Revenge Attack (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13380" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Monsters (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Battle Monsters </name>
    <desc>Try to gain control of the underworld in BATTLE MONSTERS. You must choose from a variety of monsters, and then enter one-on-one combat. Twelve characters are available (from a human/bird hybrid to a headless creature) with each having its own set of special moves, like juggling opponents in the air, and pit monster against monster. Fight through several different places where each level's background is made up of multiple levels, allowing combatants to jump from one platform to another with two attack buttons and two jump buttons controlling the action.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Naxat Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Battle Monsters (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Battle Monsters (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Battle Monsters (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="143865" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Stations (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Battle Stations </name>
    <desc>Battlestations is a title where you take control of your own fleet, ranging from patrol boats and mine layers to battleships and aircraft carriers. You'll get to pick any of the ten missions right away, all of which have a different challenge to encounter, like protecting your base from troop transports, and a mission where you'll have to prevent poachers from killing whales. You'll also get to pick from five commanders to fight against, all of which have stereotypical strengths and weaknesses. Afterwards, you'll go right to the mission, where you'll be able to navigate your ship silhouettes on a 2D, radar-esque map.</desc>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <releasedate>19970521T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Battle Stations (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Battle Stations (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Battle Stations (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13420" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./BattleSport (USA).chd</path>
    <name>BattleSport </name>
    <desc>Battlesport simulates the sport of the future. Choose your vehicle and enter the arena to face your computer opponents to see who scores the most goals before the clock runs out.

Scoring isn't easy. The ball constantly bounces over the arena, retrieved by a player constantly bombarded by opponents. A variety of weapons are available to shoot your competitor, and anyone that takes a hit while carrying the ball loses possession, sending the ball bouncing across the arena. Taking too many shots results in a temporary inability to take part in the action while your opponent happily scores goals. 

Winning matches increases standing in the rankings and the acquisition of cash to purchase a better vehicle and enhanced offensive or defensive items.</desc>
    <releasedate>19970702T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Panasonic</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/BattleSport (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/BattleSport (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/BattleSport (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1536</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13361" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Black Dawn (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Black Dawn </name>
    <desc>Black Dawn fulfills a few childhood dreams by putting gamers in control of a military helicopter. Terrorists have grown powerful in the world and it is up to you to restore stability and peace throughout the lands. Assigned to a variety of campaigns, you must fly the AH-69 Mohawk (sounds like something Jan-Michael Vincent from AIRWOLF would pilot) as you battle through enemy territory across different global locales.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Point of View</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Black Dawn (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Black Dawn (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Black Dawn (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13395" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Black Fire (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Black Fire </name>
    <desc>In Black Fire, the player takes control of the most sophisticated helicopter on the planet taking on a very dangerous enemy.  The player's helicopter is state of the art, but the enemy they are fighting has acquired alien technology and is using it to try and conquer the world and it is up to the player to use all the flying skill they have and try to stop them.

Black Fire is rendered in 3-D and has a 360 degree field to maneuver.  The chopper is outfitted with missiles and machine guns and flies through 15 levels, destroying enemy targets and providing support to allied units with the story told through CGI cutscenes.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Novalogic</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Various</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Black Fire (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Black Fire (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Black Fire (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Blast Chamber (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Blast Chamber </name>
    <desc>A quite weird puzzle/actiongame in 3d, where you are a little guy in a chamber which is rotatable by pushing around the corners. Objects will fall down then and some other parts of the level get accesible.

The game also supports a 2 player competitive mode, where you have to pick up objects and put them in another one's crystal. Try to avoid the other to get to his crystal by moving around the chamber.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19961220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Attention To Detail</developer>
    <publisher>Activision</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Blast Chamber (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Blast Chamber (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Blast Chamber (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13238" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Blazing Heroes (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Blazing Heroes </name>
    <desc>Mystaria: The Realms of Lore, originally released as Riglordsaga in Japan, is a strategy game developed by Sega and Microcabin for the Sega Saturn. Two versions of the game were released in the US: one titled Mystaria: The Realms of Lore and the other as Blazing Heroes. 
 
Mystaria, once a land of peace and serenity, is now embroiled in turmoil. The evil Lord Bane and his ruthless band of marauders have overtaken the four kingdoms that rule this land. Now you must rely on the special powers of a Prince, a Ninja, a Lion man and others to reclaim your kingdoms and regain control of this beautiful land you once called your own! Breathtaking 3D graphics plus changing views and perspectives pull you into the action. Characters learn special attacks with each battle - over 250 attacks in all! Use a vast array of spells in your quest to conquer the evil Lord Bane and over 50 monsters and enemies.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19950721T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>MicroCabin</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Blazing Heroes (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Blazing Heroes (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Blazing Heroes (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13272" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Brain Dead 13 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Brain Dead 13 </name>
    <desc>In Braindead 13, the player takes on the role of a young computer expert who one day is called to fix a computer at some scary castle and in no time flat, finds himself in trouble.

It is up to the player to use the complex moves of an interactive movie to escape from the castle. This animated adventure is basically based on the player's judgment on which direction you think the character might go, and if the player guesses wrong, death.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>ReadySoft</developer>
    <publisher>ReadySoft</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Brain Dead 13 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Brain Dead 13 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Brain Dead 13 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13366" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bubble Bobble also featuring Rainbow Islands (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Bubble Bobble also featuring Rainbow Islands </name>
    <desc>Bubble Bobble: One or two players attempt to save their friends in this re-release of the 1987 classic puzzle/action game. Players blow bubbles to trap enemies. When they pop the bubbles, fruit comes out and the players compete for the points. If they don't pop the bubbles in time, the enemies escape and become faster.

Rainbow Islands: one player only. Rainbow Islands is the sequel to Bubble Bobble. Instead of bubbles, you create rainbows. The highly versatile rainbow can be used as bridges, as platforms, or as a weapon. You can shoot a rainbow at an enemy, you can trap it inside, or you can drop a rainbow on an enemy from above.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Compilation</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Bubble Bobble also featuring Rainbow Islands (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Bubble Bobble also featuring Rainbow Islands (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Bubble Bobble also featuring Rainbow Islands (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>3840</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13193" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bug Too! (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Bug Too! </name>
    <desc>Bug Too! is the sequal to Bug, a Sega Saturn game that was ported to the PC.  Bug Too! Is a 3rd person action/adventure platformer, and has lots of console-style play mechanics. You play as Bug and his two sidekicks, SuperFly and Maggot Dog. You go through several 3D worlds, all of which are parodies of movies. You must defeat the themed villans through all of the environments to make your homeland safe again!</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970424T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Bug Too! (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Bug Too! (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Bug Too! (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13112" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bug! (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Bug! </name>
    <desc>Bug's creepy-crawly insect friends need rescuing from the evil widow Queen Cadavra's clutches. Fight your way through six worlds to rescue them and find and defeat the spider queen. There are three levels to get through in each world of 3D platform action. Bug's key attack is his bug bounce but he can also somersault, spit and zap when powered up. The game also includes some simple puzzle elements.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Bug! (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Bug! (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Bug! (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13160" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Burning Rangers (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Burning Rangers </name>
    <desc>As a member of the Burning Rangers, it is your job to put out a range of fires and rescue those trapped in the heat of the blaze.

During each level, your quad leader informs you of the critical areas inside certain buildings, such as multi-level warehouses.
Following his advice, you must use your cybernetic powersuit to put out the flames in each area. Along the way you will also come across boss characters, who are out to light up the town, and you.
Your performance is then rated on your time to complete the objectives, how many lives were saved, and so forth. The better you go, the higher the rating.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19980315T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Burning Rangers (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Burning Rangers (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Burning Rangers (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13186" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition </name>
    <desc>Bust-A-Move 2: Arcade Edition, known in Japan as Puzzle Bobble 2X is the sequel to the arcade version of Bust-A-Move. Like its prequel, Bust-A-Move 2 also started life out in the arcades, but was brought to home consoles including the Sega Saturn in 1996. Bust-A-Move 2 adds staples to the series such as the branching, tournament-style gameplay when playing against the computer. There is also a level editor.nnDespite its name, Bust-A-Move 2: Arcade Edition is an slight upgrade on the standard Bust-A-Move 2 released for other consoles. It includes an alternative set of levels as well as the original</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Bust-A-Move 2 - Arcade Edition (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13336" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bust-A-Move 3 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Bust-A-Move 3 </name>
    <desc>Link 3 or more colored bubbles by shooting an identical colored bubble. When they are joined together, they pop.

This game completely abandons the idea of previous titles that the playfield is being pushed down by some sort of mechanical device and instead attaches groups of bubbles to nodes that move downwards. When a node is no longer connected to any bubbles it will disappear and when all nodes in a level have vanished the level is complete. One result of this change that may appear strange to players of previous versions is that shooting a bubble to the top of the visible playfield without striking any bubbles causes it to bounce and start travelling back downwards. The player is not penalised if such bubbles again leave the playing field without attaching to anything (except for adding to the number of moves until the field is pushed down by one empty line).</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Bust-A-Move 3 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Bust-A-Move 3 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Bust-A-Move 3 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13249" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Casper (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Casper </name>
    <desc>Based on the Casper film, the game pits you in the role of the friendly ghost trying to make a friend and a second chance at life instead of scaring everyone away.

The plot centers around the "spoiled, grasping inheritor of Whipstaff Manor" - Carrigan Crittenden.  She's after the treasure she thinks is hidden in the walls.  Casper will need the help of Dr James Harvey - therapist to the dead - if he has any hope of succeeding in his adventures.

Casper will also have to deal with his uncles - Stretch, Stinkie and Fatso, who just love to scare "Fleshies" and thwart Casper's efforts.  The gameplay is 3d - and is mostly puzzle solving, with Casper able to take a variety of forms and manipulating objects.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19960913T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Funcom</developer>
    <publisher>Interplay</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Casper (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Casper (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Casper (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13430" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Center Ring Boxing (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Center Ring Boxing </name>
    <desc>Center Ring Boxing is an unlicensed 3-D polygon boxing game where the player can choose from 30 different male or female boxers and compete in six different weight divisions.  They may also create their own boxer and use them to rise through the ranks to become champion choosing from one of five distinct styles of boxing.

There is also a trainer by the name of Snake that will help train the player as they progress thorough the game as well as become a selectable character along with a hidden character in two-player versus mode once the player becomes heavyweight champion.  A practice mode also is present that will allow the player to get accustomed to the game's controls and features 12 different camera angles and a replay mode that will the player to view their previous fight in it's entirety.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>JVC</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Boxing-Various-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Center Ring Boxing (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Center Ring Boxing (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Center Ring Boxing (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1540</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13344" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Chaos Control (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Chaos Control  </name>
    <desc>Chaos Control has seen three separate releases on the Saturn. Its original Japanese incarnation, Chaos Control was released in December 1995 to mixed views from critics. When brought to Europe in 1996, many of the underlying issues were addressed, leading to faster load times, improved graphics and cutscenes, and support for the Virtua Gun. It was then re-released in Japan as Chaos Control Remix in November of that year. No versions of the game were ever released in North America.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19960901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Infogrames</developer>
    <publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Chaos Control (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Chaos Control (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Chaos Control (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13240" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Christmas NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Christmas NiGHTS into Dreams... </name>
    <desc>Christmas NiGHTS into Dreams is a one level themed "demo" of NiGHTS into Dreams. It was originally released in November 1996 for the Sega Saturn.nnDue to its freebie nature, Christmas NiGHTS is a much smaller game than NiGHTS into Dreams - there is only one level (Spring Valley - almost identical to the level seen in regular NiGHTS) however unlike the original it is playable as Elliot as well as Claris. When playing as Elliot the stage is mirrored.nnChristmas NiGHTS is Christmas-themed, and so its graphics and music have been replaced with winter-esque versions of the original stage (but only in winter). For example, Ideya Captures are now giant floating Christmas trees, and NiGHTS wears red attire rather than purple. Gameplay is largely identical to the original game, including the A-Life system altered by defeating enemies.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19961114T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Christmas NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Christmas NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Christmas NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13155" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Clockwork Knight - Pepperouchau's Adventure (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Clockwork Knight - Pepperouchau's Adventure </name>
    <desc>Clockwork Knight is a game that depicts the sometimes friendly, sometimes combative, secret lives of toys. Betsy has a huge number of toys that come to life in the absence of humans and normally play nicely with each other. In the opening introduction, the somewhat inept clockwork knight Pepperouchau is competing with some other knights for the affections of a princess who lives in the clock. Everyone is having a grand time until a rogue toy shows up through the air vent, absconds with the princess, and turns many of the other toys against Pepperouchau.

The gameplay consists of side scrolling action through various stages constructed of elaborate series of toys, traps, and common household items. The first stage is a quest through Betsy's room with lots of letter blocks, sharp crayons, and dollhouses precariously balanced on robots that tend to fall on you. Pepperouchau is armed with a key sword that has offensive use as well as the ability to open boxes that functions as warps to other areas. The second stage takes place in Betsy's brother's room. Kevin has a lot of engineering skill and has built an impressive network of cranes and trains that Pepperouchau will need to activate in order to clear the area. Watch out for the jet transformer boss at the end of the room.

Other stages include missions through other areas of the house including the kitchen and the attic. Throughout the game you also collect coins. 20 coins are worth a continue when you run out of lives. Further, you meet other friendly toys between levels who give you the opportunity to gamble with your earned coins.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19950708T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>AM7</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Clockwork Knight - Pepperouchau's Adventure (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Clockwork Knight - Pepperouchau's Adventure (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Clockwork Knight - Pepperouchau's Adventure (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13200" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Clockwork Knight 2 - Pepperouchau's Adventure (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Clockwork Knight 2 - Pepperouchau's Adventure </name>
    <desc>Clockwork Knight 2 is the second (and to this date, last) game featuring the adventures of Sir Tongara de Pepperouchau III. It maintains the same game style (a mixture of 2D side-scrolling platformer with 3D elements, moderately in the fashion of Sega Saturn's Bug!), colorful music and gameplay of its predecessor. However, your mission will be somewhat different this time (although still related with Clockwork Princess Chelsea), as the ending scene of the first game did not come as good as expected and because of that, you should try to give the best of yourself again in order to completely recover Chelsea for Pepperouchau.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19951027T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Clockwork Knight 2 - Pepperouchau's Adventure (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Clockwork Knight 2 - Pepperouchau's Adventure (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Clockwork Knight 2 - Pepperouchau's Adventure (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13106" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 1) (GDI Disc).chd</path>
    <name>Command &amp; Conquer   </name>
    <desc>Command &amp; Conquer developed ideas from Westwood's previous Dune 2, forming a real time strategy game which has influenced many. The control system of selecting units with the mouse and then directing them is similar to future titles such as Total Annihilation.

The game focuses on a war between two organizations, The Brotherhood of Nod and the Global Defense Initiative. You can take control of either side for more than 15 missions. Both have different units and structures, including artillery, tanks and light infantry.

In most missions you have to build a base first to build new units and structures. Most important are the special harvesters, which collect Tiberium and deliver it to a refinery, where it's converted into money - money which is needed to create additional units.

The game also features FMV mission briefings and victory cutscenes.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19961206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Westwood Studios</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 1) (GDI Disc).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 1) (GDI Disc).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 1) (GDI Disc).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13106" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 2) (NOD Disc).chd</path>
    <name>Command &amp; Conquer   </name>
    <desc>Command &amp; Conquer developed ideas from Westwood's previous Dune 2, forming a real time strategy game which has influenced many. The control system of selecting units with the mouse and then directing them is similar to future titles such as Total Annihilation.

The game focuses on a war between two organizations, The Brotherhood of Nod and the Global Defense Initiative. You can take control of either side for more than 15 missions. Both have different units and structures, including artillery, tanks and light infantry.

In most missions you have to build a base first to build new units and structures. Most important are the special harvesters, which collect Tiberium and deliver it to a refinery, where it's converted into money - money which is needed to create additional units.

The game also features FMV mission briefings and victory cutscenes.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19961206T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Westwood Studios</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 2) (NOD Disc).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 2) (NOD Disc).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Command &amp; Conquer (USA) (Disc 2) (NOD Disc).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13356" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Courier Crisis - The Saga of the Modern Fatalist (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Courier Crisis - The Saga of the Modern Fatalist </name>
    <desc>You are the anti-mailman. A slacker courier with a goatee and a BMX-rated attitude. A psycho bike messenger thrashing through the concrete jungle. Pummel pedestrians. Rip stunts. Earn cash. Deliver the goods. And don't be late.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>BMG Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Courier Crisis - The Saga of the Modern Fatalist (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Courier Crisis - The Saga of the Modern Fatalist (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Courier Crisis - The Saga of the Modern Fatalist (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13288" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Crimewave (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Crimewave  </name>
    <desc>Crimewave is a fast and frantic driving-based shoot-em-up. You will need first class driving and combat skills coupled with razor-sharp reflexes to enjoy features which include: Eight high-powered vehicles; Eight battle zones; A vast array of High destruction weaponry; Single player and split-screen action.</desc>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <releasedate>19961108T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Crimewave (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Crimewave (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Crimewave (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13432" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Criticom (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Criticom </name>
    <desc>Criticom is a one-on-one fighting game where 8 diverse fighters from across the galaxy vie for a crystal artifact. The game features a sci-fi backstory that involves mystery and intrigue surrounding the crystal and each of the 8 fighters is given a unique storyline to explain why he or she is so interested in the artifact. Among the colorful characters are a giant lizard man named Gorm, a ninja lady named Yenji, a killing robot named S.I.D., and a mysterious vampire-like creature named Demonica who places little value on clothing.

The fighting action takes place on a round, elevated platform. Each fighter begins the fight with a full power meter and one power meter refill in reserve that is activated when the primary meter is depleted. Thus, there are no rounds. The fight runs until one fighter is knocked out (no more power in their meter), one is knocked out of the arena (or steps/jumps out), or the time runs out.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tokai Engineering</developer>
    <publisher>Kronos</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Criticom (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Criticom (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Criticom (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13124" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Croc - Legend of the Gobbos (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Croc - Legend of the Gobbos </name>
    <desc>All is not well in Croc's world. His friends, the Gobbos, have been captured by the evil Baron Dante. It is your mission in this 3D platformer to search through 42 different levels to save all of your friends before it's too late.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19971124T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
    <publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Croc - Legend of the Gobbos (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Croc - Legend of the Gobbos (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Croc - Legend of the Gobbos (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13131" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Crusader - No Remorse (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Crusader - No Remorse </name>
    <desc>Crusader: No Remorse is an action game developed by Origin Systems and published by Electronic Arts. It was first released in 1995 for the PC DOS, with the Sony PlayStation and Sega Saturn ports following in 1997. Set in a dystopian world of 22nd century, the games center on an elite supersoldier that defects from the tyrannical world government, the World Economic Consortium (WEC), and joins the Resistance rebels. 
 
Critically well-received, No Remorse was followed by the PC-only sequel Crusader: No Regret in 1996.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970314T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
    <publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Crusader - No Remorse (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Crusader - No Remorse (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Crusader - No Remorse (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13350" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Cyber Speedway (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Cyber Speedway </name>
    <desc>Cyber Speedway is a hover sled racing game set in the distant future.  The civilizations of many planets have decided to end all wars.  Instead, they will settle their differences in the Cyber Race.  You are the best hope to protect and expand the Earth's power.

Cyber Speedway's main game is the story mode.  The story follows your character as he qualifies as Earth's driver, and makes his way through a series of planetary races to become the champion.  In each of the races, you must place first to continue.

Each race consists of 5 laps around a high-speed track.  You have missiles you can use to slow down your opponents and take the lead.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Cyber Speedway (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Cyber Speedway (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Cyber Speedway (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13258" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Cyberia (USA) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Cyberia  </name>
    <desc>In the year 2027 the world is controlled by two rival super-powers, the western-bloc Free World Alliance and the east-bloc Cartel.

Transmissions from an FWA spy reveal the location of a secret multi-national labratory deep within Siberia, the "Cyberia Complex", where a mysterious weapon is being developed. FWA leader Devlin frees a cyber-hacker named Zak from prison and sends him to infiltrate the complex and discover the true nature of the Cyberia weapon.

Unfortunately, the Cartel is also interested in the weapon and will stop at nothing to get it. Not only must Zak make his way past the Cartel forces sent to stop him, but he must also overcome the Cartel agents which have already seized control of the complex. To make matters worse the Cyberian scientist's genetically engineered creations are running rampant in the same area as the weapon, and Devlin also appears to be have something up his sleeve.</desc>
    <rating>1</rating>
    <releasedate>19960419T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Xatrix</developer>
    <publisher>Interplay</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Cyberia (USA) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Cyberia (USA) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Cyberia (USA) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13256" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Darius Gaiden (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Darius Gaiden </name>
    <desc>Take command of your Silverhawk fighters once again as you battle to take back the planet Darius from the evil forces that had overpowered it! Converted from the Taito 1994 arcade game for the Windows platform (9x and NT).</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19951215T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Darius Gaiden (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Darius Gaiden (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Darius Gaiden (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13301" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Darius II (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Darius II </name>
    <desc>Darius II takes place sometime after the first Darius game. The colonized planet Darius is recuperating from its invasion from the alien Belser Army thanks to that game's heroes Proco and Tiat. Darius' inhabitants have since situated themselves on the planet Olga while Darius' societies, architecture and attacked areas were being repaired. The space flight Headquarters established on Olga picks up an SOS signal coming from Earth, where the first colonists originated before colonizing Darius. The signal included the description of alien ships similar to those of the Belser Army. Suspecting that these might be their remaining Earthling ancestors, the people of Darius sends both Proco Jr. and Tiat Young to help them.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Darius II (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Darius II (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Darius II (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13162" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dark Savior (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Dark Savior </name>
    <desc>You take the role of Garian as he searches for Bilan, an escaped prisoner. Explore more than 300 lush, 3D environments and solve a variety of puzzles. Once some puzzles have been unraveled, new weapons and items become available. Those objects and artillery are most useful against the monsters and enemies Garian will encounter. When fighting breaks out, Garian will have to defeat an enemy in a three-round fight. Over 8 different endings!</desc>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <releasedate>19970220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Climax</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Dark Savior (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Dark Savior (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Dark Savior (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13303" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Darklight Conflict (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv).chd</path>
    <name>Darklight Conflict  </name>
    <desc>A space combat game like Wing Commander; you control  space ship, as the lone man trying to save humanity from not one, but two alien races. It also has multiplayer modes like Race and Tag for IPX network users.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970701T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rage Software</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Darklight Conflict (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Darklight Conflict (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Darklight Conflict (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Sv).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13204" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Daytona USA - Championship Circuit Edition (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Daytona USA - Championship Circuit Edition </name>
    <desc>All of its predecessor and then some. More tracks, many more cars (hidden cars as well), smarter AI, more music (no more lyrics for the in-game race music either), broader 2-player gameplay, more refined arcade physics...and on top of everything else- BETTER GRAPHICS! The first Daytona on the Saturn boasted some hefty visuals, great for displaying the Saturn's power to the masses at the console's birth; but for the Saturn to be revered for everything it was, Sega (and AM2) had to make something a little flashier. All the graphics in the game have been updated...both the cars and tracks have higher polygon count, better texture mapping; the framerate is QUITE noticeably improved, everything is very smooth.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19961121T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Daytona USA - Championship Circuit Edition (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Daytona USA - Championship Circuit Edition (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Daytona USA - Championship Circuit Edition (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13122" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Daytona USA (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Daytona USA </name>
    <desc>A port of the most successful arcade racer ever, the home versions of Daytona USA include the same elements that made the original version successful: three highly detailed tracks, arcade driving physics that challenge the player to find the best trajectory to make a flying lap without kissing the rails and beating the checkpoint timer. The 40 cars of the Easy race (later named 3-7 Speedway), one of the stalwarts of the original version, are also present in this version.

These home versions include a new mode (Saturn or PC Mode, depending on the platform) where the three tracks are played without the timer, and optionally in mirror mode, using one of the bonus cars (with additional abilities such as driving on grass or hitting the rails without losing speed) and in one of three lengths: Normal (identical to the arcade original), Grand Prix (2.5 times longer) and Endurance (10 times longer). 

On the downside, detail and frame rate suffered a drop to fit the game into the limited hardware of the Saturn and Personal Computers, and lacking any kind of multiplayer, comparing to the two to eight player rumbles of the arcade version.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Daytona USA (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Daytona USA (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Daytona USA (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13091" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Deep Fear (Europe).m3u</path>
    <name>Deep Fear </name>
    <desc>All contact is lost with a submarine on a routine mission which then crashes into an underwater facility. The occupants of the underwater facility are ordered to board the submarine and find out what went wrong. On board the vessel, strange things are happening which are taking control of the crew. The crew are mutating due to an alien parasite and members of the search team have to figure out what is happening and how to stop it!

 The game is played via a third person view which is just behind the character and you look over his shoulder. The game is based underwater in a submarine so the developers have added a claustrophobic feeling by giving some areas a limited amount of air so you have to run through to activate the air circulation system. Controls are your typical Resident Evil style which is you pull the Right shoulder button to draw your gun, your d-pad to aim and then a button to shoot. Along your journey of the submarine, you will need to find objects such as keycards to unlock doors and better weapons.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19980918T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Deep Fear (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Deep Fear (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Deep Fear (Europe).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13321" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Defcon 5 (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Defcon 5 </name>
    <desc>In the far future, conflict is at an all-time low and outdated defence bases are being vacated and replaced with automated software. You play as an engineer sent to update one such base. Just after uploading the automating code, the base is suddenly invaded by unknown assailants from the air and ground. You must rely on your wits and the defence software to fend them off.

The main game takes place in a first-person view inside the complex. Trams connect the maze-like living areas to a handful of manned turrets outside. You must shuttle between shooting down waves of fighters in the turrets, and scouring the base levels for card keys during the down time.

A third consideration is the "Virtual Operating System" controlling all major base functions. You use this interface to repair damage from attacks, monitor intruders, and place robot sentries to guard key passages. As you find more access keys, you can increase the software's efficiency to the point that you can command turrets remotely, or set them to auto-attack with a high degree of success. 

As defending the base becomes more automated and efficient, you have more time to search the levels for keys. Your ultimate goal is to find the clearance to self-destruct the base, defend your escape shuttle, and get out alive.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Millennium Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Data East</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Defcon 5 (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Defcon 5 (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Defcon 5 (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13178" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Destruction Derby (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Destruction Derby </name>
    <desc>You probably feel like a crash test dummy when you're playing this game - it's not only a racing game, but you get points for wrecking your enemies! The amount of points you get depends on how you hit them ... e.g. you get more points for getting them do a 360 other than driving into theirs sides at high speed. The game has more to offer: a head to head mode with only two cars or the legendary destruction derby itself - a huge arena, every car starts at the edge of it, and then - have a nice crash!</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19960815T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Psygnosis</developer>
    <publisher>Reflections</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Destruction Derby (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Destruction Derby (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Destruction Derby (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13149" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Die Hard Arcade (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Die Hard Arcade </name>
    <desc>A conversion of Sega AM1's arcade 3D scrolling fighting game based on the first Die Hard movie. One or two players work their way up and down a skyscraper in attempting to rescue the President's kidnapped daughter.
A large number of fighting moves are available through the simple controls of punch, kick and jump, plus movement.
Many weapons are available from knives and broken bottles to machine guns and rocket launchers. Other objects can be picked up and used as weapons such as chairs, an aerosol and lighter combo and even a grandfather clock!
Between several of the stages are reaction tests that require a button to be pressed quickly, usually punch, kick or jump. Failure means an extra fight has to be won often with little or no reward in terms of items.
The climax sees the heroes fighting the mastermind (who has many swords on his person) on the roof of the skyscraper.
Also included is an old Sega arcade game, Deep Scan, used to gain extra credits for the main game.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19970318T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Die Hard Arcade (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Die Hard Arcade (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Die Hard Arcade (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13134" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Die Hard Trilogy (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Die Hard Trilogy </name>
    <desc>Die Hard Trilogy is split into three games, each game representing one of the movies, obviously.  

Die Hard 1 is a third person shooter in a style similar to Tomb Raider.  You are John McClane and must fight through twenty floors of terrorists in the Nakatomi Plaza.  The game has an invisible wall effect which allows you to see John even in small hallways.

Die Hard 2 is a first person rail shooter in the vein of Virtua Cop or Mad Dog McCree.  Once again you take the role of John  McClane firing upon terrorists who happen to be ransacking the Washington/Dulles Airport in search of a South American dictator and druglord.

Die Hard 3 is a fast-paced taxi racer through the city.  John must this time speed through New York City defusing bombs and ramming evildoers off the road behind the wheel of a cab.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving-Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Die Hard Trilogy (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Die Hard Trilogy (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Die Hard Trilogy (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13392" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Digital Pinball (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Digital Pinball </name>
    <desc>Digital Pinball: Last Gladiators , also referred to as simply Last Gladiators (in North America) or Digital Pinball (in Europe), is a pinball game developed by KAZe and released on the Sega Saturn in 1995. It is one of a number of video pinball games developed by KAZe, and directly follows the Super Pinball series on the Super Famicom. 
 
During development Digital Pinball was known as Pinball Arena: Last Gladiators. It was also once set to be published by U.S. Gold in North America as Fantasy Pinball 
 
A Japan-only sequel, Digital Pinball: The Necronomicon was released in 1996. In 1997, Last Gladiators received a Japan-only updated rerelease titled Digital Pinball: Last Gladiators Ver.9.7</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kaze</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Pinball-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Digital Pinball (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Digital Pinball (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Digital Pinball (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13206" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Discworld II - Missing Presumed...! (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Discworld II - Missing Presumed...!  </name>
    <desc>Discworld II: Missing Presumed...!? (Discworld II: Mortality Bytes! in North America) is the second point-and-click adventure game based on Terry Pratchett's series of fantasy novels set on the mythical Discworld. The game was developed and produced in 1996 by Perfect Entertainment for the PC, and ported in 1997 for the PlayStation and Sega Saturn. It was published by Psygnosis for the PC and PlayStation, and by Sega for the Saturn (only in Europe).</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Perfect World</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Discworld II - Missing Presumed...! (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Discworld II - Missing Presumed...! (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Discworld II - Missing Presumed...! (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13083" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Doom (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Doom </name>
    <desc>Doom (typeset as DOOM in official documents)[1] is a 1993 science fiction horror-themed first-person shooter (FPS) video game by id Software. It is considered one of the most significant and influential titles in the video game industry, for having ushered in the popularity of the first-person shooter genre. The original game was divided into three nine-level episodes and was distributed via shareware and mail order. The Ultimate Doom, an updated release of the original game featuring a fourth episode, was released in 1995 and sold at retail. 
 
In Doom, players assume the role of an unnamed space marine, who became popularly known as "Doomguy", fighting his way through hordes of invading demons from Hell.[2] With one third of the game, nine levels, distributed as shareware, Doom was played by an estimated 15â€“20 million people[3] within two years of its release, popularizing the mode of gameplay and spawning a gaming subculture. In addition to popularizing the FPS genre, it pioneered immersive 3D graphics, networked multiplayer gaming, and support for customized additions and modifications via packaged files in a data archive known as "WADs". As a sign of its effect on the industry, first-person shooter games from the genre's boom in the 1990s, helped in no small part by the game's release, became known simply as "Doom clones". Its graphic violence, as well as satanic imagery, made Doom the subject of controversy. 
 
The Doom franchise was later continued with the follow-up Doom II: Hell on Earth (1994) and numerous expansion packs, including Master Levels for Doom II (1995), and Final Doom (1996). Originally released for PC DOS, the games have later been ported to numerous other platforms. Once the game's source code was released in 1997, it spawned even more adaptations, as fans further ported the code to countless devices. The series started to lose mainstream appeal as the technology of the Doom game engine was surpassed in the mid-1990s, although fans have continued making WADs, speedruns, and modifications to the original. The franchise again received popular attention in 2004 with the release of Doom 3, a retelling of the original game using new technology, and an associated 2005 Doom motion picture. Doom 4 was announced as in production in 2008 and was later retitled simply as Doom</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rage Software</developer>
    <publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Doom (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Doom (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Doom (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13088" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dragon Force (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Dragon Force </name>
    <desc>Step forth brave warrior. The destiny of the world of Legendra lies solely in your hands. Play as one of eight warlords, each with a unique storyline, to conquer the evil forces of Madruk in this incredible role playing/strategy game.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19970801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SOJ</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Dragon Force (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Dragon Force (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Dragon Force (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13259" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./DragonHeart - Fire &amp; Steel (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>DragonHeart - Fire &amp; Steel  </name>
    <desc>Dragonheart: Fire and Steel was released to the public in 1996, and is a 2D side scrolling beat 'em up based off of the movie of the same name. Players take on the role of a retired knight who must return to action and remain true to the oaths he took long ago. An evil prince's tyranny threatens the land, and the knight (who was a former dragonslayer) can only defeat this scheming noble with the help of a friend who just happens to be the last surviving dragon on Earth.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Funcom</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/DragonHeart - Fire &amp; Steel (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/DragonHeart - Fire &amp; Steel (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/DragonHeart - Fire &amp; Steel (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13076" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Duke Nukem 3D (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Duke Nukem 3D </name>
    <desc>Aliens have landed in futuristic Los Angeles and it's up to the Duke to bring the pain and show them the door. After the initial entries of side-scrolling platform games, Duke Nukem 3D introduced a first-person perspective to the series and turned the game in a full-fledged shooter with 2.5D graphics.

Duke's arsenal includes pistols, pipe bombs, laser trip mines, Nordenfelt guns, a chain gun and various rocket launchers, but also his mighty foot to kick enemies. The game sports a high level of interactivity. Many objects in the environment can be broken or interacted with, such as pool tables, arcade machines, glass, light switches and security cameras. As a mature game, the protagonist is also able to hand strippers a dollars to have them remove their top.

The character, voiced by Jon St. John, also regularly delivers commentary on the events through one liners. There are 28 levels, divided over three episodes, set in locations such as streets, a church, a space station, a Japanese villa, a football field and many modern environments. Enemies mainly include aliens, mutated humans and members of the police force that have been turned into Pig Cops. Next to weapons, Duke also has access to medikits, steroids to enhance his speed, nightvision, protective boots, a hologram known as the holoduke, and a jet pack to reach higher areas. Most of the gameplay is action-oriented, but there is also an amount of puzzles needed to progress or access secret areas.

The game includes network play through the IPX protocol, for deathmatch and cooperative games.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Lobotomy Software</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter-Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Duke Nukem 3D (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Duke Nukem 3D (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Duke Nukem 3D (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13171" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Earthworm Jim 2 </name>
    <desc>An ordinary average earthworm named Jim goes about his normal daily life, cruising around avoiding crows and doing other general worm-like things. Jim is suddenly struck by a very large ultra- high- tech- indestructible- super- space- cyber- suit. Through sheer luck, Jim rests safely in the neck ring of the suit. 

Suddenly, the ultra-high-tech space particles of the suit begin interacting with Jim's soft wormy flesh. A radical light-speed evolution takes place.

Jim soon realizes he is in control of the suit.

Gameplay is similar to the first game, with Jim jumping and running through the levels. There are 5 weapons more than the original game to collect. Characters like Princess Whats-Her-Name and Psy-Crow appear.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19961001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Screaming Pink</developer>
    <publisher>Playmates Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13132" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Enemy Zero (Europe) (Disc 0) (Opening Disc).chd</path>
    <name>Enemy Zero   </name>
    <desc>Enemy Zero is one of the horror titles by Warp, closely connected to D (and its sequel D2 for Dreamcast). It also features the same heroine as in D series. 

The crew members of the spaceship Aki were in a state of suspended animation. All of a sudden, the ship emergency program woke them up. What has happened? Apparently, a hostile alien life form had penetrated the spaceship. Now Laura, the heroine of the game, has to establish contact with her comrades, finding her way through the maze-like corridors of the giant vessel. She will also have to defend herself against the aliens, which seem even more intimidating because they are totally invisible.

The game consists of two genres: puzzle-solving adventure and shooter. When you enter a room, the enemies can't attack you, and you can explore it from 1st person perspective, taking objects, and solving puzzles. When you wander through ship corridors, you enter the 1st person shooter mode. Since the enemies are invisible, you'll have to listen to the sounds they make. A high sound means an enemy is right in front of you; a mid-range sound means it is attacking from the side; a low-pitched noise tells you it is behind you. You can figure out the distance between you and the enemy by the intensity of the sound.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>WARP</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Enemy Zero (Europe) (Disc 0) (Opening Disc).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Enemy Zero (Europe) (Disc 0) (Opening Disc).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Enemy Zero (Europe) (Disc 0) (Opening Disc).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13132" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Enemy Zero (Europe).m3u</path>
    <name>Enemy Zero </name>
    <desc>Enemy Zero is one of the horror titles by Warp, closely connected to D (and its sequel D2 for Dreamcast). It also features the same heroine as in D series. 

The crew members of the spaceship Aki were in a state of suspended animation. All of a sudden, the ship emergency program woke them up. What has happened? Apparently, a hostile alien life form had penetrated the spaceship. Now Laura, the heroine of the game, has to establish contact with her comrades, finding her way through the maze-like corridors of the giant vessel. She will also have to defend herself against the aliens, which seem even more intimidating because they are totally invisible.

The game consists of two genres: puzzle-solving adventure and shooter. When you enter a room, the enemies can't attack you, and you can explore it from 1st person perspective, taking objects, and solving puzzles. When you wander through ship corridors, you enter the 1st person shooter mode. Since the enemies are invisible, you'll have to listen to the sounds they make. A high sound means an enemy is right in front of you; a mid-range sound means it is attacking from the side; a low-pitched noise tells you it is behind you. You can figure out the distance between you and the enemy by the intensity of the sound.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>WARP</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Enemy Zero (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Enemy Zero (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Enemy Zero (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13185" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Exhumed (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
    <name>Exhumed  </name>
    <desc>Destination: The ancient Egyptian city of Karnak. Alien forces possessing horrifying powers have sealed off the once thriving community from all outside contact. As a covert operations specialist, you have been trained for all forms of contingencies. Nothing can prepare you, however, for the nightmare you are about to enter. Twenty+ levels of non-stop gameplay through an ancient Egyptian city and the tomb of the pharaoh Ramses. Real-time fully 3D rendered gameplay allows you to move between multiple floors within a single level. Cross bridges, crawl through tunnels, and swim through underwater grottos.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Playmates Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Lobotomy Software</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Exhumed (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Exhumed (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Exhumed (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13268" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./F1 Challenge (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>F1 Challenge </name>
    <desc>F1 Challenge was the only Formula One title released on the SEGA Saturn, giving the player the opportunity to control five authentic Formula One cars and their drivers (Michael Schumacher, Damon Hill, Jean Alesi, Ukyo Katayama and Mika Häkkinen), with the ability to tweak their car before races, ranging from tire pressure, tire type, wing angle, etc.

There are six tracks to choose from: Hockenheim, Monte Carlo, Suzuka and three different configurations for a fictional track, Neo City, each with their own hairpin turns and fast straightaways. The player can choose from two behind the car views (no cockpit view is available) along with a pop-up screen that acts as a rear view mirror. Features a FOCA (Formula One Constructors Association) license which allows the use of thirteen teams with twenty-six drivers from the 1995 season from which the above mentioned five are the only ones playable.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960919T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/F1 Challenge (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/F1 Challenge (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/F1 Challenge (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13237" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Fighters Megamix (USA) (RE).chd</path>
    <name>Fighters Megamix  </name>
    <desc>Virtua Fighter 2 was full of many brand new gameplay elements implemented into the realistic fighting engine of the first Virtua Fighter.  The Virtua Fighter series has been heralded before as the fighting game with most involving gameplay.  

In Fighters Megamix, another game has been added, a game called Fighting Vipers.  Fighting Vipers has drastically different gameplay than the more popular Virtua Fighter 2.  Instead of being sophisticated, Fighting Vipers is simplified to appeal to a wider audience of video gamers and was meant for "casual" gamers.

Mixing a simplistic video game and a sophisticated video game must have been difficult.  But Fighters Megamix manages to do so by offering many options.  The most important option available is the choice of having Fighters Megamix run under the Fighting Vipers style of gameplay or the Virtua Fighter 2 style of gameplay.  Other options are unlockable while playing the game.

One good thing about mixing two games into one is that the game would include more selectable characters.  Not only are there the 22 characters from Virtua Fighter 2 and Fighting Vipers but there are also 10 other hidden characters that can be unlocked by playing well in the Saturn version, including two from the arcade-only Sonic the Fighters. There are only 4 characters from Virtua Fighter 2 and 4 from Fighting Vipers in the Game.Com version.

This game was one of the very last games to appear on the Sega Saturn in the United States and was directed by Yu Suzuki.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970513T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Fighters Megamix (USA) (RE).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Fighters Megamix (USA) (RE).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Fighters Megamix (USA) (RE).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13192" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Fighting Vipers (USA) (6S).chd</path>
    <name>Fighting Vipers  </name>
    <desc>Armstone City, year unknown. The Mayor decided to hold a fighting tournament with the grand finale being held on the top of the city tower, and the Vipers, young urban warriors decide to compete, each with their own goal on mind. All eight came from several backgrounds, like the hard-rocker Raxel, the orphan with a burning desire to meet his father Bahn, former gang leader Tokyo, queen of the catwalk Grace, the giant with an unknown past Sanman, construction worker and former marine trainee Jane, fashion designer to-be Candy and skater boy Picky, plus Mahler, someone with a score to settle with the Mayor.

While based on the same Model-2 arcade board as Virtua Fighter 2, Fighting Vipers included several changes, such as a wall surrounding the battle area and equipping each fighter with a two-piece (chest and legs) armour that can only be broken with power hits. Once the armour is gone, the unfortunate fighter is more vulnerable to opponent hits, and damage can also be collected after hitting the wall or floor after a throw. 

Gameplay is also radically different from Virtua Fighter - noticeably  faster, with combos done by fast button-mashing sequences sometimes on the same button, instead of the timed presses that require an additional push on the d-pad of the first title. Another new addition to gameplay is the Quick recovery, which allows a fighter that suffered a severe blow to quickly get on his feet, avoiding damage and allowing for a quick counter, but at the same time leaving him open for another blow if the opponent is fast enough. to react.

Game modes include Arcade, Vs, Team Battle (best of 9) and Training. Game options allow the player to tweak the difficulty setting, number of rounds before a match winner is decided, size of life bars, if there's a time limit, if the order of opponents is random or predefined and between three game modes: Original (based on the arcade version), Arrange (gameplay tweaked for the Sega Saturn) and Hyper (allows Vipers to voluntarily drop their armour, allowing to perform special attacks at lightening fast speeds), Stage selection, and to change the disposition of the control pad to better suit the players' style.

Another mode, Playback, allows to see rounds previously saved by the player or fighting demos recorded by the AM#2 staff, each with the ability to choose a camera. As usual with Sega's fighting ports, extensive bookkeeping is included, as well as a few hidden characters.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Fighting Vipers (USA) (6S).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Fighting Vipers (USA) (6S).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Fighting Vipers (USA) (6S).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13374" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Firestorm - Thunderhawk 2 (Europe) (En,Fr).chd</path>
    <name>Firestorm - Thunderhawk 2  </name>
    <desc>Your name is General John T. Maclaine and you are the pilot of Firestorm 1, the lead dog in special attack missions to various parts of the world. Your helicopter is extremely powerful and carries the following weapons: 30mm Chain Gun, Firestorm Homing Missile, Rocket Pod, Runaway Cratering System (bombs), the Mk-84 500-Pound Bomb, Cluster Bombs, and the Anti-Ship Missile. These weapons -- plus excellent evasive, and attack maneuvers -- should be enough to help you succeed in attacks on drug runners and terrorists, from Columbia to Iraq. 
 
Thunder Strike 2 is the sequel to Core's Amiga, ST, PC &amp; Sega CD game, AH-3 Thunderstrike. Like the previous game in the series, this is a helicopter simulator/shooter. It features realistic features like multiple weapons selection, full freedom of movement, and a mission-based structure. On the other hand, it also throws lots and lots of enemy tanks and helicopters at you to blow up.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
    <publisher>Core Design</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Firestorm - Thunderhawk 2 (Europe) (En,Fr).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Firestorm - Thunderhawk 2 (Europe) (En,Fr).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Firestorm - Thunderhawk 2 (Europe) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="152239" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Formula Karts - Special Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
    <name>Formula Karts - Special Edition  </name>
    <desc>Formula Karts, released for both Sega Saturn and PC, is a semi-realistic racing title that attempts to capture the spirit of kart racing with it's low slung feeling of speed, and corner after corner of impressive handling (and inevitable sliding). The title supports both simulation and arcade modes, and features some effective race AI for non-player vehicles.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970522T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Manic Media</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Formula Karts - Special Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Formula Karts - Special Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Formula Karts - Special Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13307" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Galactic Attack (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Galactic Attack </name>
    <desc>Galactic Attack is a coin-op conversion of the Japanese arcade game RayForce (GunLock for European arcades). A top-down shooter, there are seven levels to play, ranging from battles in the atmosphere of planets to battling over mountain ranges, each with their own standard huge bosses at the end of each of these levels. The player takes control of a starfighter called the RVA-818 X-LAY, out to destroy any opposing forces.

The story has the future of Earth governments gathering together to construct a massive super computer called Con-Human to help with the planet's environment, providing nutrients to the earth and caring for the ecosystem. However, a cloned human is linked with the system and makes Con-Human a sentient being. The system eventually becomes insane and starts to create natural disasters, wiping all nearly all of mankind and destroying the ecosystem, driving the survivors into space to develop colonies on other planets. Con-Human then makes Earth into a giant fortress and is assembling a massive armada to destroy the remaining survivors, but before it can attack, the survivors amass a first strike in order to reclaim the Earth.

The goal is to fly around in the level, using the primary laser weapon to destroy various enemies flying in and out of the screen.  Players can upgrade this weapon by collecting "L" icons floating around when enough enemies are destroyed.  There is also a secondary weapon, a lock-on missile launcher, that has the ability to fire upon eight different ground enemies at once.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Galactic Attack (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Galactic Attack (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Galactic Attack (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13154" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Gex (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Gex </name>
    <desc>Enter your television to defeat the evil Rez by collecting remotes to  open worlds inside your tv. 
You are a gecko with all the usual platform hero skills such as jump, fire and close range attack, but also suction cups to help you scale walls, a tongue to pick up those tricky to get power-ups
and plenty of wise-cracks to keep you amused. Use them all to make your way through TV land searching for the remotes, collecting pickups, power-ups and killing TVs.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
    <publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Gex (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Gex (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Gex (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13435" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ghen War (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Ghen War </name>
    <desc>Ghen War is a classic first-person shooter. The solar system is being attacked by an evil force of aliens known as Ghen. The player is a Lieutenant surface engineer in a hypersuit, and it is his task to boot these aliens out of your world in twenty levels. From the cockpit of this hypersuit, the character operates lasers, grenades, mines, missiles and more while making his way across planet surfaces and city environments protecting the human race. It also has a claw that can operate elements in the environment and can send out a decoy of itself to confuse opponents.

The game is also one of the first to feature deformable terrain. Explosions make craters and firing into the environment can make it wear away.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960426T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Jumpin' Jack Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Ghen War (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Ghen War (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Ghen War (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13168" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Golden Axe - The Duel (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Golden Axe - The Duel </name>
    <desc>Many years have passed since the last war with Death Adder. But, as memories of those dark times begin to fade, another war is beginning. Out of the mists of time, a magical axe is discovered. The legend of the axe is well known throughout the land, for it is told that this axe is the very one which Gillius Thunderhead used to slay Death Adder. 
 
Over time, the powers of the axe have grown. It is said that the artifact can grant its owner anything his or her heart desires. Young and old, good and evil, many are drawn towards the power of the weapon. Thus begins the war of the Golden Axe.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>AM3</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Golden Axe - The Duel (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Golden Axe - The Duel (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Golden Axe - The Duel (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13373" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./GridRun (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>GridRun </name>
    <desc>Aliens have captured you and you are forced to play a deadly game of what appears to be capture the flag combined with tag. Race your way around the area and capture the required number of flags before being touched by your opponent. If they do touch you, you must find and touch them before they capture the right number of flags. Who ever is "it" cannot capture flags until their opponent is tagged. There is a story and 2 player versus mode. Through the story, you face many different enemies with ranging speeds and firepower (gun fire only slows down the person shot, there is no health bar).</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Radical Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/GridRun (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/GridRun (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/GridRun (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13094" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Guardian Heroes (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Guardian Heroes </name>
    <desc>Treasure's unique scrolling beat-em-up/RPG hybrid, Guardian Heroes introduces the player to a motley crew of heroes (Consisting of a swordsman, a ninja, a cleric and a mage), formed to find a "legendary sword". The game begins with the heroes in a bar, having found this sword, as they decide what to do with it. Before they have a chance to come up with an idea however, they are interrupted as an Imperial General charges in and warns them they are in grave danger. Seconds later, Imperial troops swarm into the inn and the heroes are forced to take flight along with this general.

The fighting mechanic is slightly deeper than the average scrolling beat-em-up, with light and heavy attacks, special moves (executed the same way you'd expect a normal beat-em-up to work), magical attacks and the ability to block. As you defeat enemies you gain experience points, with which you can upgrade your character between levels - sharing them between various factors such as strength, speed, constitution and magic resistance.

Even more interesting however is the hugely branching storyline, which changes according to decisions you make (of which there are many) and which character you select to play with.

Also of note is the fact that even in one-player mode there are always two of you on screen - you command the other character by changing his "mood" - aggressive, cowardly etc. - of which there are six. On top of this, it is possible to play the game as a more traditional beat-em-up with up to six players/bots, and in this mode you can play as any character that you have encountered during the main game mode.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-6</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Guardian Heroes (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Guardian Heroes (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Guardian Heroes (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13296" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Gungriffon (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Gungriffon </name>
    <desc>Pilot an enormous walking mech to complete missions set all over the world in late 21st century warfare fighting other mechs, trucks and helicopters. The missions, set in different weathers and at different times of day, usually have specific objectives, be they search and destroy, protecting allies or killing everything. Four weapons are available: the main cannon; a weak machine gun that overheats with prolonged use; clusters of grenades and limited supplies of homing missiles. Damage repair and extra ammo is available from supply helicopters, but these are vulnerable to attack. Ally mechs can be useful, but it is the player who has to do most of the work by far, battling mechs that are sometimes faster and more agile, therefore a certain amount of strategy and planning is required.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Arts</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Gungriffon (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Gungriffon (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Gungriffon (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13327" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hang-On GP (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Hang-On GP </name>
    <desc>Hang-On GP features three tracks: Albatross Cliff Reef, Great Crimson Wall, and New Dwells.  Each track contains an additional route that becomes available after a high placing.  This makes a total of six possible races.  

Players can choose from among ten motorcycles to use during a race as well as an automatic or manual transmission for each. Players can also decide how the bike should control, highside or power slide.

Placing in the top three on any of the first three tracks will release the additional routes.  When players place in the top three on the additional routes an endurance mode will be available.  In endurance mode players attempt to complete as many laps as they can in 10 minutes.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Genki</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Hang-On GP (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Hang-On GP (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Hang-On GP (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13469" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hardcore 4x4 (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Hardcore 4x4  </name>
    <desc>Hardcore 4x4 (initially known as TNN Motorsports Hardcore 4X4 in the US and known as Deka Yonku ~Tough The Truck~in Japan) is a racing video game developed by Gremlin Interactive for the Sega Saturn, PlayStation and Microsoft Windows. It became available for download from PlayStation Store as a PSone Classic for play on the PlayStation 3 on January 10, 2008, in PAL regions.[4] The game utilizes 3D environments and truck models. The soundtrack features hard rock music. It was the first game to feature vehicles with independent suspension.[citation needed] 
 
In 1996, ASC (publisher) hired Top Dog Entertainment in Austin, Texas, to develop Hardcore 4x4 II (the second version). The first Sony PlayStation developer in the Americas, Brett Butler, was lead programmer. He travelled to England to collect the game code and world builder tools. Both were defective, so he spent the first month repairing the code base. He then designed new tracks, rebuilt the graphics engine in MIPS RISC R3000 assembly, and hired artists and designers to create new tracks, menu interfaces, and vehicles. The title was completed in late 1997 as Top Dog went out of business shortly after Brett Butler left the company.[citation needed]</desc>
    <releasedate>19961220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Hardcore 4x4 (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Hardcore 4x4 (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Hardcore 4x4 (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126280" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hebereke's Popoitto (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Hebereke's Popoitto </name>
    <desc>Hebereke's Popoitto is a Tetris variant. The goal in each level is to remove the blocks already on the playfield, representing characters from the franchise. Other blocks fall down from the top of the screen and have to be steered to the right place before touching the ground or another block. When four or more of the same blocks are together, they vanish. The catch of this variant is that the blocks which have to be removed move over the playfield. The player takes the role of the penguin Hebereke who wants to win a tournament against his friends.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19950303T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Success</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Hebereke's Popoitto (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Hebereke's Popoitto (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Hebereke's Popoitto (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13174" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hexen (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Hexen </name>
    <desc>While you were battling the evil forces of D'Sparil, the other Serpent Riders were busy sowing the seeds of destruction in other dimensions. One such dimension is the decaying world where Hexen takes place. A world littered with the mangled corpses of nonbelievers. Only three humans - a warrior, a mage and a cleric - have escaped the leader's vicious spell. Now these three brave souls have sworn to crush the evil regime that threatens to destroy the world forever.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Raven Software</developer>
    <publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Hexen (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Hexen (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Hexen (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13379" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./High Velocity - Mountain Racing Challenge (USA).chd</path>
    <name>High Velocity - Mountain Racing Challenge </name>
    <desc>Known in Japan as Touge King: The Spirits (often mistakenly translated as Touge: King of the Spirits), High Velocity is a fast-paced racer from Atlus. Choose your dream ride and blast off to see how fast you can race up the mountain. Customize your car, change its color, choose the engine, turbo charger, then tune it for perfection by setting up the suspension and tires. High Velocity: Mountain Racing Challenge features three different tracks based on real-life Alpine roads. You can also challenge a friend in a two-player split-screen mode</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Cave</developer>
    <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/High Velocity - Mountain Racing Challenge (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/High Velocity - Mountain Racing Challenge (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/High Velocity - Mountain Racing Challenge (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="152242" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hi-Octane - The Track Fights Back! (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Hi-Octane - The Track Fights Back! </name>
    <desc>A futuristic racing game with hover cars, in the same line as Wipeout, using a modified version of the Magic Carpet 2 engine. 
 
Gameplay takes a straightforward approach, with the directional keys controlling the steering and throttle, and three keys to fire the minigun, missiles or charge the booster. While the minigun has unlimited ammo, both fuel, armour and missiles must be replenished by passing through some marked areas or picking up powerups in the track or by left destroyed opponents. While the vehicles float on the track they are still influenced by the ground material: they slow down on dirt and even more on water. Each track has a number of shortcuts or alternate routes that offer powerups, and some tracks feature gates and ramps that open or close randomly. 
 
Includes 9 tracks and several game modes (for Saturn owners and PC players with the 1.2 patch installed) such as single race mode (with option to change the number of laps), a Championship mode, Split Screen, Clone Race (beating the ghost of the best race time), Death Match (Where instead of finishing first what matters is finish alive and with the most kills) and Hot Seat, where up to eight players can compete in the same race by taking turns, with the computer taking control of the players' vehicles waiting for their turn. There are six hover cars to choose from: the fast Flexiwing and Outrider, the balanced KD-1 Speeder and Vampyr and the slow but armed to the teeth Berserker and Jugga. In addition to the natural capacity of each, their Minigun, Missle and Booster capacities can be upgraded by picking up powerups during the race. There are Eight teams to choose from, which change the colour of the vehicle: Mad Medicine (white), Bullfrog (aqua green), Storm Riders (purple), Fire Phreaks (orange), DethFest (blue), Foo Fighters (yellow), Gorehounds (red) and Assassins Anonymous (black).</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bullfrog</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Hi-Octane - The Track Fights Back! (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Hi-Octane - The Track Fights Back! (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Hi-Octane - The Track Fights Back! (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13135" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./House of the Dead, The (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>House of the Dead, The </name>
    <desc>House of the Dead is your basic rail shooter. Go through the branching levels and kill all the zombies, avoid killing the humans and rescue the girl.  Shooting various special targets along the way or in a certain time period give you temporary health and weapon upgrades.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19980410T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/House of the Dead, The (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/House of the Dead, The (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/House of the Dead, The (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13448" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Impact Racing (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Impact Racing </name>
    <desc>With disregard for a background story, Funcom Dublin offers a Wipeout-esque mix of racing and driving at a very fast pace. Completing laps within the allotted time does not suffice, you also need to destroy a certain amount of vehicles. Contrary to the aforementioned title, you drive ordinary racing cars, if you count out the mounted weapons. These include mines, concussion missiles, smart bombs, heat-seeking missiles, lasers and firewalls. Some are provided by taking out enemies, but power-ups, time bonuses, energy, armor and a handicap that turns the screen upside-down, can also be collected.

Five cars are available, with different statistics and built-in weapons. The initially weak weapon is soon replaced when you collect upgrade icons. To activate these, you have to complete a bonus stage after which you can also save your game. To add to the game's length, each of the twelve tracks, based on the settings "city", "mountain" or "space", has three variations: reverse, at night or the combination of the two. Other features include a small diagram showing approaching cars to time your mines, and pumping electronic tracks to match the game's pace.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Coconuts Japan</developer>
    <publisher>Funcom</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Impact Racing (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Impact Racing (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Impact Racing (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13325" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./In the Hunt (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>In the Hunt </name>
    <desc>A 2D side scrolling shooter in which you take control of a small attack submarine and engage in underwater combat. The Dark Anarchy Society's forces threaten to destroy the earth's most important cities  and only you can get past their defenses and destroy their secret underwater lair.

In the Hunt follows the classic template for 2D shooters, with the added feature of being able to control scrolling speed. Includes seven levels of underwater action (and keep an eye out for threats from above the surface), upgradeable weapons, and two player cooperative gameplay.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kokuzeichou</developer>
    <publisher>Irem</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/In the Hunt (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/In the Hunt (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/In the Hunt (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13436" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Incredible Hulk, The - The Pantheon Saga (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Incredible Hulk, The - The Pantheon Saga  </name>
    <desc>True to the comic books, the Hulk relies on no other weapons than his massive muscles to punch, kick and crush his enemies. When he has accumulated enough gamma energy, he may use powerful special moves like a Vortex Spin or the Floor Hammer. Rare bonus items also allow the Hulk to summon one of the four Pantheon team members Atalanta, Ulysses, Ajax and Hector to assist in the thick of battle. 
 
Most levels include at least one arch-enemy, such as Piecemeal, Trauma &amp; Lazarus or the U-Foes. Luckily, the Hulkâ€™s regenerative powers allow him to regain health slowly. Little seems to be left of the Hulkâ€™s legendary leaping capacity, however, so the green meat ball is forced to hop from platform to platform every now and then.</desc>
    <rating>0.15</rating>
    <releasedate>19970121T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Attention To Detail</developer>
    <publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Incredible Hulk, The - The Pantheon Saga (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Incredible Hulk, The - The Pantheon Saga (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Incredible Hulk, The - The Pantheon Saga (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13291" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Independence Day (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Independence Day </name>
    <desc>This arcade game is based loosely on the 1996 blockbuster movie "Independence Day." Interspersed with cutscenes lifted from the film, the game consists of flying a jet through various missions in order to take down the gargantuan, city-destroying spaceships. This entails flying around the 3D level and taking out targets such as: communication uplinks, shield generators, the occasional alien fighter craft, and ultimately bringing down the major alien ship via a strike on its main cannon. Powerups are plentiful, such as medical packs that heal your jetcraft, bonus weapons, bonus planes, and an item that freezes enemy planes for a brief time. 
 
Mission settings include the Grand Canyon, Washington D.C., and New York City. There are other missions that are provided on a need-to-know basis (as stated in the manual). The game also features 2-player head-to-head action via a network or null modem link.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19970311T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Radical Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Fox Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Independence Day (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Independence Day (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Independence Day (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13367" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Iron Storm (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Iron Storm </name>
    <desc>This is a very traditional turn-based strategy game for the Sega Saturn. It uses a hex-based map and features fog-of-war, weather, unit experience, unit upgrading, vehicles, and other goodies you expect in a realistic WWII simulation. It also adds simple 3d animated cutscenes showing what happened during each attack.

Originally developed for the PC by SystemSoft as part of their (still running) Daisenryaku (~Great World War) series of games, it was ported to the Sega Saturn by Sega for it's Japanese release. It was then licensed by Working Designs and translated to English for it's US release.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Working Designs</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Iron Storm (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Iron Storm (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Iron Storm (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="152244" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Jewels of the Oracle (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Jewels of the Oracle  </name>
    <desc>Jewels of the Oracle is a stationary puzzle game with no real story line or plot. A total of 24 ingenious puzzles must be solved, each independent of the others. Most of them can be played in two difficulty levels (Easy or Hard), and the Oracle provides clues to help along the way. 
 
The graphics for the puzzles are designed in an Egyptian or Mesopotamian style. Music plays in the background to provide atmosphere, but it can be turned off, if it gets repetitive. The basic layout is a hexagon around an Oracle's well. There are three doors on the outside of the hexagon, and the first one is where you begin the game. In each room is a puzzle you have to solve to get a jewel which must be taken back to the Oracle's well. 
 
The puzzles in this game can be compared to those found in The 7th Guest. The Chinese Checkers puzzle in Shivers rivals many of the ones contained in Jewels of the Oracle.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19961018T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>ELOI Productions</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Jewels of the Oracle (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Jewels of the Oracle (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Jewels of the Oracle (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13287" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Johnny Bazookatone (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Johnny Bazookatone </name>
    <desc>The original guitar hero with the Elvis attitude and purple hair pompadour, Johnny Bazookatone, has been imprisoned in the year 2050 in Sin Sin Prison by El Diablo, the Lord of the Underworld, who is jealous of his talent and kidnaps other musical legends as well in this 3D side-scrolling platformer.  Johnny's guitar Anita has been taken from him and he sets out to escape and vanquish foes on his way to be reunited with Anita. 

He can perform moves such as 360-degree spin jumps, and hover jumps among others, while using his bazooka guitar as a weapon.  When powered up, it can emit a special sonic blast that fries anything within hearing range. As you make your way through the demonic levels such as Hotel Demonique, Hell's Kitchen, and Mr. Diablo's fiery Penthouse, you can  acquire more weapons, power-ups and find secret passages that lead to bonus levels. The game's soundtrack includes the title track contributed by Bon Jovi guitarist Richie Sambora and Tico Torres.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Arc Developments</developer>
    <publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Johnny Bazookatone (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Johnny Bazookatone (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Johnny Bazookatone (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13359" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Keio Flying Squadron 2 (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Keio Flying Squadron 2 </name>
    <desc>This is a crazy Japanese anime-style 2D platformer with shooting stages. The game features lots of different gameplay styles and some of the most bizarre bosses you will ever find in a game.  Its beautiful platform sections make good use of the Saturn's 2D hardware with scaling, rotation and transparencies. Your protagonist is Rami, a cute, scrawny blonde who dresses like a bunny and kills raccoons with a pink mallet.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960517T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Victor Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Adventure-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Keio Flying Squadron 2 (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Keio Flying Squadron 2 (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Keio Flying Squadron 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13279" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./King of Fighters '95, The (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>King of Fighters '95, The </name>
    <desc>The first sequel in the King of Fighters series picks up a year after the end of the first tournament. Once again, fighters from all over the world receive a mysterious invitation to a team-based fighting tournament. And just like last year, it appears that the notorious criminal Rugal Bernstein is behind it, apparently returning from the dead to raise havok once again...

The King of Fighters '95 introduces Kyo Kusanagi's rival Iori Yagami, and firmly places Kyo as the main character for the rest of the series. The gameplay of The King of Fighters '95 is essentially unchanged from the previous title, though it does introduce the "team edit" concept which would remain as a standard feature of the series. Using the "team edit" feature, it is possible to create a totally customized team using any of the available fighters, or use one of the default teams if you wish.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960328T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rutubo Games</developer>
    <publisher>SNK</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/King of Fighters '95, The (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/King of Fighters '95, The (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/King of Fighters '95, The (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13425" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Krazy Ivan (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Krazy Ivan </name>
    <desc>In the early 21st century, the Earth is under attack by aliens. In five areas of the planet, they have erected energy generators, creating a field that slowly encompasses the entire planet surface. They have also taken hundreds of humans prisoner. Someone has to stop them. Enter Russian Commander Ivan Popovich, nicknamed "Krazy Ivan". He is a paranoid schizophrenic, prone to burst out into violence at any time. In other words, he's perfect for the job.

The player controls Ivan's "Steel Cossack" power suit on the three-dimensional battlefields. In each of the five areas in the game, two kinds of enemies can be found: Drones and Sentients. Drones are smaller air and ground vehicles that often respawn. Sentients are mechs similar in size and capability to the Steel Cossack. Each of the Sentients must be eliminated before the energy field generator can be destroyed to complete the mission.

The Cossack is capable of carrying lots of weapons: projectile and energy guns, unguided and guided missiles, and other special weapons. Destroyed enemies reveal captured humans, to be rescued by Ivan, and power-ups, which recharge shields or rearm weapons.

After a successful mission, Ivan can upgrade the Cossack with more powerful weapons and replace the mech's armor.

Between the missions, rather humorous live-action cutscenes (starring English actors sporting thick Russian accents) continue the story.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Psygnosis</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Krazy Ivan (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Krazy Ivan (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Krazy Ivan (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13151" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Last Bronx (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Last Bronx </name>
    <desc>The leader of Soul Crew, the toughest gang in Tokyo, was viciously killed. Shortly after that an anonymous challenge appeared in graffiti scrawls all over the city "inviting" all of the city's gang leaders to a fighting tournament that will settle which group has the power to rule Tokyo. Everyone knew refusing to participate was not an option.

Just like in Virtua Fighter 2, you fight in 3D stages and every character has its unique style and feel. But unlike the PC version of Virtua Fighter 2, where the background of every stage is a flat picture, in Last Bronx all the scenery is done in 3D. Plus, you can taunt your opponent during the fight!</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>AM3</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Last Bronx (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Last Bronx (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Last Bronx (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13392" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Last Gladiators - Digital Pinball (USA) (4S).chd</path>
    <name>Last Gladiators - Digital Pinball  </name>
    <desc>Digital Pinball: Last Gladiators , also referred to as simply Last Gladiators (in North America) or Digital Pinball (in Europe), is a pinball game developed by KAZe and released on the Sega Saturn in 1995. It is one of a number of video pinball games developed by KAZe, and directly follows the Super Pinball series on the Super Famicom. 
 
During development Digital Pinball was known as Pinball Arena: Last Gladiators. It was also once set to be published by U.S. Gold in North America as Fantasy Pinball 
 
A Japan-only sequel, Digital Pinball: The Necronomicon was released in 1996. In 1997, Last Gladiators received a Japan-only updated rerelease titled Digital Pinball: Last Gladiators Ver.9.7</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kaze</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Pinball-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Last Gladiators - Digital Pinball (USA) (4S).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Last Gladiators - Digital Pinball (USA) (4S).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Last Gladiators - Digital Pinball (USA) (4S).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13099" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Legend of Oasis, The (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Legend of Oasis, The </name>
    <desc>The Story of Thor 2, known in Japan as Thor: Seireioukiden and the US as The Legend of Oasis, is video game on the Sega Saturn console. It is the prequel to The Story of Thor: A Successor of the Light/Beyond Oasis on the Sega Mega Drive. The music was composed by Yuzo Koshiro, who is also famous for composing music for the Streets of Rage series.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960731T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ancient</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Legend of Oasis, The (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Legend of Oasis, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Legend of Oasis, The (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13254" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Lost Vikings 2 - Norse by Norsewest (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Lost Vikings 2 - Norse by Norsewest  </name>
    <desc>The Lost Vikings 2 is a puzzle platform video game developed by Blizzard Entertainment and published by Interplay The sequel to The Lost Vikings, it features the original three characters plus two new playable characters, Fang the wolf and Scorch the dragon. However, to avoid becoming too complex, the game only lets the player control three of the five characters in each level. The gameplay remains largely the same, though the pre-existing characters all have new or modified abilities.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Melbourne House</developer>
    <publisher>Interplay</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Lost Vikings 2 - Norse by Norsewest (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Lost Vikings 2 - Norse by Norsewest (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Lost Vikings 2 - Norse by Norsewest (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13137" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Lost World, The - Jurassic Park (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Lost World, The - Jurassic Park </name>
    <desc>The Lost World: Jurassic Park is a 3D action video game released in 1997 for the Sega Saturn and Sony PlayStation. Developed by DreamWorks Interactive and published by Electronic Arts, The Lost World: Jurassic Park is based on both the novel by Michael Crichton and Steven Spielbergâ€™s film The Lost World: Jurassic Park. A year later a special edition of the game was released for the Sony PlayStation as a part of their Greatest Hits line-up and featured several modifications to the game play. 
 
The player takes control of characters struggling to survive on INGenâ€™s â€œSite Bâ€  populated by over 20 species of dinosaurs in an environment of escalating chaos. There are 5 characters in all to choose from, each with their own special abilities and attributes. While the game is in 3D, the game play resembles early 2D platformers in which you generically either go left or right, limiting the mobility of each character.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19971023T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Lost World, The - Jurassic Park (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Lost World, The - Jurassic Park (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Lost World, The - Jurassic Park (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13353" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Machine Head (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Machine Head </name>
    <desc>Blam! Machinehead is basically a normal 3D shooter where you shoot enemies and explore the futuristic, barren wastelands and abandoned factories and such as you try to save the world. 
The player controls Kimberly Stride, who is a scientist.
She has to save the world from bad DNA that is slowly "eating" everything away.

As a player, you control this hovercraft-thingy which was designed to be a safe vehicle to be in while travelling through this infested world. The game has nice 3D graphics and a very unique mood to it that separates it from the more common shooters.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19961031T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Core Design</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Machine Head (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Machine Head (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Machine Head (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13450" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Madden NFL 98 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Madden NFL 98 </name>
    <desc>Playcalling expert John Madden again licenses Electronic Arts' flagship football simulation. New features for 1998 include more advanced Quarterback functions such as the ability to play lob passes and adjust timing patterns, and more instinctive AI features to adjust as the match goes on. Squad features have also been advanced, with the opportunity to create plays and trade them.

Gameplay is much the same as the other editions, with the full season on offer as well as playoffs and the Superbowl. Everything is presented TV-style, with play-by-play analysis and reports. The contemporary NFL teams are joined by great squads of the past.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Sports</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Football-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Madden NFL 98 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Madden NFL 98 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Madden NFL 98 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13177" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Magic Carpet (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Magic Carpet </name>
    <desc>Magic Carpet is a first-person perspective game, in which you are a mage who flies on a, well, magic carpet and casts spells. The game has 50 levels, called "worlds"; each of those is set in a sea terrain with several mountainous islands. Your goal on each level is to amass enough mana within your castle to "restore the equilibrium" within the world. Once this happens, you can head to the next level. 

To collect mana, you have to find it (it is represented by golden spheres) and cast a specific spell to make it "yours". To collect this mana, you have to use a special spell to raise a castle of your own out of the ground. A balloon will appear over the newly created castle; it will proceed to fly around the level and collect "your" mana. Initially, your castle will be small and won't be able to hold much mana, so you'll have to keep casting the "castle" spell at it to make it bigger. 

The levels typically have monsters and rival mages in them. Not only they can hurt you with their attacks, but killing them is often necessary, as upon death they will release some of the mana you need to complete the level. To attack your enemies, you have a variety of spells at your disposal: fireballs, lightning bolts and meteors. 

There are also many other spells available to you - they allow you to heal yourself, surround yourself with a protective shield, teleport around, summon a skeleton army, or even modify the terrain by creating volcanoes and splitting landmasses. Not all spells are available to you from the beginning, though. 

Throughout all the levels, you are on your flying carpet, which can move in 3 dimensions. You can bring up a top-down map at any time.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bullfrog</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Magic Carpet (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Magic Carpet (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Magic Carpet (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13152" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Magic Knight Rayearth (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Magic Knight Rayearth </name>
    <desc>The balance in the magical world of Cefiro is supported by the prayers of the lovely princess Emerald. When the evil Sage Master imprisoned her, the existence of the entire world was endangered. Using her spiritual powers, the princess contacted three Japanese high-school girls, Hikaru, Umi, and Fuu, turned them into Magic Knights, and summoned them to Cefiro, where their goal is to save her and to restore the balance.

This adaptation of the eponymous manga and anime series is an action adventure, somewhat similar in style to  Zelda games. The protagonists are all the three girls, but the player can controls only one of them at a time. Each one has advantages and disadvantages, as well as different fighting styles: Hikaru uses swords, Umi a rapier, and Fuu a bow. The player advances through the game by exploring the world, talking to non-playable characters, and fighting enemies in real-time combat. There is no experience system; new abilities (among them swimming and jumping) are gained as dictated by the story, and must be used in certain points in order to advance.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure-Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Magic Knight Rayearth (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Magic Knight Rayearth (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Magic Knight Rayearth (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13229" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mansion of Hidden Souls, The (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Mansion of Hidden Souls, The </name>
    <desc>This Saturn-exclusive game is actually a sequel to the Sega CD game Mansion of Hidden Souls, even though the title might lead one to believe it is a remake. 
 
This game takes place after the events of the first game. The souls of the hidden mansion have asked you to return, because they have recognized that you possess special powers that allow you to see the butterfly manifestations of the souls living there. Something terrible is afoot at the mansion, and you must investigate things and set them right. Along the way you must discover the true purpose of the mansion and it's significance in the universe. 
 
Much like the Sega CD game, this is an FMV adventure. You move from location to location via video sequences, and solve puzzles to move on in the story.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mansion of Hidden Souls, The (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mansion of Hidden Souls, The (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mansion of Hidden Souls, The (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13250" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Manx TT SuperBike (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Manx TT SuperBike </name>
    <desc>Race motorcycles in this arcade port based on the real-life Isle of Man Trophy Race.  There are two courses to race with the usual reversed and mirrored variations on the tracks.  Also provided is a short and long version of the main course.  Play modes include arcade (standard tracks), PC mode (added variations), time trial, and network games with up to eight people.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19970314T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SCEE Studio Cambridge</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Manx TT SuperBike (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Manx TT SuperBike (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Manx TT SuperBike (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13187" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Marvel Super Heroes (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Marvel Super Heroes </name>
    <desc>Marvel Super Heroes is a 2D fighting game and the second Capcom title to feature characters from the Marvel comic universe. The gameplay is very similar to X-Men: Children of the Atom, but with a simplified Super Combo gauge and the addition of infinity gems. Each character starts with a set of gems. These can be activated during a fight to improve speed, power and defence, or provide special abilities to create crushing stone walls, open up a rift in space, or reverse the opponent's controls. The use of the gems is inspired by the The Infinity Gauntlet comic book series.

There are ten playable characters. The heroes are Captain America, The Incredible Hulk, Iron Man, Psylocke, Spider-Man and Wolverine. The villains are Blackheart, Juggernaut, Magneto and Shuma-Gorath. Anita from the Darkstalkers series is a hidden character in the Japanese version. The bosses are Doctor Doom and Thanos. During the boss fight Thanos steals all the player's gems (except for mind) and uses them with new effects.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19970808T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Marvel Super Heroes (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Marvel Super Heroes (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Marvel Super Heroes (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13340" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mass Destruction (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
    <name>Mass Destruction  </name>
    <desc>Mass Destruction puts players behind the controls of a one-man tank. The environments range from arctic to desert to urban. The player can blow up trees, buildings, walls - whatever you don't like the look. Enemies will come at you in tanks, planes, helicopters, and on foot. Each of the different weapons available to the player works best on a specific enemy. The player can use guided missiles for the helicopters and run over infantry men with the tank.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19971231T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>NMS Software</developer>
    <publisher>BMG Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mass Destruction (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mass Destruction (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mass Destruction (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="0" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./MechWarrior 2 - 31st Century Combat (USA).chd</path>
    <name>MechWarrior 2 - 31st Century Combat</name>
    <desc>You are the genetically engineered Clan Mechwarrior. The Clans are invading the Inner Sphere. Join either the Wolf Clan or the Jade Falcon Clan as they pursue their own agenda against the Inner Sphere and other Clans. Take your advanced Omnimechs into battle against all comers. Win high warrior ratings (by using less mechs or smaller mechs than needed, completing secondary objectives, etc.) and you'll get chance at a promotion trial where you face superior odds in an arena. If you win, you advance in rank. If you are very successfully, you can make it all the way up to Khan, leader of the Clan! Mechwarrior II was developed in-house by Activision as the successor to their original Mechwarrior. While this time there are no dynamic campaign and mercenary actions, the Clan culture is integrated into the two campaigns. Different clans have different mechs and different rules, even different weapons. You can customize your mechs in order to use less than the "par" force in order to get a higher rating. The full 3D environment wasn't pretty as this was before the 3D accelerators made their debut, but it's still better than anything that came before. Let addition of NetMech allowed users to fight each other online. When 3D cards came along, special versions were created to take advantage of 3D texturing. While not QUITE as replayable as Mechwarrior, it's nonetheless a classic.</desc>
    <releasedate>19970401T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Quantum Factory</developer>
    <publisher>Activision</publisher>
    <genre>Action;Vehicle Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
  </game>
  <game id="13184" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mega Man 8 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Mega Man 8 </name>
    <desc>Le combat contre le Dr Wily n'est pas encore terminé puisqu'il continue dans Mega Man 8 sur Saturn. Ce jeu d'action plates-formes marque les dix ans de la série et permet de retrouver le héros bleu et son armure aux multiples pouvoirs. Cette édition Saturn contient quelques éléments bonus que n'a pas la version Playstation tels que les robots ennemis Cut Man et Wood Man issus du premier et deuxième volet de la saga.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970117T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mega Man 8 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mega Man 8 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mega Man 8 (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13097" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mega Man X3 (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Mega Man X3 </name>
    <desc>A Reploid scientist named Dr. Doppler begins creation of a new city for Reploids, which will bring a new era of peace to the Reploids and humans. But something goes terribly wrong, and now Mavericks have begun to appear everywhere! It's up to X and Zero to find out who is behind this Maverick revolt and bring them down for good!</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mega Man X3 (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mega Man X3 (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mega Man X3 (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13108" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mega Man X4 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Mega Man X4 </name>
    <desc>Mega Man X, the reploid leader of the 17th unit Maverick Hunters, and his best friend Zero have to stop a reploid rebellion. Each of them gets involved in a different way and you can play as either character through the  parallel stories.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19970801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Platform / Run Jump-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mega Man X4 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mega Man X4 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mega Man X4 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13103" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mortal Kombat II (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat II </name>
    <desc>The Mortal Kombat fighters, plus several new ones, return for a tournament held by the evil Shang Tsung of the Outworld. The action is one-on-one as before, and famed for its high level of violence and blood (other than the sanitised Nintendo version). There are 5 difficulty levels and optional credits, as well as the usual two player mode including same character duels.

To win the main tournament, the player must beat each of the other human players, before taking on Shang Tsung, Kintaro and finally Shao Kahn. Players have a range of punches and kicks available, as well as flying kicks, uppercuts, roundhouses, and the special moves, which vary for each player. These include throws, uppercuts, long-distance bullets, bicycle kicks and a teleport feature.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Midway</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mortal Kombat II (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mortal Kombat II (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mortal Kombat II (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13087" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mortal Kombat Trilogy (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Mortal Kombat Trilogy </name>
    <desc>All the characters from the first three Mortal Kombat games return for the ultimate battle. You can play as Kano, Reptile, Mileena, Kung Lao, Shang Tsung, Sindel, Sketor, Stryker, Nightwolf, Sheeva, Kitana, Scorpion, Sonya, Smoke (Cyber Ninja), Rain, Jade, Baraka, Johnny Cage, Ermac, Noob Saibot, Sub-Zero (Unmasked), Sub-Zero (Classic), Jax, Rayden, Cyrax, Liu Kang, Smoke (Human), Kabal, Goro, Kintaro, Motaro, or Shao Kahn.

This game is one-on-one martial arts fighting. The player can choose from over thirty different characters, all with their own fighting style and their own special moves. Trilogy differs from the other games in that you can play combinations of people that otherwise isn't possible, such as old Liu Kang vs. new Liu Kang, etc.

Mortal Kombat Trilogy also allows you to challenge a friend to a fight through a Windows IPX network connection.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19970411T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Point of View</developer>
    <publisher>Midway</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Compilation-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mortal Kombat Trilogy (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mortal Kombat Trilogy (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mortal Kombat Trilogy (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13114" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mr. Bones (USA).m3u</path>
    <name>Mr. Bones </name>
    <desc>Mr. Bones is a unique game released exclusively for the Saturn. It combines several different types of gameplay. Some levels are side-scrolling action, some have a top-down perspective, and still others are single-screen mini games.

The story is meant to be a humorous horror tale. An evil wizard known as Dagoulian has created an army of skeleton warriors, and he plans to use this army to conquer the world. Fortunately for us, one of the skeletons he raised, Mr. Bones, was not obedient to his commands. You play as Mr. Bones as he attempts to both escape from Dagoulian and put and end to his plot.

There is a lot of video to watch in Mr. Bones. In fact, there is so much video that the game uses 2 CD-ROMs. The video is a combination of computer-generated animation and live action. Mr. Bones is a computer generated character, while Dagoulian is played by an actor.</desc>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <releasedate>19960930T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Zono</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mr. Bones (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mr. Bones (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mr. Bones (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13074" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Myst (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Myst </name>
    <desc>You have just stumbled upon a most intriguing book, a book titled Myst. You have no idea where it came from, who wrote it, or how old it is. Reading through its pages provides you with only a superbly crafted description of an island world. But it's just a book, isn't it? As you reach the end of the book, you lay your hand on a page. Suddenly your own world dissolves into blackness, replaced with the island world the pages described. Now you're here, wherever here is, with no option but to explore.

Myst is a first-person point-and-click adventure where the player controls a character known as The Stranger. Magically transported into the world described in the book, he needs to explore Myst Island and solve its mysteries. The game is presented as a series of static scenes where the player acts with the environment by clicking and manipulating objects. There are no enemies and it is not possible to die. Through Myst Island, the game is further divided into mini-worlds set in different ages accessed through different books.

The PSP version adds new adventure scenarios and includes widescreen support.

The DS version includes a completely new age, the Rime Age, and, next to a code rewrite, includes new and re-mastered sound effects and video clips.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Cyan</developer>
    <publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Myst (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Myst (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Myst (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13238" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mystaria - The Realms of Lore (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Mystaria - The Realms of Lore </name>
    <desc>Mystaria: The Realms of Lore, originally released as Riglordsaga in Japan, is a strategy game developed by Sega and Microcabin for the Sega Saturn. Two versions of the game were released in the US: one titled Mystaria: The Realms of Lore and the other as Blazing Heroes. 
 
Mystaria, once a land of peace and serenity, is now embroiled in turmoil. The evil Lord Bane and his ruthless band of marauders have overtaken the four kingdoms that rule this land. Now you must rely on the special powers of a Prince, a Ninja, a Lion man and others to reclaim your kingdoms and regain control of this beautiful land you once called your own! Breathtaking 3D graphics plus changing views and perspectives pull you into the action. Characters learn special attacks with each battle - over 250 attacks in all! Use a vast array of spells in your quest to conquer the evil Lord Bane and over 50 monsters and enemies.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19950721T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>MicroCabin</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Mystaria - The Realms of Lore (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Mystaria - The Realms of Lore (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Mystaria - The Realms of Lore (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13247" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NASCAR 98 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>NASCAR 98 </name>
    <desc>NASCAR 98 is a racing simulator video game published and developed by EA Sports and released in 1997 for the Sega Saturn and the Sony PlayStation. This was the first of the EA Sports NASCAR series.</desc>
    <releasedate>19971113T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Sports</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/NASCAR 98 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/NASCAR 98 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/NASCAR 98 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13158" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).chd</path>
    <name>NBA Jam - Tournament Edition </name>
    <desc>NBA Jam Tournament Edition is the second game in Midwayâ€™s basketball arcade series, featuring two-on-two fast paced matches with NBA players from the 1993-94 season (1994-95 on consoles). In total, the game features over 120 NBA athletes and over 40 hidden characters. Improvements include additional power-ups, more detailed player attributes, player substitutions after each quarter, and a new soundtrack. The namesake "Tournament Mode" turns off all cheats and power-ups, and rewards players with expanded rosters for nearly all teams if the player beats all 27 teams.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Basketball-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13370" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NBA Jam Extreme (USA).chd</path>
    <name>NBA Jam Extreme </name>
    <desc>"Takes the NBA Jam game and puts into an all new 3d engine with lifelike player movement. All the real basketball action is bundled with extreme moves. Zany sound fx, commentary and victory dances by the players."

Basketball with altered gameplay. Features two players on each team with a huge number of special dunks and moves. There is an inclusion of a new extreme button for added excitement. Commentary by Marv Albert.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19961126T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Basketball-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/NBA Jam Extreme (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/NBA Jam Extreme (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/NBA Jam Extreme (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13406" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NBA Live 98 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>NBA Live 98 </name>
    <desc>NBA Live 98 offers the player all teams, players and stadiums of the 1998 NBA season. More than 350 faces got scanned to improve realism. Also some new moves like crossover or fade-aways are implemented. You can play single games, whole seasons, the playoffs or new things like manager career or 3-point-shootout in the style of an all-star-game.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19971218T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Sports</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Basketball-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/NBA Live 98 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/NBA Live 98 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/NBA Live 98 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13439" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NHL 98 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>NHL 98 </name>
    <desc>NHL 98 features much faster and refined gameplay (now using four action keys instead of two, removing the need to double-tap to perform some actions), along other new features such as "in-the-fly" tactics developed by Marc Crawford, then manager of the Colorado Avalanche and new commentary lines from Jim Hughson and Darryl Reaugh and a re-worked interface.
Graphics are improved from the previous version with the players being less angular, and thanks to 3Dfx support, with less pixels showing in the textures. The in-game presentation follows a TV-style script, zooming in players while displaying stats during clock stoppages.

As far as game modes go, in the year of the first Olympic Tournament with professional players, NHL 98 introduced the first real international competition, with 18 International teams to choose from. Other game modes include Season (option to pick between 25 or 82 games) and Playoff (best of 1, 3, 5 or 7 matches) and a Penalty Shootout mode.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19971113T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>EA Sports</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/NHL 98 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/NHL 98 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/NHL 98 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1536</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13332" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Night Warriors - Darkstalkers' Revenge (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Night Warriors - Darkstalkers' Revenge </name>
    <desc>Darkstalkers 2 est un jeu de combat en 2D sur Saturn dans lequel s'affrontent diverses créatures fantastiques ou mythologiques. Il reprend en tout point le premier opus en y ajoutant simplement deux nouveaux personnages, Pyron et Lei-Lei. Faites monter votre jauge d'attaque pour déclencher votre super-pouvoir et annihiler l'ennemi !</desc>
    <releasedate>19960226T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Night Warriors - Darkstalkers' Revenge (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Night Warriors - Darkstalkers' Revenge (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Night Warriors - Darkstalkers' Revenge (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13085" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA) (RE).chd</path>
    <name>NiGHTS into Dreams...  </name>
    <desc>Immerse yourself in an unparalleled 3D flying experience. NiGHTS truly delivers an amazing virtual world of dreams -- filled with unbelievable real-time effects, fantastic creatures and nightmarish monsters. 
 
* Master a showcase of Sega Saturn's Processing Power. 
* Face your worst nightmares in a stunning world of 3D gameplay. 
* Dozens of camera angles, never-seen-before effects and 3D positional sound. 
* Developed exclusively for Sega Saturn by the creators of "Sonic the Hedgehog."</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960919T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sonic Team</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Action / Adventure-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA) (RE).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA) (RE).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/NiGHTS into Dreams... (USA) (RE).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13393" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Off-World Interceptor Extreme (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Off-World Interceptor Extreme </name>
    <desc>You play a Trashman, a bounty hunter paid to capture criminal scum hiding on harsh alien worlds. 

Your job is to race the enemy crime boss to the finish, blasting his goons along the way. Get blown up or drive too slowly and the boss gets away. But if you make it to the check point in time, you block the boss' escape and trap him on the planet.

You can upgrade your vehicle with the cash from your bounties. You can also go up against a buddy in the vertical split-screen deathmatch mode.

Off-World Interceptor's most unique feature is the storyline, told in  full-motion video. Standard for the time. But OWIE's FMV is mocked by a couple of guys sitting in chairs, a la Mystery Science Theater 3000.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>BMG Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Off-World Interceptor Extreme (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Off-World Interceptor Extreme (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Off-World Interceptor Extreme (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13140" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pandemonium! (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Pandemonium! </name>
    <desc>The young sorceress Nikki, the court jester Fargus, and his side-kick Sid the puppet are the three main protagonists of this 3D platform game. While attending a "Wizards in Training" seminar, Nikki accidentally casts a powerful magic spell, which results in a giant monsters swallowing the whole village. The three friends must now travel to a place called "Wishing Engine", and be granted a wish to revert the world back to normal.

The characters each have a special movement to kill enemies with. The game uses floating camera angles through a vast Prince of Persia-style world. The goal of the game is to clear the various levels, avoiding spikes and enemies and collecting coins for extra lives.

Unlike most 3D platformers, Pandemonium offers only two-dimensional movement, rather than complete freedom of movement. The characters move along a curving 2D course within a 3D environment.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970228T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>BMG Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Pandemonium! (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Pandemonium! (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Pandemonium! (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13096" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Panzer Dragoon (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Panzer Dragoon </name>
    <desc>One thousand years into the future, you live in constant fear of the Dark Dragon and his giant cyborg insect armies. Armed with a deadly weapon from the ancient past and the guidance of your armored blue dragon, you must save your people from endless swarms of deadly foes. Fulfill your destiny and keep the Dark Dragon from reaching the tower; or die trying.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19950310T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Team Andromeda</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Panzer Dragoon (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Panzer Dragoon (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Panzer Dragoon (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13093" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Panzer Dragoon II Zwei (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Panzer Dragoon II Zwei </name>
    <desc>Flash backwards to several years before the vicious battle against the empire in Panzer Dragoon 1. In the country of Machania, dragons are bred for the exclusive use of the dragoons, or Knights. Dragons with wings are normally executed as they are deemed to be a bad omen by the citizens. In the war with the Empire, Machania has begun to examine the ancient ways rather than to try to fight a futile war using technological advances. The Empire is technologically more advanced. Randy, the hero, and his newfound friend, the dragon he saved, want to turn the tide of battle.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960417T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Team Andromeda</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Panzer Dragoon II Zwei (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Panzer Dragoon II Zwei (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Panzer Dragoon II Zwei (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13078" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Panzer Dragoon Saga (USA).m3u</path>
    <name>Panzer Dragoon Saga </name>
    <desc>Panzer Dragoon Saga is set in the same universe as the other Panzer Dragoon games, but it differs from the rest of the series by having strong RPG elements.

The hero of the game is Edge, one of the soldiers of the mighty Empire. The Empire has recently ordered some excavations at ancient ruins, trying to discover the secret of an old technology that is much superior to that of present time. During the excavation works, Edge encounters a mysterious young girl. He then witnesses the murder of his captain and other soldiers by Crayden, one of the Empire's officers. Coming into contact with an ancient dragon, Edge begins to roam the world, determined to find Crayden and to avenge the death of his comrades. Nobody helps him but his faithful dragon. But the Empire is also after Crayden, so there appear to be at least three sides in the conflict... or are there more?

"Panzer Dragon Saga" combines elements of shooter and role-playing. You don't have a party in the game: you control only Edge on his dragon, who is in fact the playable character in battles. You move around through the game's fully 3D world by flying on the dragon. In towns and some dungeons you also move on foot. During battles, you can shoot with Edge's gun, or use one of the many special attacks of your dragons. You shoot in real time, and can also move around to attack your enemies from the sides of from the back, or to avoid their attacks. The dragon gets experience points for fighting and also gains levels. You will be able to customize your dragon by assigning to him one of the four available dragon classes, that will determine his attack power, speed, etc.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>Team Andromeda</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Panzer Dragoon Saga (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Panzer Dragoon Saga (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Panzer Dragoon Saga (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126385" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Parodius (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Parodius </name>
    <desc>The Parodius  series is a series of horizontally scrolling shooters developed by Konami. The games are tongue-in-cheek parodies of Gradius, hence the name (Parodius is a portmanteau of Parody and Gradius). It also parodies many other Konami franchises, including Antarctic Adventure, Castlevania, Xexex, Axelay,[citation needed] Thunder Cross, Taisen Puzzle-Dama, Space Manbow, Ganbare Goemon, Lethal Enforcers, R-Type, Tokimeki Memorial and TwinBee.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950519T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Konami</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Parodius (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Parodius (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Parodius (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126392" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pinball Graffiti (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Pinball Graffiti </name>
    <desc>Pinball Graffiti is a Sega Saturn pinball game. Unlike its other Saturn rivals, Pinball Graffiti is rendered entirely in 3D, and can hence offer several interesting camera modes (such as a ?ball cam?) which most other pinball games are unable to provide. Pinball Graffiti has remained a Saturn exclusive and has not been ported to any other platforms as of yet.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960712T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Pack In Video</developer>
    <publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
    <genre>Pinball</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Pinball Graffiti (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Pinball Graffiti (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Pinball Graffiti (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1792</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13285" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Primal Rage (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt).chd</path>
    <name>Primal Rage  </name>
    <desc>A meteor struck the Earth, and caused great chaos. Seven gods from ancient times awoke, and are now attempting to take control of the post-apocalyptic world.

Primal Rage is a one-on-one fighting game featuring dinosaurs and giant apes as the fighters. The graphics are done with digitized stop-motion animation. Gameplay is similar to Mortal Kombat in that it is viewed from a side perspective, and features deadly finishing moves at the end of the match.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19960801T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Time Warner Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Atari</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Primal Rage (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Primal Rage (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Primal Rage (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Pt).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13115" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Quake (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Quake </name>
    <desc>An enemy with the codename ''Quake'', which is believed to come from another dimension, is using teleporter gates to invade Earth. The player takes the role of a nameless soldier who arrives at his base only to find out Quake has overrun it and killed everyone. Somewhere in the base there must be a teleporter to Quake's realm. The mission is clear: take the fight to the enemy, overcoming countless hordes of monsters, and exact revenge.

id Software's followup to Doom and Doom II, "Quake" is a first-person shooter. Its main technological innovation is the use of a true 3D engine - the levels themselves as well as the enemies are polygonal. This not only allows for more natural level designs and character animations, but also for more realistic lighting and the inclusion of simulated physics that have an effect on gameplay: grenades can bounce off walls and around corners, for example.

In single-player mode, gameplay consists mainly of proceeding through the levels (spread over four distinct episodes) in search of an exit, killing everything that moves. Interaction with the game world is reduced to a minimum: since there is no use key, buttons are pressed by running into or shooting at them. As in id's earlier games, many secrets are waiting to be discovered, including a few hidden levels.

Unlike Doom's rather straightforward design that couples futuristic environments with demonic imagery, the theme of Quake's levels, enemies and weapons is not so easily pinpointed. While each episode begins in a futuristic military base (with a technological 'slipgate' as the level exit), later levels take place in environments inspired by medieval fantasy and gothic horror (castles, dungeons and caverns) and the player passes through magical portals to advance. In a departure from Doom's colorful environments, all Quake levels are dominated by earth colors.

The enemies conform to the mishmash of designs: there are human opponents armed with shotguns and energy weapons in the early levels, while the later levels include medieval knights, ghosts, zombies, ogres (armed with grenade launchers and chainsaws) and some more unearthly beasts. The player's weapons, while relatively modern, all have a low-tech feel.  Besides a (bloodstained) axe, there are shotguns, nailguns, rocket and grenade launchers and the Thunderbolt, which discharges electrical energy.

Quake was one of the first games playable natively over the Internet in addition to LANs. The single-player levels can be played cooperatively, but the game is most famous for its deathmatch mode. One-on-one duels, team play and free-for-all competition are possible. The emphasis is on fast reaction and skillful maneuvering through the levels. All of the single-player maps can be used as arenas, but the game also comes with six maps especially designed for deathmatch.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19971203T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Lobotomy Software</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Quake (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Quake (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Quake (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13089" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Rayman (Europe) (En,Fr,De) (6S).chd</path>
    <name>Rayman   </name>
    <desc>When a villain known only as Mr. Dark appears, trouble brews in Rayman's world.  Mr. Dark captures the Toons - source of light and Rayman's friends.  With no more light, evil creatures begin to roam, making the world unsafe for everyone.  Its up to you, as Rayman, to free your friends and put an end to Mr. Dark's dastardly schemes!

Rayman is side-scrolling platformer starring the titular Rayman, a big-nosed chap with no arms or legs.  Rayman can jump and use his hair to hover for a short period of time.  He can also attack by throwing his fists, or winding up his fists for a more powerful punch.  He can occasionally find special power ups that grant him unlimited flying power, giving him the ability to navigate through tricky mazes.

Aside from the platforming action, the other notable feature of Rayman is its large, detailed and vibrant graphics, which have helped it to stand out from most other similar games in the genre.</desc>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <releasedate>19951101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
    <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Rayman (Europe) (En,Fr,De) (6S).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Rayman (Europe) (En,Fr,De) (6S).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Rayman (Europe) (En,Fr,De) (6S).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13072" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Resident Evil (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Resident Evil </name>
    <desc>A team of S.T.A.R.S (Special Tactics And Rescue Squad) members are called to investigate a series of murders near Raccoon City.
While searching the woods near the city, the team is attacked by bloodthirsty dogs and they have to retreat to a nearby mansion. 

The player chooses between Jill Valentine or Chris Redfield and starts to explore the mansion. It soon becomes very clear that it isn't just any mansion, but a hellish place where the undead walk the corridors and other horrors are lurking in the darkness, waiting to eat some heads. While solving puzzles, collecting keys, and shooting monsters, the player has to unravel the mystery behind this mansion and, if possible, get out alive.

Exclusive to the SEGA Saturn version is a Battle Mode bonus mode, where, with limited ammo and under the threat of limited time, the player must survive a series of rooms filled with monsters</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19971001T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Resident Evil (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Resident Evil (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Resident Evil (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13328" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Rise 2 - Resurrection (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Rise 2 - Resurrection  </name>
    <desc>In the sequel new troubles in ElectroCorp have begun. As we remember, this corporation made robots for civilian jobs, but one Supervisor decided to make robot-killers. Human brains were implanted on some of them. But this time, one hacker has infected the ElectroCorp's network with a virus, so Supervisor lost control over robots and they began to kill each other. You are one of them.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960521T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Mirage</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Rise 2 - Resurrection (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Rise 2 - Resurrection (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Rise 2 - Resurrection (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13130" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Road &amp; Track Presents - The Need for Speed (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Road &amp; Track Presents - The Need for Speed </name>
    <desc>Drive some of your favourite sports cars through wild and fast tracks, including the Dodge Viper, Lamborghini, Ferrari, Porshe, Corvette, Mazda RX7, Toyota Supra Turbo, and Acura NSX.
Some of the tracks are open road, meaning you simply fly down a huge highway, with cops following in hot pursuit. One of the options in the game allows you to pick which time of the day to race in.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19960705T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Pioneer Productions</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Road &amp; Track Presents - The Need for Speed (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Road &amp; Track Presents - The Need for Speed (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Road &amp; Track Presents - The Need for Speed (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13172" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Road Rash (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Road Rash </name>
    <desc>This is a remake of the original Road Rash from the early nineties. For those who have not played the original, you are competing against thirteen other "Road Rashers" who will stop at nothing to win 1st, 2nd, or 3rd place. During the race, you have two options available to you: you can either do your best to cross the finish line, or use your weapon to bring the Rashers to the ground if they are giving you trouble. If you do the latter, your opponents will do the same to you during the next race that takes place. 

There are five circuits to race: The City, The Peninsula, Pacific Highway, Sierra Nevada, and Napa Valley. Some of these circuits are dangerous. As well as the obstacles and traffic that you encounter along the way, there are also cops driving on bikes who will arrest you if you happen to crash or stop your bike near them, and you have to pay a fine in order to get in any more races. Your bike will be wrecked if you crash too many times, and you have to pay for damages, but the amount you have to pay depends on the bike that you are riding. Once you have completed the first five circuits, you have to race them again another four times - but at a much more difficult level. Manage to win all five circuits on all levels, and you win the Road Rash cup.

There are about five bikes to choose from, which are divided into three groups. Rat, Sport, and Super. You start the first level with a Rat bike, but as you proceed through the levels, it is important to pick bikes from a different bike class.

If you have no plans to win the Road Rash cup, you can choose the game's Thrash mode. The difference between this and the other mode is that there is no money involved (ie: you are not allowed to buy bikes), and you are competing against fourteen opponents. And if you wreck your bike or you get busted, you have to start all over again. Regardless of the mode you pick, you will always start in the last place.

The remake also contains FMV movies that usually depict the outcome of the races, as well as limited songs performed by various recording artists, including Soundgarden, Therapy?, Monster Magnet, and Swervedriver. These songs can be changed on-the-fly via the game's options menu.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19960628T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Buzz Puppet</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Road Rash (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Road Rash (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Road Rash (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13455" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Robo Pit (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Robo Pit </name>
    <desc>Robo Pit is an arena fighter, plain and simple. Well, maybe not so simple. When you start your game, you have to build your mechanical gladiator; choosing the color, body, eyes and legs. While most of your starting choices are purely cosmetic, the legs you choose do slightly affect your game by changing the speed and mobility of your fighter, as well as its special attack.

Once you've created your robotic brawler, it's time to start climbing the ranks. To progress, you have to fight the robot that's occupying the rank above yours. Once you beat them, you get to take an arm and then move up. The game continues on in this fashion until you've bested all of the other combatants. However, a few curve-balls are thrown your way as you climb the ladder. For starters, there are several different arms you can acquire; from swords and shields to cannons and lasers, and the more you use them, the faster and more effective (i.e. damaging) they are. On top of that, even so often a sort of "boss" robot is put in your way. These "bosses" use special weapons that only they have access to. Until you pound them into scrap and take them, that is. These weapons can be incredibly powerful if you stick with them, making the rest of the fighters, save number one, a breeze. As an added bonus, you can even save your cyber-combatant to a memory card and bring it to a friend's house for some one-on-one let's-see-who-has-the-best-robot fighting goodness!

The arenas themselves are fairly basic, but they are varied, offering up different layout and obstacles to take cover behind or use to get the drop on your opponent. They also have ledges, and like most fighting games a ring-out means an instant loss. As for the fighting, it's simple, but effective. Square and circle attack with the left and right arms, X jumps and triangle triggers your special (which has to charge of course). Of course different weapons have different ranges and timing, which will also improve the more you use them.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Altron</developer>
    <publisher>Altron</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Robo Pit (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Robo Pit (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Robo Pit (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13333" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Robotica (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Robotica </name>
    <desc>Robotica was the first firstperson shooter for the platform and a first generation game for the console. It is somewhat similar to Space Hulk, only that the player takes the role of a machine that rebels against the robots to save mankind. The weapons include a punch, Vulcan gun, Missiles, and Lasers. The main environment is made up of various hallways. The player runs through the various stages collecting keys, using computers, and triggering lights. The enemies are relatively basic but are dangerous in numbers.

The game is set in 2877, 800 years after the world's peacekeeping unions have collapsed. They are replaced with World Silent Security Service, a global world order to maintain the security on earth and in space. However, over time the role of the order is questioned, and the Reformist Faction rebel group sends three pilots in Laocorn assault robots to the WSSS' space station Daedalus in earth's orbit. Two are immediately destroyed, but the player gets to control the remaining robot.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19950324T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Micronet</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Robotica (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Robotica (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Robotica (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13458" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV - Wall of Fire (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV - Wall of Fire </name>
    <desc>It's the era of the Second Han Dynasty, and China is being overrun by powerful warlords. A struggle for power among the court families has spawned a time known as the Three Kingdoms, and it's up to you (as the current ruler) to restore peace to your troubled country. Rebuild the land by creating a strong military or try to outwit your opponents using negotiation. 
 
Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV: Wall of Fire (Sangokushi IV in Japan) is the fourth game in Koei's Romance of the Three Kingdoms series. Wall of Fire was the first game for the Playstation &amp; Saturn consoles and the last in the series to be released on PC in the U.S. until Romance of the Three Kingdoms XI.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960327T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Koei</developer>
    <publisher>Koei</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Action-Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV - Wall of Fire (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV - Wall of Fire (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Romance of the Three Kingdoms IV - Wall of Fire (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13159" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Saturn Bomberman (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Saturn Bomberman </name>
    <desc>An all out party game, this Saturn exclusive title has you controlling the little blue bomber along with up to 10 other bomber pals planting bombs to trap enemy characters. 

Although there is no story mode, you can take on a host of other characters in one on one battles to see who is the master of the bomb. 10 players can then play on the one screen at a time, either against each other or in teams.

Saturn Bomberman can also connect to the Sega Saturn NetLink internet system, allowing two people from opposite ends of the earth to battle it out.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960719T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Hudson</developer>
    <publisher>Hudson</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>8+</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Saturn Bomberman (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Saturn Bomberman (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Saturn Bomberman (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13306" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Scorcher (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Scorcher </name>
    <desc>Scorcher is a futuristic racing game by Scavenger. In dark post-war-looking decors, you race against a couple of opponents driving in a spherical racer. You can pick up special triangles to gain speed powerups.

The graphics support resolutions up to 640x480.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19970301T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Zyrinx</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Scorcher (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Scorcher (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Scorcher (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13472" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sea Bass Fishing (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Sea Bass Fishing  </name>
    <desc>Seabass Fishing est une simulation de pèche sur Saturn. Vous participez à une compétition et vous devez, bien entendu, la remporter. Vous pouvez soit vous entraîner d'abord, soit entrer directement dans la compétition dans laquelle vous devez gagner trois défis afin de devenir le champion. Choisissez un capitaine pour votre bâteau. Une fois au large, vous pouvez commencer à pécher.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960223T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Victor Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Victor Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Hunting and Fishing-Fishing-Sports-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sea Bass Fishing (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sea Bass Fishing (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sea Bass Fishing (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1027</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13210" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sega Touring Car Championship (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Sega Touring Car Championship </name>
    <desc>After Virtua Racing, Daytona USA and Sega Rally, yet another classic SEGA arcade racer (this time, from the Model 2C CRX architecture) is converted for home users. After open-wheel, stock and rally cars, Sega took on the popular European Touring Car races (factory models modified for racing), featuring four real models (Alfa Romeo 155V6TI, Toyota Supra GT, AMG Mercedes C-Class and Opel Calibra V6) as well as some hidden cars. Some models feature four-wheel drive (easier to control on sharper turns) while other only have rear-wheel drive (forcing the player to calculate turns properly so the car doesn't skid). Because of this, gameplay is notoriously tighter and less forgiving than in any of the previous titles by Sega. 

Like with other Sega arcade ports, this home versions features both an "Arcade" and a "PC"/"Saturn" mode (the biggest difference being the time constraints and inability to use tweaked cars in arcade) with the usual Championship (three races in a row) and Time Attack modes, and a 2P split-screen race is also available. There are three tracks, plus one more as the final race (as usual with contemporary Sega arcade racers), and two viewpoints (behind and front bumper) are at the disposal of the player.
As usual, there are additional modes, tracks and cars to be unlocked for those proficient in the game.

Another feature was the "Global Ranking" mode, where players of either version could e-mail Sega of Japan a password containing his times, and compare them to the World's finest players, as well as in special one-day only "Global Net Events".</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19971127T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>AM Annex</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sega Touring Car Championship (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sega Touring Car Championship (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sega Touring Car Championship (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13457" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shanghai - Triple-Threat (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Shanghai - Triple-Threat </name>
    <desc>Shanghai : Triple Threat sur Saturn est un jeu de Mah-Jong où le but est de retrouver les paires pour les faire disparaître. Ces pièces ne doivent pas être bloquées pour pouvoir être retirées. D'autres modes de jeu sont disponibles en plus de ce "Classic Shanghai" de même qu'un mode 2 joueurs.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Activision</developer>
    <publisher>Activision</publisher>
    <genre>Asiatic board game-Board game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Shanghai - Triple-Threat (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Shanghai - Triple-Threat (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Shanghai - Triple-Threat (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2048</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13086" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shining Force III (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Shining Force III </name>
    <desc>Set in a world of fantasy and magic, Shining Force III places you in the boots of a young general, fighting to preserve the peace in your world. The story starts out as the Emperor is abducted from within the city of Saraband, and you must go on the run with your king, who is suspected of being the mastermind behind the abduction. Of course, things are not as they seem, and you will be taken through a web of lies and deceit in your quest to prove the King innocent.

The game is very similar in style to the earlier Shining Force titles, so anyone who's played them will be comfortable with the game, though likely they'll also be happy to find the game graphically overhauled, with a 3-D landscape and 3D characters during the battle animations. As ever the main game is controlled like a traditional RPG, with you controlling the main character, talking to NPC's and searching various items. However, the main selling point of the Shining Force series has always been its battle sequences. 

The combat system is amended from the earlier titles, with a new and unique "friendship" system, whereby the more two characters work together (helping each other out, healing each other etc.) the closer they bond, and they will start to give each other bonuses on the battlefield. Other traditional features, such as the rock-paper-scissors nature of the weapons (sword beats axe, axe beats spear, spear beats sword etc.) and the terrain effects (someone hiding in a forest is going to get better protection than someone on an open road) remain fully intact, and anyone who's played the earlier titles in the series will likely be very comfortable with the combat system.

It should be noted that this is actually the western conversion of Shining Force III: Episode I, and was therefore only the first episode in an intended series of three. Unfortunately the other two titles were never released outside of Japan, so most western gamers were only able to experience a third of the storyline.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19980731T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Camelot Software</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Shining Force III (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Shining Force III (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Shining Force III (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13190" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shining the Holy Ark (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Shining the Holy Ark </name>
    <desc>Part of the Shining game universe, "Shining the Holy Ark" is a pure console-style RPG (unlike  Shining Force games, that were strategy/RPG hybrids). You play the role of a young swordsman Arthur, who decided to work as a mercenary for various people needing his services. On his first mission, the King of Enrich sends him to a mine, in order to find and punish a renegade ninja who has escaped from him. However, an accident occurs that makes Arthur realize that he'll have to do much more than his usual mercenary assignment, and that there is a true evil in the world that must be defeated at all costs.

The game features 3D graphics and utilizes first-person perspective for dungeons and battles. The turn-based battles are of a traditional Japanese RPG kind, except the addition of "Pixie System". In various places in the game you can find pixies who can later be used as allies in battles.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19970619T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Shining the Holy Ark (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Shining the Holy Ark (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Shining the Holy Ark (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13128" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shining Wisdom (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Shining Wisdom </name>
    <desc>Shining Wisdom is the 4th game in the Shining series, but is completely different from the others. Neither a dungeon crawl like Shining in the Darkness, or a tactical battle RPG like Shining Force, the game plays very similarly to Zelda, with its action RPG elements. 
The game proceeds by collecting various items found in dungeons and then combining them with magical orbs to create different spell effects that can be used to tackle enemies and solve the riddles that must be bested to beat each labyrinth.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19960711T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sonic Co.</developer>
    <publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Shining Wisdom (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Shining Wisdom (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Shining Wisdom (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13100" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shinobi-X - Shin Shinobi Den (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Shinobi-X - Shin Shinobi Den </name>
    <desc>Blood is thicker than water. 
 
Not in this family. Twin Brothers Sho and Kazuma give sibling rivalry a bad name. While Sho does all the nice things that would make his Shinobi ancestors proud, Kazuma has them turning in the family plot. Kazuma's band of merciless mercenaries is intent on reducing the family membership by one. Meanwhile, Kazuma abducts his own sister, Aya, just to make sure Sho has soemthing to think about before storming in on his brother. Sometimes kids just don't turn out the way you want them to. 
 
Nine stages of explosive action. Digitized characters. Vertical and horizontal scrolling. Beautifully detailed multi-layered backgrounds. Movie quality cinematics.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19950630T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Shinobi-X - Shin Shinobi Den (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Shinobi-X - Shin Shinobi Den (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Shinobi-X - Shin Shinobi Den (Europe).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13419" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shockwave Assault (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Shockwave Assault </name>
    <desc>Shockwave Assault combines Shock Wave and its expansion Operation Jumpgate and makes them available for systems other than the 3DO for the first time. 
 
In Shock Wave, the player takes the role of a rookie pilot, defending the Earth from an alien invasion. From the cockpit of the F-177 fighter, one shoots at the alien walkers and fighters with lasers and missiles, rearming and refueling at supply depots when necessary. The story is told with live-action cutscenes.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960705T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Shockwave Assault (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Shockwave Assault (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Shockwave Assault (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13104" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./SimCity 2000 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>SimCity 2000 </name>
    <desc>SimCity 2000 is the successor to the ground breaking city simulation game Sim City. You are once again the mayor, but this time you can fully customize the terrain before building your city. The graphics are isometric, whereas the original had graphics displayed in a top-down fashion.

This title adds numerous features over the original such as the ability of building "light" zones, subways, hospitals, colleges, zoos, and arcos which are actually cities in cities. You can now give names to places, and your city is surrounded by neighboring towns with which you can make trade. Finally, instead of the poll in the first game you now have the option of reading several newspapers to get an idea of your progress.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19950929T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Maxis Software</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/SimCity 2000 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/SimCity 2000 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/SimCity 2000 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13360" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Skeleton Warriors (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Skeleton Warriors  </name>
    <desc>You're Prince Lightstar, with the quest to conquer and slay Baron Dark, who holds the half of a mighty crystal called the Lightstar Crystal. With that crystal he can change anyone with an evil heart into his skeleton slave.

The game is a 2D sidescrolling platform game with 3D pre-rendered graphics, with about 100 types of enemies for you to slay with the weapons you possess. You need to complete 21 levels filled with demonic evil creatures before you can fight the Baron Dark himself, with 3D rendered cutscenes inbetween some levels.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960904T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Neversoft</developer>
    <publisher>Playmates Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Skeleton Warriors (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Skeleton Warriors (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Skeleton Warriors (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126469" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sky Target (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Sky Target </name>
    <desc>Sky Target was originally released as a 1995 arcade game. The game is a rail shooter featuring a number of planes including the default F-14D Super Tomcat. It is best remembered for its semi-official connection to Sega's earlier hit After Burner. The Saturn port retains the gameplay of the original but has completely redone cutscenes, a difficulty select option, and a new Ranking Mode.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19970425T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sky Target (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sky Target (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sky Target (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13111" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sonic 3D - Flickies' Island (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Sonic 3D - Flickies' Island </name>
    <desc>Sonic 3D Blast, also known as Sonic 3D: Flickies' Island, is a 1996 platform video game developed by Traveller's Tales and Sonic Team, and published by Sega for the Genesis, Saturn, and Windows. Part of the Sonic the Hedgehog series, the game abandons previous Sonic games' side-scrolling style in favor of isometric gameplay, making use of some pre-rendered 3D models converted into sprites. The game features creatures known as Flickies, which first appeared in the 1984 arcade game Flicky. Controlling only Sonic himself, the player's goal is to collect Flickies and carry them to safety, periodically sparring with the series antagonist Dr. Robotnik, who is imprisoning them within robots. 
 
While 3D Blast was initially created for the Genesis Sega also commissioned a port for the Saturn as a backup plan in case Sonic X-treme could not be released in time for the Holiday season.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19970214T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sonic 3D - Flickies' Island (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sonic 3D - Flickies' Island (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sonic 3D - Flickies' Island (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13111" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sonic 3D Blast (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Sonic 3D Blast </name>
    <desc>Sonic 3D Blast, also known as Sonic 3D: Flickies' Island, is a 1996 platform video game developed by Traveller's Tales and Sonic Team, and published by Sega for the Genesis, Saturn, and Windows. Part of the Sonic the Hedgehog series, the game abandons previous Sonic games' side-scrolling style in favor of isometric gameplay, making use of some pre-rendered 3D models converted into sprites. The game features creatures known as Flickies, which first appeared in the 1984 arcade game Flicky. Controlling only Sonic himself, the player's goal is to collect Flickies and carry them to safety, periodically sparring with the series antagonist Dr. Robotnik, who is imprisoning them within robots. 
 
While 3D Blast was initially created for the Genesis Sega also commissioned a port for the Saturn as a backup plan in case Sonic X-treme could not be released in time for the Holiday season.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19961130T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sonic 3D Blast (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sonic 3D Blast (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sonic 3D Blast (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13125" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sonic Jam (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Sonic Jam </name>
    <desc>A compilation of Sonic's greatest 2D adventures. Included on the disk is the original Sonic the Hedgehog, Sonic 2 (featuring Tails), Sonic 3 plus Sonic &amp; Knuckles.

Each game has you taking control of Sonic (and later on in the series, Tails and Knuckles) who must use his speed to blast his way through level after level and rescuing his animal friends from the evil Dr. Robotnik. Along the way you will also enjoy 3rd person bonus rounds and take on a host of end of level bosses.

Exclusive to the Saturn compilation is the Sonic 3D museum, which allows you to control a 3D animated Sonic through a world full of historical information on the Sonic series, including behind the scenes, details on the characters from each game, artwork and more.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970731T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Compilation-Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sonic Jam (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sonic Jam (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sonic Jam (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13092" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sonic R (USA, Brazil).chd</path>
    <name>Sonic R </name>
    <desc>While on vacation, Tails and Sonic come across a recruiting advertisement for the World Grand Prix race, and when he learns that Dr. Robotnik will participate he decides to enter. Robotnik is only interested in the race as he has located the Chaos Emeralds and now he'll get a chance to beat Sonic while he gets them. Knuckles and Amy join the race as well.nn-Grand Prix: You race against the rest of the characters on each of the circuits, and get a chance to race the level's boss to unlock some of the extra playable characters.nn-Time Attack: Run on one of the tracks as fast as you can, get 5 balloons or tag 4 characters.nn-Multi Player: 4 players on a split-screen or over a network. You can race against up to three players or challenge them on a balloon finding game. The screen can be divided horizontally or vertically for 2 player games.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19971204T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Sonic R (USA, Brazil).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Sonic R (USA, Brazil).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Sonic R (USA, Brazil).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13232" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Soviet Strike (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Soviet Strike </name>
    <desc>In 1991, the U.S.S.R. (Union of Soviet Socialist Republics) boasting the largest military force in history, suddenly and unexpectedly collapsed. Since that time the fallen empire has lain lifeless -- a rich corpse waiting to be picked clean. Now, a sinister ex-KGB general codenamed Shadowman directs a flock of vultures to swoop in from all parts of Eastern Europe and claim Russia's nuclear warheads and weapons of mass terror. While directing these 'wars of liberation' Shadowman intends to shake democratic Russia to it's foundations, bringing about a return to the Cold War...or even worse. You chopper into Crimea and discover the plot of this Russian madman using thermal spy devices. You must quickly move on to the Black Sea to prevent the hijacking of ICBM ships, respond to an attack on a chemical weapons plant in the desert passes, and then recover a nuclear reactor core in Transylvania. As you successfully thwart these stages of Operation Vulture, Shadowman is forced to take his coup to the streets of Moscow. Guide your chopper through five unique 3D worlds as you complete 41 deadly missions. Enemy vehicles, tactics, and responses change, based upon your activities, making this the first of STRIKE's new "Living Battlefields".</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19970217T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tiburon Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Soviet Strike (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Soviet Strike (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Soviet Strike (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13207" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Space Hulk - Vengeance of the Blood Angels (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Space Hulk - Vengeance of the Blood Angels </name>
    <desc>It's the 41st Millennium. For 20,000 years mankind has expanded forth throughout the galaxy aided by a phenomenal invention known as the Warp Drive, which allows huge spatial distances to be traversed in a matter of hours. Under the auspices of the Emperor; a psychic so powerful he is essentially immortal, a pan-galactic Imperium has been established in which mankind has spread and prospered. The defenders of the Imperium are the Adeptus Astartes, or Space Marines, bio-genetically engineered warriors of superhuman prowess, ever vigilant to destroy the many threats that face mankind across the cosmos. 
The player is one such Space Marine, belonging to one of the oldest and most honourable Chapters known as the Blood Angels, whose battle honours date back as long as the Imperium has existed. He finds him/herself assigned to the Terminator company. Among the thousand warriors that compose a Space Marine Chapter, only the hundred most valorous and gifted brothers are deemed worthy enough of this honour. Terminators are the Chapter's ultimate warriors. They are protected by suits that make them all but impervious to conventional weaponry, and armed with the most devastating weaponry available.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960927T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Space Hulk - Vengeance of the Blood Angels (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Space Hulk - Vengeance of the Blood Angels (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Space Hulk - Vengeance of the Blood Angels (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13318" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Space Jam (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Space Jam </name>
    <desc>Based on the movie of the same name, Space Jam centres around an invasion of Looney Tunes land by tiny aliens. The fate of the Tunes is to be decided by a basketball game, and for this the aliens turn into the huge, evil Monstars.

The game is about two thirds basketball sim and then minigames are stuck in to fill all the gaps. You can play as the Monstars or the Looney Tunes who have the help of Michael Jordan. The basketball games themselves come in two flavours, two-on-two and three-on-three.

Successful completion of the minigames upgrades your character's abilities on the court. There are several - one involves finding MJ's basketball togs, one is a space race in the style of the retro Micro Machines games. There are about five minigames in all, and a player from both teams participates.

The multiplayer is a big aspect of the game. There is the traditional two-player versus, one team Tunes, one team Monstars, and there is also co-operative mode. In this two or even three players can play on the same team. Using multitaps, you can actually have a three-on-three game.

The Tunes roster is made up of Michael Jordan, Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Lola Bunny, Taz, Foghorn Leghorn, Pepé Le Pew, Sylvester, Wile E. Coyote, Porky Pig, Elmer Fudd and Yosemite Sam. The Monstars have access to Pound, Bupkus, Bang, Blanko and Nawt.

There are three statistics in the game, namely Speed, Shooting and Rebounds. These are pretty self-explanatory, but there is another more subtle one that's similar to stamina. Throughout the course of play your characters will get tired and lose their focus. A successful slam dunk usually tops this up.

The closest thing the game has to a single player mode is the Intergalactic Tournament (though it can be played multiplayer). This is a series of five matches in a row. One captain is picked and plays every game, while the rest of the team is substituted in and out.

There is no real way to progress in the game as it does not support memory cards. Space Jam has more of an arcade, lighthearted feel to it.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19970314T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Basketball-Sports-Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-6</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Space Jam (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Space Jam (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Space Jam (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13293" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Spot Goes to Hollywood (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Spot Goes to Hollywood </name>
    <desc>The central character in this game is Spot, the little red guy from the 7-Up TV commercials.  Spot has somehow become trapped in a movie projector.  As he jumps from film to film, he encounters many classic film genres that make up all the different levels of the game.  The main levels are a pirate movie, an adventure movie, and a horror movie, but there are many other bonus films to unlock.

The game is played from an isometric perspective.  As you control spot, you have to collect 5 Hollywood stars per level to unlock hidden areas and ultimately complete the game 100%.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19970122T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Burst Studios</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Spot Goes to Hollywood (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Spot Goes to Hollywood (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Spot Goes to Hollywood (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="152265" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./StarFighter 3000 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>StarFighter 3000  </name>
    <desc>You are the only crack pilot who can test the most advanced ship ever to join the FedNet fleet. Get ready to put your life into the hands of the boys in R&amp;D. 60 tough missions test your metal against hundreds of enemies. Immerse yourself in a vast 3D world. Soar. Explore. Scorch thousands of enemy targets. Battle on the ground, at sea, in the air, and in space-even the sky is no limit for this mighty ship. But don't lose your head, or you'll find the inventive aliens using it as a souvenir ash tray.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960621T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/StarFighter 3000 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/StarFighter 3000 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/StarFighter 3000 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13099" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Story of Thor 2, The (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Story of Thor 2, The </name>
    <desc>The Story of Thor 2, known in Japan as Thor: Seireioukiden and the US as The Legend of Oasis, is video game on the Sega Saturn console. It is the prequel to The Story of Thor: A Successor of the Light/Beyond Oasis on the Sega Mega Drive. The music was composed by Yuzo Koshiro, who is also famous for composing music for the Streets of Rage series.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19960919T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ancient</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Story of Thor 2, The (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Story of Thor 2, The (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Story of Thor 2, The (Europe).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13165" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Street Fighter - The Movie (USA) (8S).chd</path>
    <name>Street Fighter - The Movie  </name>
    <desc>Street Fighter: The Movie is a Saturn fighting game. This is the Street Fighter movie adaptation with Jean-Claude Van Damme. The game features digitized characters and places great importance on character specialties and the combos they can achieve.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19950810T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Street Fighter - The Movie (USA) (8S).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Street Fighter - The Movie (USA) (8S).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Street Fighter - The Movie (USA) (8S).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13146" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams </name>
    <desc>Street Fighter Alpha : Warriors' Dreams sur Saturn est un jeu de combat en 2D qui réunit bon nombre de personnages connus de la série. Choisissez parmi une trentaine de combattants et débloquez-en plusieurs autres totalement inédits. Le titre permet d'affronter un ami.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960522T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Fight / 2D-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Street Fighter Alpha - Warriors' Dreams (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13110" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Street Fighter Alpha 2 </name>
    <desc>Another Street Fighter sequel (this time for Street Fighter Alpha) adds even more to the classic fighting series.

New characters in this version include Gen (a wise kung-fu master), Rolento (who you may remember from another Capcom classic, Final Fight) and Sakura, a young school girl who follows her hero Ryu so close, she has the same type of moves. Dhalsim and Zangief also return to the fight with some news moves.

The other major difference is the loss of chain-combos and the gain of a custom combo system. Once you reach the required level (which is 1 at the least) you can execute a custom combo by combining any of the buttons (which there are 6 in total) or any of the special attacks (fireballs, etc.)</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13148" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Street Fighter Collection (USA).m3u</path>
    <name>Street Fighter Collection </name>
    <desc>Street Fighter Collection is a bundle comprising several different games of the Street Fighter series. It includes:

1. Super Street Fighter II: The New Challengers
2. Super Street Fighter II Turbo
3. Street Fighter Alpha 2 Gold (updated Street Fighter Alpha 2 with balancing fixes: Evil Ryu and Cammy added as playable characters, timing of some characters changed)</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19971211T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Compilation-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Street Fighter Collection (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Street Fighter Collection (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Street Fighter Collection (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13280" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Street Racer (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Street Racer </name>
    <desc>Street Racer is a kart racing game similar to Super Mario Kart.

Up to four players can play by split-screen. If there are no human opponents, the player can drive against seven computer opponents in three leagues. If the player wins the first league, they can play the second and so on. The game has eight different vehicles with different skills in speed, haste or resistance. There are also some power-ups on the tracks such as bombs, nitro fuel, and health packs.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19961116T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Vivid Image</developer>
    <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Street Racer (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Street Racer (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Street Racer (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13351" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo </name>
    <desc>A Tetris-like puzzle game featuring popular characters from many Capcom games.

Colored gems fall from the top of the screen in pairs, but this time lining up those of the same color is not enough. To break the gems and punish your opponent with counter gems you have to place a crash gem of the same color next to the gems. If you make a block of gems of the same color they'll fuse, forming a power gem. Breaking a power gem sends more counter gems to your opponent than breaking the same amount of gems in some other configuration. But the ultimate attack is breaking power gems in chain.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19970124T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Super Puzzle Fighter II Turbo (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13212" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Terry Pratchett's Discworld (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Terry Pratchett's Discworld  </name>
    <desc>This adventure game puts you in the shoes of Rincewind, a wizard whose sole purpose in life is to stay alive. He appears to be very good at it as well, because apparently the universe has decided to continuously challenge him.

The game takes place in the insane fantasy world created by Terry Pratchett, one of this world's most humourous authors, and is generally nuts.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Perfect World</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Terry Pratchett's Discworld (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Terry Pratchett's Discworld (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Terry Pratchett's Discworld (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13377" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tetris Plus (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Tetris Plus </name>
    <desc>This is yet another updated version of Tetris which was released for PlayStation, Saturn, and Game Boy.  This version features Classic mode, Puzzle mode, Versus mode, and Edit mode.  In Puzzle mode, you must save the professor who climbs his way to the top.  In order to do that, you must clear the blocks away and bring him to the bottom.  Versus mode brings you head to head with another player.  Edit mode allows you to create and save your own custom levels.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19960930T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Natsume</developer>
    <publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Tetris Plus (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Tetris Plus (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Tetris Plus (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13082" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Theme Park (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Theme Park </name>
    <desc>Dominating the exciting world of Theme Park ownership is your goal in this strategy game from Bullfrog. The first task is to set up your rides within the available land, structuring convenient paths and queues and ideally leaving some space for bigger rides once they become available, and include some lakes and trees to increase the park's allure. Rides range from Teacups and Haunted Houses to the biggest most elaborate roller-coaster you can design, and water rides that loop around other rides.

Shops must also be included, so that the visitors can buy food, drinks and souvenirs - the cunning player will combine salt, sugar and caffeine settings to maximize consumer interest. Staff must be hired to keep everything running smoothly, and they will only work for what they consider a fair rate of pay.

You are competing against other Theme Parks, so don't let them get an advantage over you - monitor your success in attracting customers and financial viability closely using the supplied statistics pages. More important, ensure that research is adequately funded to produce new rides.

It can be played in three modes - Sandbox level lets you concentrate on the park design elements, while Sim and Full add more strategic features.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19951101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Krisalis Software Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Theme Park (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Theme Park (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Theme Park (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13248" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Three Dirty Dwarves (USA) (RE).chd</path>
    <name>Three Dirty Dwarves  </name>
    <desc>Three Dirty Dwarves is a side-scrolling action game with an interesting plot: genetically altered "super kids" playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons open a portal that allows their "alter-egos" (the three dirty dwarves) to enter our world and try to rescue them from their evil Army Base captivity.

Once the dwarves arrive, they ransack the local "armory" (a sporting goods store) for weapons and set off to rescue the kids. The portal also lets in a number of fantasy bad guys too and they must be squashed on the way.

The main game mechanics allows the player to switch between each dwarf and uses its special attack (e. g. baseball bat and baseballs, bowling pins and bowling balls, and a shotgun). Additionally, there is the DwarfMorph" attack where the dwarves act as one.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960927T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Appaloosa</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-3</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Three Dirty Dwarves (USA) (RE).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Three Dirty Dwarves (USA) (RE).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Three Dirty Dwarves (USA) (RE).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13374" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Thunderstrike 2 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Thunderstrike 2 </name>
    <desc>Your name is General John T. Maclaine and you are the pilot of Firestorm 1, the lead dog in special attack missions to various parts of the world. Your helicopter is extremely powerful and carries the following weapons: 30mm Chain Gun, Firestorm Homing Missile, Rocket Pod, Runaway Cratering System (bombs), the Mk-84 500-Pound Bomb, Cluster Bombs, and the Anti-Ship Missile. These weapons -- plus excellent evasive, and attack maneuvers -- should be enough to help you succeed in attacks on drug runners and terrorists, from Columbia to Iraq. 
 
Thunder Strike 2 is the sequel to Core's Amiga, ST, PC &amp; Sega CD game, AH-3 Thunderstrike. Like the previous game in the series, this is a helicopter simulator/shooter. It features realistic features like multiple weapons selection, full freedom of movement, and a mission-based structure. On the other hand, it also throws lots and lots of enemy tanks and helicopters at you to blow up.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>U.S. Gold</developer>
    <publisher>Core Design</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Thunderstrike 2 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Thunderstrike 2 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Thunderstrike 2 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="152243" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tilt! (Europe) (En,Fr,De).chd</path>
    <name>Tilt!  </name>
    <desc>Hyper 3D Pinball, also known as Tilt!, is a pinball game. Players can choose between 6 boards to play, in 3D full screen-modus or in classic 2D scroll-modus. The themes of the pinballs are Science Fiction (Star Quest), Horror (Monster), Racing (Road King), Underworld (Gangster), Fantasy (Myst &amp; Majik) and Fair (Funfair). Every pinball has multi-ball gaming, animations during the game and intermezzos in the scoring field.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960906T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>NMS Software</developer>
    <publisher>Virgin</publisher>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Tilt! (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Tilt! (Europe) (En,Fr,De).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Tilt! (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="13469" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./TNN Motor Sports HardCore 4X4 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>TNN Motor Sports HardCore 4X4 </name>
    <desc>Hardcore 4x4 (initially known as TNN Motorsports Hardcore 4X4 in the US and known as Deka Yonku ~Tough The Truck~in Japan) is a racing video game developed by Gremlin Interactive for the Sega Saturn, PlayStation and Microsoft Windows. It became available for download from PlayStation Store as a PSone Classic for play on the PlayStation 3 on January 10, 2008, in PAL regions.[4] The game utilizes 3D environments and truck models. The soundtrack features hard rock music. It was the first game to feature vehicles with independent suspension.[citation needed] 
 
In 1996, ASC (publisher) hired Top Dog Entertainment in Austin, Texas, to develop Hardcore 4x4 II (the second version). The first Sony PlayStation developer in the Americas, Brett Butler, was lead programmer. He travelled to England to collect the game code and world builder tools. Both were defective, so he spent the first month repairing the code base. He then designed new tracks, rebuilt the graphics engine in MIPS RISC R3000 assembly, and hired artists and designers to create new tracks, menu interfaces, and vehicles. The title was completed in late 1997 as Top Dog went out of business shortly after Brett Butler left the company.[citation needed]</desc>
    <releasedate>19961220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/TNN Motor Sports HardCore 4X4 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/TNN Motor Sports HardCore 4X4 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/TNN Motor Sports HardCore 4X4 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13075" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tomb Raider (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Tomb Raider </name>
    <desc>Lara Croft is a Tomb Raider, an archaeologist who explores ancient sites in search of valuable artifacts.  In the game, Lara Croft is hired to retrieve an artifact from a tomb in Peru, which turns out to be one of three parts of the Atlantean Scion.  Soon betrayed by her employer, Lara Croft travels to Greece, Rome and Egypt to recover the other parts before this powerful device falls into the wrong hands.

Tomb Raider is a 3D action/adventure game in which players control Lara Croft from a third person perspective.  The camera follows Lara as she climbs, jumps, and swims through detailed environs overcoming environmental obstacles and deadly fauna.  Moving through levels often involves finding spots where Lara can climb, looking for spots where Lara can use her acrobatic ability, and sliding blocks and pushing levers to solve puzzles and open passageways.

Lara is armed with, now trademark, twin pistols with infinite ammunition, but she can pick up higher caliber weapons to take on deadlier human opponents.  Lara also comes across restorative health packs and has a compass with which she can orient herself.  Lara’s opponents include animals, gunmen, as well as primeval and supernatural beings.  Careful explorers can also find secret areas and avoid traps.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19961024T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Core Design</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Tomb Raider (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Tomb Raider (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Tomb Raider (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13176" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Torico (Europe).m3u</path>
    <name>Torico </name>
    <desc>As Torico opens, a traveler called Fred finds himself imprisoned in Misty Town jail. He came to the village in search of answers to his past, a past of which he has no recollection. On his head, he bears a crescent shaped tattoo. In his cell, Fred meets the strange and seemingly all-knowing Anthony, who tells him of the legends of the City of Moons. It is said that the road to the City lies through the Misty Town. Anthony offers him the key to his cell, but after an attempted escape, Fred quickly finds himself back in the hands of Lord Gordon, the ruthless town ruler.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19970531T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>System Sacom</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Torico (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Torico (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Torico (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="152268" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Trash It (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Trash It  </name>
    <desc>Trash It is an arcade action game where player(s) have to destroy buildings with a gigantic hammers. As a player, you take a role of construction worker who has only one mission: To smash everything to bits. Pieces are flying and houses falling as players hack their way through levels and earning points as they go.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Rage Software</developer>
    <publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Trash It (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Trash It (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Trash It (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13326" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./True Pinball (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>True Pinball </name>
    <desc>True Pinball is a console version of Pinball Illusions that has 4 different tables, named "Extreme Sports", "Vikings - The Tales", "Ricochet" and "Babewatch".

Both 2D and 3D views (not available in computer versions) are available and over 32,000 colors in high resolutions boost it visually.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960405T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Digital Illusions</developer>
    <publisher>Ocean</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Pinball</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/True Pinball (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/True Pinball (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/True Pinball (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="154863" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tunnel B1 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).chd</path>
    <name>Tunnel B1  </name>
    <desc>Tunnel B1, later released as 3D Mission Shooting: Finalist in Japan, is a sci-fi first person shooter developed by NEON Software and published by Ocean in 1996 for the Sega Saturn, Sony PlayStation and DOS comptuers. It features a soundtrack by Chris Hülsbeck of Turrican fame.nnThe game has the player navigate tunnels in a hovercraft destroying enemies.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19961016T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>NEON Software</developer>
    <publisher>Gaga Communications</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Tunnel B1 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Tunnel B1 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Tunnel B1 (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13107" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 </name>
    <desc>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 combines the best of all the Mortal Kombats into a single cartridge. 23 playable characters are immediately available, such as Reptile, Cyrax, Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Jax, Katana, Sonya, and more. There are two bosses that are unlockable, as well as additional characters.

There is a variety of new levels, some of which are interactive. Characters can uppercut someone, causing them to hit the ground hard and crash through to the bottom floor, or they can knocked someone off a bridge, landing in a pit of spikes.

Players can go against the computer one-on-one, two-on-two, or take part in the 8-fighter tournament.

The DS version has a wireless one-one-one multiplayer mode and includes the Puzzle Kombat mini-game from Mortal Kombat: Deception.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960601T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</developer>
    <publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126530" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Valora Valley Golf (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Valora Valley Golf </name>
    <desc>Valora Valley Golf is an exaggerated approach to the world of golfing. While it does feature traditional golf course hazards like water hazards and bunkers, lava pits and greens on top of a mountain are also present. 
 
The courses ranges from basic looking golf courses with long fairways where the player can drive the ball 450 yards in one shot and giant water hazards to ancient ruins and a course inside of a volcano. 
 
The controls are simplistic, click one time to bring up a meter, clicking again to set the angle and once more for how much power to drive the ball with special shots are obtained at the end of the meter. It doesn't feature any real life golfers or courses.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19960412T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>T&amp;E Soft</developer>
    <publisher>VIC Tokai</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Sports / Golf</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Valora Valley Golf (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Valora Valley Golf (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Valora Valley Golf (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13430" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Victory Boxing (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Victory Boxing </name>
    <desc>Center Ring Boxing is an unlicensed 3-D polygon boxing game where the player can choose from 30 different male or female boxers and compete in six different weight divisions.  They may also create their own boxer and use them to rise through the ranks to become champion choosing from one of five distinct styles of boxing.

There is also a trainer by the name of Snake that will help train the player as they progress thorough the game as well as become a selectable character along with a hidden character in two-player versus mode once the player becomes heavyweight champion.  A practice mode also is present that will allow the player to get accustomed to the game's controls and features 12 different camera angles and a replay mode that will the player to view their previous fight in it's entirety.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19951101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
    <publisher>JVC</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Boxing-Various-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Victory Boxing (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Victory Boxing (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Victory Boxing (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1540</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13265" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Cop (USA) (8S, 12S).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Cop  </name>
    <desc>Cast as one of two brave cops, players of Virtua Cop are charged with bringing down an evil crime syndicate that is running riot in some unspecified town. Dropped into a series of locations, one or two players must arm up and shoot their way through three death filled levels, in an attempt to restore peace and order. Played from a first person perspective view, players can use keys or joypad, to aim and fire at the multitude of sharp shooters who come gunning for them.
Starting the game armed with just a trusty old six-shooter, players can pick up more powerful, state-of-the-art weapons -- such as machine guns and shotguns -- as they progress. As these are hidden away in crates and the like, finding these weapons is an important part of the game and they can give players extra firepower when they most need it. In particular, such weapons can be extremely useful when trying to take on the customary end-of-level bosses. Made of stern stuff, you'll need all the help you can get in dispatching them off to hell.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19951202T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Cop (USA) (8S, 12S).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Cop (USA) (8S, 12S).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Cop (USA) (8S, 12S).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13141" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Cop 2 (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Cop 2 </name>
    <desc>Virtua Cop 2 follows the same gameplay pattern of its predecessor. You are a police officer sent after criminals, from subways and a bank to aboard helicopters. The game moves you automatically, although you can find hiding places to shoot from a safe angle. Your main task is to aim and fire your weapon so as to take out the bad guys for points. Avoid the innocents, as shooting them costs you points. The enemies have tougher firepower than in the original.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19961122T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Cop 2 (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Cop 2 (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Cop 2 (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13142" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Fighter (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Fighter </name>
    <desc>Virtua Fighter was the first of it's kind:  A one-on-one fighting game featuring fully 3D environments and characters. The fighters and arenas are rendered in flat-shaded polygons. Unlike many fighting games, Virtua Fighter focuses on deep gameplay based on actual fighting styles, rather than outrageous special moves and story lines.

There are 8 fighters to choose from in Virtua Fighter, and an equal number of fighting backdrops in which to compete. Each fighter has a distinctive fighting style, and their own set of signature moves.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19950511T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Fighter (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Fighter (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Fighter (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13113" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Fighter 2 (USA) (RE).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Fighter 2  </name>
    <desc>One year after after the first tournament Akira, Wolf, Pai, Jeffry, Kage, Jacky, Sarah and defending champion Lau are invited to the World Fighting Tournament, and are joined by the master of drunken Kung-Fu Shun-di, who wants to prove he's more than an old geezer and Lion Rafale, who's fighting for his freedom. Each fighter has his own style, from the lightning fast attacks of Pai to the powerful slams of Jeffry.

Home port of Sega's popular Model 2A arcade vs. fighter released in 1995. Game modes include classic arcade mode, 2P vs mode, Expert mode (where the computer character progressively learns and counters players' technique), Ranking Mode (similar to Arcade, but at the end, a fighting style analysis is shown based on number of specials and time to knock down an opponent), Team Battle Mode (two teams composed of five fighters go against each other, the first to beat five characters being the winner) and Watch mode (allows choosing two fighters and then see them fighting). Both VF2 and VF2.1 (a tweaked version available only in Japan) modes are included. Gameplay keeps the same style from the first game, adding more moves to each fighters' roll. Using a three-key layout (block, kick and punch, being possible to assign button combinations to the extra keys) the player is able to control their fighter, aiming to knock or push the opponent outside the rink inside the time limit. Combo moves range from the quickest, which require the player to push up to five buttons quickly, to strong moves that require more button presses along d-pad nudges to be successful. As with the previous game, fighting is realistic (except the physics-defying leaps), and each fighter has nothing but their body to harm the opponent.

While in comparison with the arcade version some parts took a hit on graphical quality (such as the texture details and backgrounds), the game uses the Saturn High-Resolution mode and flowing 60-fps  to bring the arcade experience home.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Fighter 2 (USA) (RE).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Fighter 2 (USA) (RE).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Fighter 2 (USA) (RE).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13214" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Fighter Kids (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Fighter Kids </name>
    <desc>Virtua Fighter Kids is a modified version of Virtua Fighter 2 for Sega Saturn. All characters were left the same but the difference is that they are no longer adults but kids with traditional anime huge heads and short arms and legs.

A variety of new features has been added to increase the gameplay such as the ability to program specified moves for each character or new endings.</desc>
    <rating>0.95</rating>
    <releasedate>19961003T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Fighter Kids (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Fighter Kids (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Fighter Kids (Europe).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13239" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Fighter Remix (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Fighter Remix </name>
    <desc>Akira Yuki, the only active master of the powerful Kung Fu technique known as Hakkyoku ken (“The Eight Point Fist") travels the world in search of enlightenment and worthy opponents. He has found them in in the World Fighting Tournament, where the strongest fighters determine who the master of hand-to-hand combat is. All techniques are allowed as long as the contestants use no weapons but their own bodies.

After weeks of trials, only seven other warriors remain:
Sarah Bryant and her brother Jacky, Lau Chan and his daughter Pai, Jeffry McWild, Wolf Hawkfield and the ninja Kagemaru.

Virtua Fighter PC (aka - Virtua Fighter PC Remix) is an enhanced port of Sega's arcade hit Virtua Fighter. It features the original characters and stages with higher polygon counts and texture mapping (a la Virtua Fighter 2) and various minor gameplay tweaks.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19951002T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SEGA</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Fighter Remix (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Fighter Remix (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Fighter Remix (USA).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13282" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Racing (USA) (15S).chd</path>
    <name>Virtua Racing  </name>
    <desc>Virtua Racing or V.R. for short, is a Formula One racing arcade game, developed by Sega AM2 and released in 1992. Virtua Racing was initially a proof-of-concept application for exercising a new 3D-graphics platform under development, the "Model 1". The results were so encouraging, that Virtua Racing was fully developed into a standalone arcade title. Though its use of 3D polygonal graphics was predated by arcade rivals Namco (Winning Run in 1988) and Atari (Hard Drivin' in 1989), Virtua Racing had vastly improved visuals in terms of polygon count, frame rate, and overall scene complexity, and displayed multiple camera angles and 3D human non-player characters, which all contributed to a greater sense of immersion. Virtua Racing is regarded as one of the most influential video games of all time, for laying the foundations for subsequent 3D racing games and for popularizing 3D polygonal graphics among a wider audience</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19951106T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Time Warner Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Time Warner Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtua Racing (USA) (15S).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtua Racing (USA) (15S).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtua Racing (USA) (15S).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13118" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtual Hydlide (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Virtual Hydlide </name>
    <desc>Virtual Hydlide is a 3D remake of the original Hydlide for the NES. You must defeat the evil demon Varalys, who turned a beautiful princess into three fairies. Before you confront the ultimate fiend, you must find the three fairies and restore the princess to her normal self by collecting three jewels.

You roam the 3D world of Hydlide, fighting monsters in real time, finding weapons and armor, descending into dungeons, hunting for treasure, and collecting points after defeating your foes, which you can then exchange for items. RPG elements are very slight, as you level up only after completing a portion of the game. You can also generate random maps by yourself and let the hero perform the same quest in your own world.</desc>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <releasedate>19950428T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>T&amp;E Soft</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtual Hydlide (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtual Hydlide (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtual Hydlide (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13188" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtual On - Cyber Troopers (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Virtual On - Cyber Troopers </name>
    <desc>Virtual-On : Cyber Troopers sur Saturn est un jeu de combat dans lequel vous pouvez voir s'affronter des colosses d'acier. Choisissez votre mécha-robot (grand robot) et activez la machine. Que ce soit avec une cyber-épée ou avec vos roquettes, réduisez en tas de ferraille vos adversaires avant que ce ne soit eux qui vous coupent les batteries.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19961108T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>CRI</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Virtual On - Cyber Troopers (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Virtual On - Cyber Troopers (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Virtual On - Cyber Troopers (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13090" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./WarCraft II - The Dark Saga (USA).chd</path>
    <name>WarCraft II - The Dark Saga </name>
    <desc>You take charge of either the humans and elves or the orcish hordes for control of the lands of Azeroth. Eventually you work through the dark portal and into the orcs homeland. You take charge of either side as you work through more than 20 missions per side in the fight for survival. 
 
New features for the console release include an auto-build option, where you can set a queue of units to be produced and the ability to select sixteen units at a time instead of the PC's nine.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19970820T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Climax</developer>
    <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/WarCraft II - The Dark Saga (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/WarCraft II - The Dark Saga (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/WarCraft II - The Dark Saga (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13407" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Whizz (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Whizz </name>
    <desc>Whizz is one of the few 3D platformers to use an isometric viewpoint. The controls reflect this, with moving the controller to the right actually moving the character down and right, moving it down and right moving the character down directly, and so on. Each level is played out against a time limit, and the paths through the level aren’t always clear-cut. There are four different types of doors, each of which needs a particular icon to pass (the icons represent the door type, such as ice or bricks, rather than hot water or a key, or anything you’d logically expect to clear the path). You can avoid the baddies, which may be the best option, as killing them costs you some energy –this reduces the significance of the points system.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19970829T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Microvalue</developer>
    <publisher>Konami</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Whizz (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Whizz (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Whizz (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126553" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Wing Arms (USA).chd</path>
    <name>Wing Arms </name>
    <desc>Wing Arms is action/shooter starring airplanes mainly from the WW2 era. There is very little simulation here as you shoot your way through levels where usually your mission is to shoot everyone, or to bomb certain targets. Night missions add to the variety. Gameplay is similar to the Wing Commander series, and is intended to be easy to play but hard to master.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19950929T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bell Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Wing Arms (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Wing Arms (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Wing Arms (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13191" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Winter Heat (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Winter Heat </name>
    <desc>Winter Heat is the home conversion of the DecAthlete (also known as Athlete Kings) sequel, replacing decathlon by Winter sports. Competition (in Arcade, Saturn or Practice modes) includes 11 events featuring eight athletes of different nationalities - Li Huang, Karl Vain, Joe Kudou, Ellen Reggiani, Aleksei Rigel and Rick Blade are joined by B.B. (replacing Jef Jansens, who appears as a secret athlete) and Johann Stensen (instead of Femi Kadiena). 

The game is a typical Winter-sports game, in the line of those released by Epyx but with a more arcade feel. The events include:

1. Speed Skiing: A simple dashing event where the goal is to descend the hill as fast as possible (in speeds over 200 km/h). Action is reduced to mash the button to gain speed.

2. Ski Jumping: Composed by four parts: The run up (mash the button to gain speed), the jump (selecting the angle), the flight (mash the button to gain extra length) and the landing (pressing the action button too early will lose valuable meters, too late will cost the jump).

3. Downhill: A simplified version of the real downhill event. It's impossible to miss the gates, and the challenge is to get a strong start-up, keep a straight path not losing speed hitting the fences and hitting the action button to jump hills perfectly.

4. Short Track Speed Skating: A straightforward event where the directional pad controls the direction of the athlete along the speed button to control the pace. As the event runs for over 40 seconds, it's possible to hold second position, making the opponent cut air resistance which allows the player to reach fastest speeds with less button presses.

5. Skeleton: The first event in the ice tunnels, it requires a fast run-up followed by a strong entrance in the tunnels. By pressing the action button it's possible to slow down the sled and make more controlled turns, or the athlete can fall from it, which not only loses time but also requires a small run-up.

6. Slalom: Just like the Downhill, it's impossible to miss a gate in the Slalom. After an initial sprint the player has to press the action button to approach each flag in the best way possible. Hitting the button too early or too late will make the athlete hit the flag, losing valuable time.

7. Aerial: An event similar to the Ski Jump. Instead of offering a "click-along" version, the player starts by setting the difficulty of the jump, and then three parts follow: in the run-up, the player sets the speed by mashing the speed button, followed by the jump which sets the strength (by pressing the action button) and when the athlete leaves the launch ramp, the player must mash the speed button once again to complete the jump. To complete a jump, the player must fill each section of the jump bar by making enough button presses

8. Bobsleigh: In all similar to the Skeleton, except there's no option to slow down.

9. Speed Skating: Another simple button-mashing event but with a twist: speed must be controlled on the turns, or the athlete will slip out losing a few seconds in the process. The speed can be controlled by a color graph above the power bar.

10. Snowboard: A mix between the Slalom and Downhill. There are several gates to be passed, plus two jumps. Unlike the other two events, it's possible to miss a gate, which carries a one second penalty for each missed.

11. Cross Country:
 The stamina-influenced event. There's a long track with some hills that can be taken for advantage, as during downhill slopes it's possible to gain a lot of speed without losing stamina.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19980213T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Data East</developer>
    <publisher>SEGA</publisher>
    <genre>Sports</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Winter Heat (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Winter Heat (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Winter Heat (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1536</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13225" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./WipEout (USA).chd</path>
    <name>WipEout </name>
    <desc>Wipeout is a futuristic racing game set in the year 2052. Racing for one of four teams, the player competes in the F3600 Anti-Gravity Racing League on six tracks. Each team's hovercraft racer has different ratings in speed, acceleration and turning. In addition to high-speed racing, there is also shooting in the game, with different weapon pickups like rockets and mines available, useful for slowing one's opponents down. Shields can also be picked up and can block the weapons' effects.

There are championship, single race and time trial modes. Winning the championship in the regular Venom class unlocks the Rapier class, where the craft are faster and the tracks have slightly different looks.

There is also a two-player mode where two opponents can race and shoot at each other.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Psygnosis</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/WipEout (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/WipEout (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/WipEout (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13150" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./WipEout 2097 (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>WipEout 2097 </name>
    <desc>WipEout XL is set in the year 2097, around four decades after its predecessor. Instead of the F3600 anti-gravity racing competition, the game features an even faster and more dangerous tournament: the F5000 AG league. The gameplay system is similar to that of the previous game: players race against each other or computer in high-speed futuristic environments, liberally picking up weapons scattered around the stages and using them against the opponents to finish the race in the highest position.

Each vehicle is provided with a shield; once this shield is breached (by weapons or other kinds of damage), the craft explodes. As in the first game, the vehicles move at very high speeds. The game's four difficulty levels are used to crank the speed up and down, with the highest setting corresponding to the highest speed. In addition to the main championship mode, there are also challenge modes, winning in which rewards the player with faster game settings, new tracks, and new vehicles.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19980305T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Psygnosis</developer>
    <publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/WipEout 2097 (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/WipEout 2097 (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/WipEout 2097 (Europe).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13127" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Worms (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Worms </name>
    <desc>Worms is a turn-based strategy game. It features up to 4 teams of 4 worms, aiming to destroy the others on a generated terrain. Each worm has 100 hit points, and dies when his hit points fall to 0. Upon death, a worm explodes, causing damage to everyone around.

Gameplay is turn-based. Each turn, the player can control one specific worm from his team. The worm can crawl left and right or jump. However, there is a time limit to make a move; also, if the worm falls from a great height, it loses health and the turn ends immediately; and if a worm falls into water or offscreen, it dies. Each turn, a worm can also make a single attack: the player can aim up and down, choose a weapon and then fire it. After attacking, the turn ends. 

There's a lot of weapons available - the standard ones as bazookas (which is affected by the (random) wind settings and gravity) and grenades. The others include a Fire Punch, dynamite, air strikes, and utilities such as ropes and girders.

There are 10 styles of terrain, ranging from forests and deserts to Candy land and the moon (complete with affected gravity). Shots leave craters in the ground, and complex tunnels can be formed.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19960702T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Team 17</developer>
    <publisher>Ocean</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-16</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Worms (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Worms (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Worms (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13376" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./WWF In Your House (USA).chd</path>
    <name>WWF In Your House </name>
    <desc>WWF In Your House includes 10 bodyslamming, mat-pounding, suplex-serving, ring-wrecking superstars including Bret "The Hitman" Hart, Ahmed Johnson, Vader, Goldust, The Ultimate Warrior, Owen Hart, Hunter Hearst Helmsley, British Bulldog, The Undertaker, and Shawn "The Heartbreak Kid" Michaels.

Experience a whole new level of hurt with hardcore super pin finishing moves, plus every superstar has their own personal fighting venue! With a houseful of superstar soundbites, WWF In Your House is a 10 man wrecking crew...and they've got your address!</desc>
    <rating>0.2</rating>
    <releasedate>19961108T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/WWF In Your House (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/WWF In Your House (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/WWF In Your House (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13276" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game (USA).chd</path>
    <name>WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game </name>
    <desc>WWF Wrestlemania: The Arcade Game merges the personalities and action of the popular WWF TV show characters with a Mortal Kombat-style fighting game. This title features digitized graphics of 8 WWF superstars: Doink, Razor Ramon, Bret "Hit Man" Hart, Shawn Michaels, The Undertaker, Yokozuna, Bam Bam Bigelow, and Lex Luger.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960809T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/WWF WrestleMania - The Arcade Game (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13153" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./X-Men - Children of the Atom (USA).chd</path>
    <name>X-Men - Children of the Atom </name>
    <desc>X-MEN UNLEASHED! A 100% conversion of the arcade mega-hit! It's here! Ultimate combat! Mutant mayhem! X-Power! Special moves! Mid-air action! Big characters! Sizzling graphics! Exactly like you played in the arcade! You will need all your mutant powers, all your speed, all your strength... for this is the ultimate combat! Have you got enough to defeat Magneto, Omega Red and the Sentinel? Are you tough enough for Wolverine, powerful enough for Cyclops, cool enough for Iceman... are you good enough to join the new breed of mutant heroes? X-Men Children of the Atom - the fighting game to end them all!</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19960405T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Rutubo Games</developer>
    <publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
    <genre>Fight-Fight / 2D</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/X-Men - Children of the Atom (USA).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/X-Men - Children of the Atom (USA).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/X-Men - Children of the Atom (USA).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="13169" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./X-Men vs. Street Fighter (Japan) (1M).chd</path>
    <name>X-Men vs. Street Fighter  </name>
    <desc>X-Men VS Street Fighter is one of the best 2D Fighting Game on the Saturn. It is an adaptation from the Arcade game. 
Let´s fight with all best Heroes from the Capcom family and the well-known mutants from X-Men world in nervous and dynamics fight. 
You have the possibility to create teams and swap your fighters during the fight.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19980416T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Capcom</developer>
    <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/X-Men vs. Street Fighter (Japan) (1M).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/X-Men vs. Street Fighter (Japan) (1M).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/X-Men vs. Street Fighter (Japan) (1M).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="126573" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Z (Europe).chd</path>
    <name>Z </name>
    <desc> 
Z is a real-time strategy game in which you fight for control of the sectors, some of which contains manufactories that can gain you additional units. Touch the "flag" in the sector and it's yours. Capture the sector before the new unit comes out of the manufactory and the new unit is yours. With six different robots (different armaments, armor, and speed), multiple vehicles (from jeeps to tanks) the robots can utilize, your ultimate objective is to destroy the opponent's base, and prevent him from doing the same to you.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>The Bitmap Brothers</developer>
    <publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./media/mixart/Z (Europe).png</image>
    <thumbnail>./media/wheel/Z (Europe).png</thumbnail>
    <video>./media/snap/Z (Europe).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
</gameList>