<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<gameList>
  <provider>
    <System>Sega Megadrive</System>
    <software>Skraper</software>
    <database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
    <web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
  </provider>
  <game id="1011" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./16t (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>16t</name>
    <desc>16t is a scrolling platform action game similar to Teddy Boy, in which the player controls a youngster in prison garb named Apple Gaikichi, who must eliminate all the enemies on each stage. Apple's only method of attack is throwing enormous 16 ton weights (thus the title), which can and will crush enemies in a bloody mess. However, these weights will bounce off each other, so the player must be careful to not let Apple get crushed himself. They are also not entirely unlimited, as the player can only hold five at once, and they must be allowed to recharge when Apple runs out. Enemies on each stage will appear from the top of the screen in waves, through a randomly cycling "slots" meter, and once all slots and enemies have been cleared, the player moves on to the next stage.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/16t (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/16t (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/16t (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18364" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./A Ressha de Ikou MD (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>A Ressha de Ikou MD</name>
    <desc>A Ressha de Ikou MD is a real-time railroad simulation game, and part of the A-Train series from Artdink. Based on the first two games in the series, in each scenario the player must use the resources at hand to build a railroad connecting from one end of a map to the other. During the day, the titular "A-Train" can be controlled, by which the player can build tracks and stations. During the night, train schedules can be modified. As the player builds, development will spring up around the tracks and stations, bringing in income by which more tracks and stations can be built.

The game offers a total of five different scenarios of increasing difficulty, ranging from a practice scenario for beginners to very difficult scenarios for experienced players. There are also three different game speed settings available.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19920410T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>MNM Software</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/A Ressha de Ikou MD (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/A Ressha de Ikou MD (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/A Ressha de Ikou MD (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1012" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Aa Harimanada (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Aa Harimanada</name>
    <desc>Aa Harimanada is a sumo wrestling game based on the manga and anime created by Kei Sadayasu. As in the real sport, the goal is to knock the opponent out of the ring. However, it is not a particularly realistic interpretation of sumo, playing much like a traditional 1-vs-1 fighting game. There are grabs, throws, and special moves, and the player can also win by knockout by draining the opponent's stamina. There is a single-player mode that follows the story of protagonist Harimanada, as well as a versus mode for one or two players where any of 15 characters can be used.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Megasoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Aa Harimanada (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Aa Harimanada (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Aa Harimanada (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="283" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Advanced Busterhawk Gleylancer (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Advanced Busterhawk Gleylancer</name>
    <desc>A side-scrolling sci-fi shooter, Gleylancer casts you as Lucia, a young pilot in the Space Fleet of starfighters that hijacks the experimental Gleylancer fighter to go explore the outer borders of known space in search of her missing father. Along the way Lucia will have to shoot down dozens of enemies in standard shooter fashion, while avoiding destruction and collecting power-ups that extend her ship's energy, upgrade weapons and gather screen-clearing bombs.

The Gleylancer comes equipped with two hovering satellites that can receive weapon upgrades of their own, and can lock their positions at specific angles to increase your firepower and protect the player from enemy attacks. Features only a single-player campaign with two different endings depending on how the final stages are completed (e.g. if Lucia's father is rescued or not). </desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19920717T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Masaya Games</developer>
    <publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Advanced Busterhawk Gleylancer (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Advanced Busterhawk Gleylancer (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Advanced Busterhawk Gleylancer (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="38952" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Advanced Daisenryaku - Deutsch Dengeki Sakusen (Japan) (Rev A) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Advanced Daisenryaku - Deutsch Dengeki Sakusen</name>
    <desc>Advanced Daisenryaku: Deutsch Dengeki Sakusen  commonly referred to simply as Advanced Daisenryaku, is a 1991 strategy game developed jointly by Sega and SystemSoft and published by Sega for the Sega Mega Drive exclusively in Japan. It is part of SystemSoft's Daisenryaku series of strategy games, and is one of the few retail Mega Drive games to have online play compatibility via Sega Meganet. It also started the Advanced Daisenryaku line, all of which have been published by Sega. 
 
Sega and now-renamed SystemSoft Alpha rereleased the game in 2006 as part of Sega Ages 2500. 
 
In 2002-2006, Nebelwurfer fan-translated the game to English as Advanced Military Commander along with a translated manual.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19910617T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Systemsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Various</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Advanced Daisenryaku - Deutsch Dengeki Sakusen (Japan) (Rev A) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Advanced Daisenryaku - Deutsch Dengeki Sakusen (Japan) (Rev A) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Advanced Daisenryaku - Deutsch Dengeki Sakusen (Japan) (Rev A) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1015" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Adventurous Boy - Mao Xian Xiao Zi (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Adventurous Boy - Mao Xian Xiao Zi</name>
    <desc>Adventurous Boy: Mao Xian Xiao Zi is an unlicensed Fantasy Zone clone, though features completely original graphics and sound.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>GameTek</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Adventurous Boy - Mao Xian Xiao Zi (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Adventurous Boy - Mao Xian Xiao Zi (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Adventurous Boy - Mao Xian Xiao Zi (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="109050" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Aladdin II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Aladdin II</name>
    <desc>Aladdin II is an unlicensed Mega Drive port of the SNES version of Disney's Aladdin, originally made by Capcom in 1994. 
It was developed by an unknown company and was likely published by X Boy. 
This port can be considered the "opposite" of Aladdin 2000, a port of Virgin's Aladdin to the SNES. 
Some of Aladdin's moves as well as some of the enemy sprites can be found in Hercules 2, which was published by X Boy in 1999.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Aladdin II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Aladdin II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Aladdin II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1018" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Aworg (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Aworg</name>
    <desc>Aworg is an Action game, developed and published by Sega,  which was released in Japan in 1991.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Aworg (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Aworg (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Aworg (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18366" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bahamut Senki (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Bahamut Senki</name>
    <desc>The world of Bahumut is divided into eight powerful countries, four of which are ruled by humans or human-like creatures, while the other four are ruled by evil forces. These countries constantly wage war against one another trying to dominate and destroy the others. It's the player's job to choose which country to control and make it the most powerful country in all of Bahumut.   
  
At the beginning of each turn, you control your leader and take certain actions such as: recruit soldiers, declare war, engage in diplomatic talks, ect. In battles you can control several units of soldiers or magical creatures you can summon to assist you in battle.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19910308T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bahamut Senki (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bahamut Senki (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Bahamut Senki (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="155462" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bao Xiao San Guo (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bao Xiao San Guo</name>
    <desc>Bao Xiao San Guo is an unlicensed turn-based tactical role-playing game for the Sega Mega Drive by C&amp;E Inc. released in some unknown year.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>C&amp;E</developer>
    <genre>Strategy-Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bao Xiao San Guo (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bao Xiao San Guo (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Bao Xiao San Guo (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="143230" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bare Knuckle III (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Bare Knuckle III</name>
    <desc>Streets of Rage 3 aimed to build on the success of its predecessor, so while the style of gameplay and control scheme is largely identical to its predecessors, significant changes were made to the overall structure of the game. Streets of Rage 3 is a faster paced release with longer levels, a more complex plot (which in turn leads to more in-depth scenarios complete with interactive levels and multiple endings) and the return of traps such as pits. Dash and dodge moves were added to each character's arsenal of moves, and weapons can now only be used for a few times before breaking. 
 
Changes to the fighting mechanics allows for the integration of weapons with certain movesets. Team attacks, absent from Streets of Rage 2 but available in the original Streets of Rage, make a return, and are occasionally used by enemies too. Blitz moves, performed while running, have also been altered and are now upgradable over the course of the game (predicated on how many points are earned per level). Death causes a downgrade, however holding the X button before a series of button combinations can give players access to the upgraded moveset at any point in the game, at the expense of the time taken to perform attacks. 
 
Enemies are also smarter with weapons, and some can even steal health upgrades, and there are also several secret playable characters, unlockable after overcoming certain conditions during the game. Special moves also no longer drain the user's health - a separate, automatically regenerating bar is introduced for this purpose.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940318T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bare Knuckle III (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bare Knuckle III (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Bare Knuckle III (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1020" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Barver Battle Saga - Tai Kong Zhan Shi (Taiwan) (Unl) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Barver Battle Saga - Tai Kong Zhan Shi</name>
    <desc>Humans and daemons develop civilization independently using technology and magic, respectively. Technology comes to triumph over magic, and the world is destroyed in an technological accident. Survivors continued without technology for a thousand years, until the old technology was discovered and returned to use. 
 
Furthermore, the world is divided into four kingdoms, each representing one of the four natural forces and with four temples: Cruz, whose Moon Temple controls water, Galien, whose Sun Temple controls the earth, Zak, whose Star Temple controls technology, and Lear, whose Wind Temple controls wind. 
 
Now the daemons have returned... 
 
</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chuanpu</developer>
    <publisher>Chuanpu</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Barver Battle Saga - Tai Kong Zhan Shi (Taiwan) (Unl) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Barver Battle Saga - Tai Kong Zhan Shi (Taiwan) (Unl) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Barver Battle Saga - Tai Kong Zhan Shi (Taiwan) (Unl) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1021" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Golfer Yui (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Battle Golfer Yui</name>
    <desc>Gil Hazard, president of the Hazard Foundation, is secretly Professor G, the leader of the evil Dark Hazard organization. He has designs on world domination, and has plans to use the power of golf toward this end; this is the Battle Golfer project. Yui Mizuhara and Ran Ryuzaki are two ordinary high school girls who just so happen to be golf prodigies, and so are prime candidates for the Battle Golfer project. They are abducted by Professor G, but are rescued by a mysterious man before they can be taken under his control. Having escaped, Yui hears about a golf tournament being held by the Hazard Foundation, and suspecting more nefarious plans, she secretly enters the tournament to stop him for good.

Battle Golfer Yui is a unique genre fusion between a golf game and a Japanese-style adventure game. The main adventure mode casts the player as Yui competing in the Hazard Cup tournament. The player can interact with other characters on the course, and will need to defeat several different opponents at match play on oddly-themed courses in order to proceed. The system is quite simple and fast-paced; simply choose a direction, a club, spin, and hit the bar with the right timing to adjust shot power. Each character also has special abilities to help them out, but these are limited in use. There is also a regular golf mode for one or two players, offered as both stroke and match play.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Santos</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games-Sports / Golf-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Battle Golfer Yui (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Battle Golfer Yui (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Battle Golfer Yui (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1022" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Mania Daiginjou (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Battle Mania Daiginjou</name>
    <desc>The Trouble Shooters, Mania Otorii and Maria Haneda, are a pair of bounty hunters who will take any job that involves lots of trouble and plenty of shooting. Their last job saw them saving the Crown Prince Denka from the evil military mastermind Don Morguestein, presumably ending his evil plans. However, three days later, Morguestein has returned once more to take revenge upon the Trouble Shooters. Mania and Maria, never wanting to miss out on the action, head off to take care of him once and for all.

Battle Mania Daiginjo is a comical anime-themed scrolling shooter, and the sequel to Trouble Shooter. The player controls the Dirty Pair-esque Mania and Maria simultaneously, with Maria following closely behind Mania, and also able to turn around and fire to the rear. Unlike most shooters, Mania has a health meter which can be replenished via pickups. There are a variety of weapons to choose from at the start of each stage, and during the game, weapons can be powered up. There is also a screen-clearing bomb attack, but it must be allowed to charge back up each time it is used.

The game includes a standard single-player mode with three difficulty settings. There is also a score attack mode which challenges the player to earn the most points possible in two minutes on a set stage. </desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Vic Tokai Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Tokai Engineering</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Battle Mania Daiginjou (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Battle Mania Daiginjou (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Battle Mania Daiginjou (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1022" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Battle Mania Daiginjou - Trouble Shooter Vintage (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Battle Mania Daiginjou - Trouble Shooter Vintage</name>
    <desc>The Trouble Shooters, Mania Otorii and Maria Haneda, are a pair of bounty hunters who will take any job that involves lots of trouble and plenty of shooting. Their last job saw them saving the Crown Prince Denka from the evil military mastermind Don Morguestein, presumably ending his evil plans. However, three days later, Morguestein has returned once more to take revenge upon the Trouble Shooters. Mania and Maria, never wanting to miss out on the action, head off to take care of him once and for all.

Battle Mania Daiginjo is a comical anime-themed scrolling shooter, and the sequel to Trouble Shooter. The player controls the Dirty Pair-esque Mania and Maria simultaneously, with Maria following closely behind Mania, and also able to turn around and fire to the rear. Unlike most shooters, Mania has a health meter which can be replenished via pickups. There are a variety of weapons to choose from at the start of each stage, and during the game, weapons can be powered up. There is also a screen-clearing bomb attack, but it must be allowed to charge back up each time it is used.

The game includes a standard single-player mode with three difficulty settings. There is also a score attack mode which challenges the player to earn the most points possible in two minutes on a set stage. </desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Vic Tokai Corporation</developer>
    <publisher>Tokai Engineering</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em up / Horizontal-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Battle Mania Daiginjou - Trouble Shooter Vintage (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Battle Mania Daiginjou - Trouble Shooter Vintage (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Battle Mania Daiginjou - Trouble Shooter Vintage (Japan, Korea) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="273" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon</name>
    <desc>The game is based on the popular manga/animé series of the same name. The heroine of the series is a 14-year-old schoolgirl named Serena (Usagi in the Japanese version). One day she encounters a magical talking cat named Luna, who tells her she has been chosen to be a Sailor Moon fighter, to find the lost Princess of the Moon Kingdom and to fight the forces of darkness lead by the evil Queen Beryl. 

This adaptation of the story is a beat-'em-up game. You can control either Serena herself or one of her Sailor Moon companions. Each girl has different strengths and special attacks. You advance in the game by moving on a platform and defeating the enemies you encounter. You can't move on if you haven't defeated all the enemies that keep coming at you. </desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19940708T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Arc System Works</developer>
    <publisher>Ma-Ba</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="124888" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bomber (Brazil) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bomber</name>
    <desc>Unofficial port of Bomberman.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bomber (Brazil) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bomber (Brazil) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="64833" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bomboy (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bomboy</name>
    <desc>It is a simple clone of Bomberman. Bomboy is said to have been a pack-in game with the unlicensed Dynacom Megavision console.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bomboy (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bomboy (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Bomboy (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="103612" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Bug's Life, A (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Bug's Life, A</name>
    <desc>Pixar's second animated feature, A Bug's Life, arrived in movie theatres in 1998, and the videogame adaptation was released on the Nintendo GameBoy Color and the Sony Playstation. 
 
It wasn't supposed to appear on the Genesis at all -- Sega's 16-bit system was well past its commercial prime by the late 1990's, even on the hand-me-down/bedroom system basis that tends to keep a trickle of kids' titles coming late in a console's life.  And it never did in any legal form.  But enterprising Asian game pirates saw an opportunity to cash in on Sega and Disney in one go, and thus this wholly unlicensed conversion of the GameBoy Color version of A Bug's Life appeared on the Genesis:</desc>
    <releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>X BOY</developer>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Bug's Life, A (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Bug's Life, A (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Bug's Life, A (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18373" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Chibi Maruko-chan - Wakuwaku Shopping (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Chibi Maruko-chan - Wakuwaku Shopping</name>
    <desc>It's vacation time for Maruko and her friends. Hanawa, the ladies' man with rich parents, invites Maruko and Tamae to an island down south to relax, and rounding out the group, Maruo butts in and comes along as well. Since they're going to get souvenirs and such while they're there, they decide to make a game of it and see who is best at shopping!

Waku Waku Shopping is a sugoroku-style board game based on the popular characters created by Momoko Sakura. The game takes place on a board made up of various spaces: there are spaces which increase or decrease the character's money or happiness, spaces where the player can spend their money to buy things to increase their happiness, and spaces that trigger various events. The game ends when the goal has been reached a set number of times, and the winner is the player with the most happiness at the end of the game. Up to four players can play, with the computer taking control of any remaining characters.</desc>
    <rating>0.2</rating>
    <releasedate>19920114T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Chibi Maruko-chan - Wakuwaku Shopping (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Chibi Maruko-chan - Wakuwaku Shopping (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Chibi Maruko-chan - Wakuwaku Shopping (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1034" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Chou Kyuukai Miracle Nine (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Chou Kyuukai Miracle Nine</name>
    <desc>Chokyukai Miracle Nine is a fast-paced arcade-style baseball game similar to Konami's Power Pro series. The game has a cartoonish superdeformed visual style much like Konami's title, and also features an official NPB license, meaning it includes all 12 Central and Pacific League teams and full player rosters from the 1995 season.

The game offers a full-season "Pennant" mode, as well as All-Star and Exhibition matches for one or two players. You can also opt to watch the computer control both teams. The game also allows for simplified play per player, as well as shorter games with as few as three innings. </desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19950721T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Sports / Baseball</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Chou Kyuukai Miracle Nine (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Chou Kyuukai Miracle Nine (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Chou Kyuukai Miracle Nine (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1040" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Crayon Shin-chan - Arashi o Yobu Enji (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Crayon Shin-chan - Arashi o Yobu Enji</name>
    <desc>Five-year-old Shinnosuke Nohara is the epitome of noisy children: loud and inappropriate, infuriating to his parents, and hilarious to onlookers. Shin-chan is always getting in trouble with his parents and saying bizarre or offensive things to everyone he meets. Every so often, though, he'll try to do what his mom wants him to, but more often than not, he'll misunderstand and simply confound his parents further.

Arashi o Yobu Enji ("A Kindergartner Called Tempest") is one of many games based on the manga and anime created by Yoshito Usui. In four stages, each made up of five areas, Shin-chan must explore his neighborhood looking for a specific object. He can enter houses to ask people for information, but will often end up simply insulting them. He must also avoid or knock over the other children in the neighborhood, and has various ability cards that he can use to assist him, which might give him a water pistol or refill his health. After finding what he's looking for, Shin-chan will move on to the next area.

Also included is a minigame mode with eight different minigames, such as a bubble-blowing contest, a three-legged race, and a desperate search for clothing before school. The entire game, including the minigames, is filled with dialogue containing the same humor as the source material. </desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19940611T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ma-Ba</developer>
    <publisher>Ma-Ba</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Crayon Shin-chan - Arashi o Yobu Enji (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Crayon Shin-chan - Arashi o Yobu Enji (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Crayon Shin-chan - Arashi o Yobu Enji (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="150" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Curse (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Curse</name>
    <desc>Curse is a basic horizontal-scrolling shooter, one of the first released for the Megadrive, where one pilots a space fighter through deadly environments such as a mutated jungle, a ruined city, and an underground volcano. The game features five stages, and at several points in each stage, a larger boss enemy appears which must be destroyed to continue.

There a variety of weapon power-ups to collect, each with three power levels. There is a spread shot that can cover nearly the entire screen, a bomb that explodes into shrapnel when it connects, and a twisting wide shot that can pass through environmental obstacles. There are also homing missiles, smart bombs, speed-ups, and an option that can be placed on any side of the ship. The ship also has a shield which can absorb damage from smaller bullets, meaning it can take a few hits before exploding unless it's hit by an enemy ship, part of the landscape or some special enemy weapons that just ignore the shield.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19891223T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Micronet</developer>
    <publisher>Micronet</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up-Shoot'em up / Horizontal</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Curse (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Curse (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Curse (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1042" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Cutie Suzuki no Ringside Angel (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Cutie Suzuki no Ringside Angel</name>
    <desc>"Cutie Suzuki no Ringside Angel" is a wrestling game in which you can choose to play as one of the nine female wrestlers available. Each girl has her own strengths and weaknesses. There are three modes in the game: you can fight against any of the opponents with the character you have chosen; you can participate in a playoff tournament; and there is an additional "watch" mode in which you can simply watch the fights without participating. Beside the traditional moves, the wrestling style of the girls allows punching the opponents.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19901212T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Copya System Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Asmik</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Sports / Fighting</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Cutie Suzuki no Ringside Angel (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Cutie Suzuki no Ringside Angel (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Cutie Suzuki no Ringside Angel (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1540</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="611" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dahna - Megami Tanjou (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Dahna - Megami Tanjou</name>
    <desc>Dahna: Megami Tanjo (Dahna: Birth of a Goddess) is a beat'em up with some RPG elements. The player controls Dahna as she scrolls horizontally or vertically through the levels. Dahna fights her enemies using a sword, and she can jump in two heights, duck and crawl. Dahna has also a magic meter, which has several colored levels. Different levels of her magic will produce different magical effects (as in Golden Axe). Her magic can be replenished by gathering magical orbs, dropped by enemy mages when killed. They will also drop health orbs as well.

She starts the game "riding" a giant, and in other portions of the game, she'll also ride other creatures, such as a horse and a griffin. When riding a creature, Dahna can't use her magic powers.

As she kills enemies and gather orbs, Dahna gains experience points, which grant her level upgrades. Leveling up affects only her health, as she gains more health points. </desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>IGS</developer>
    <publisher>IGS</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dahna - Megami Tanjou (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dahna - Megami Tanjou (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dahna - Megami Tanjou (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="538" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dangerous Seed (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dangerous Seed</name>
    <desc>It is the 25th century, and the solar system has come under attack by an mysterious alien enemy known as Dangerous Seed. Human forces have been decimated, and the aliens' next target is Earth! The enemy draws closer to the frontline base on the moon by the hour, and the final line of defense for Earth, the fighter ship Moon Diver, has launched.

Dangerous Seed is a vertical scrolling shooter converted from the 1989 Namco coin-op. The player controls the three-part fighter ship Moon Diver through 12 stages to confront the alien menace and secure peace in the solar system. Each of the three parts of the ship, Alpha, Beta, and Gamma, have their own properties which can be combined in various ways. Each type and combination has multiple shot types which can be powered up, and there are also options and bombs available which contribute to Moon Diver's extensive arsenal.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19901218T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dangerous Seed (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dangerous Seed (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dangerous Seed (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1043" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Darwin 4081 (Japan, Korea).zip</path>
    <name>Darwin 4081</name>
    <desc>Lakya is a technologically-advanced civilization on a planet far from our own galaxy. The planet's inhabitants have unknowingly unleashed the planet's life force, Evol. As the Evol drifts from Lakya, it reaches a planet called Cokyo, whose inhabitants use it to attack and invade Lakya. Now, fighters from Lakya must fight back against the invading army by using the Evol themselves.

Darwin 4081 is a vertical scrolling shooter based on the 1987 Data East coin-op Super Real Darwin. The main attraction of the game is the ability to evolve your ship into a wide variety of different forms, each with their own attack abilities, by collecting DNA dropped by enemies. Other powerups will increase you ship's speed, give you an option that follows your ship, or even increase the power of your smart bombs. The game features surreal futuristic art design fitting of its title.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19900407T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Data East</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Darwin 4081 (Japan, Korea).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Darwin 4081 (Japan, Korea).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Darwin 4081 (Japan, Korea).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1045" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Daze Before Christmas (Australia).zip</path>
    <name>Daze Before Christmas</name>
    <desc>Christmas is a time where people get together and give others presents and spend all day eating food. But there's only one problem this year. You see, while Santa was sleeping in his bed, the cold and evil snowman spooked all the elves away, and the Timekeeper has stolen Santa's plans from his house. There won't be any Christmas if Santa doesn't stop them.

In Daze Before Christmas, you're Santa. According to the game's Christmas calender, you have 24 areas to explore such as factories, workshops, caves, and more. Each area is filled with nasty enemies like penguins, jack-in-the-boxes, helicopters, snowmen, and many others. Furthermore, after every five areas, Santa has to come face-to-face with not only The Evil Snowman, The Timekeeper, and Louse the Mouse,  but also Mr. Weather.

Santa's health is represented by five Santa hats. When Santa is hit by any one of his enemies, one hat is lost. If Santa loses all of his hats, then he will lose a life. He will then have to restart at the beginning of the area, unless he passes a gold bell somewhere in the area. When you explore each area, Santa can collect presents that contain a mini-Santa (aka: Extra Life), a red hat, or he may release an elf. Santa should be careful when opening these presents as some of them may contain bombs or other enemies. If Santa manages to find a spinning star, he must get it as this will take him to the next area.

Santa kills his enemies by throwing magic at them. In almost each area, Santa can get a cup of hot cocoa. Doing this will transform him into Anti-Santa, a type of Santa who wears nothing but white, grows Satan's horns on top of his head, is invincible, and comes equipped with a hammer in which he can use to bonk enemies with. The Anti-Santa business only lasts for 20 seconds, but this can be changed via the Options menu.

Daze acts like one of those platform games where you run through the level, shoot at enemies, and proceed to the exit. However, there are some areas where the gameplay changes, and these areas involve Santa flying through the sky in England, Russia, Japan, and the USA, and dropping presents in chimneys to score points. The game also uses a password-saving system, where entering a password given will allow gamers to restart at the beginning of a specific area, in case they happen to run out of lives.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Funcom</developer>
    <publisher>Funcom</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Daze Before Christmas (Australia).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Daze Before Christmas (Australia).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Daze Before Christmas (Australia).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="693" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Divine Sealing (Japan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Divine Sealing</name>
    <desc>Falchion is an ace pilot in the Space Defense Force, and the pilot of a space ship known as Divine. On his way back to his home planet, daydreaming about girls, Divine's computer picks up a transmission from a nearby planet. Answering the transmission, it turns out to be a distress call from a beautiful woman on the Water Planet. "Save me..." she pleads, "and I will lend you my power." Falchion, lonely bachelor in space that he is, can't say no to a pretty face, and flies off towards the Water Planet.

Divine Sealing is a basic vertically-scrolling shooter with adult content. The player controls the spaceship Divine, and shoots a variety of enemies. There are no bombs or powerups, but every 10,000 points the player is awarded with an extra life and a firepower upgrade. A boss appears at the end of each stage which must be destroyed. After defeating a boss, the player will meet up with one of four girls, who are then shown in various states of undress as Falchion "borrows their power".</desc>
    <rating>0.1</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>CYX</developer>
    <publisher>Studio Fazzy</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Divine Sealing (Japan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Divine Sealing (Japan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Divine Sealing (Japan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1050" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Doraemon - Yume Dorobou to 7 Nin no Gozans (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Doraemon - Yume Dorobou to 7 Nin no Gozans</name>
    <desc>A dream thief has come and stolen the dreams of all the children, using them to create his own personal paradise where nobody may trespass. The children can't continue on without their dreams, and someone need to save them...that someone being Doraemon, the mechanical blue cat from the future! Finding his friends have lost their color, Doraemon flies into the sky and chases after the dream thief into his world of dreams.

Doraemon: Yume Dorobo to 7-nin no Gozans ("Doraemon: The Dream Thief and the Seven Gozans") is an action platform game based on the popular children's cartoon Doraemon. Doraemon must make his way through each of the seven dreamscapes, stunning enemies with a water pistol, throwing them out of his way, and collecting coins and stars. He can run and jump, and even flail his arms to extend the reach of his jumps. </desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>G-Sat</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Doraemon - Yume Dorobou to 7 Nin no Gozans (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Doraemon - Yume Dorobou to 7 Nin no Gozans (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Doraemon - Yume Dorobou to 7 Nin no Gozans (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="177" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Double Dragon II - The Revenge (Japan) (En).zip</path>
    <name>Double Dragon II - The Revenge</name>
    <desc>The lovely Marian was rescued from the clutches of the Black Warriors gang by Billy &amp; Jimmy Lee in the first Double Dragon game, but now the gang has killed her in retaliation of their early defeat. The Dragons must now embark on a mission to avenge her death and defeat the Black Warriors for the second and final time.

The original arcade version of "Double Dragon II" was essentially an improved version of the first game. In addition to offering renewed audio and visuals, as well as new traps, moves and enemy characters, "Double Dragon II" discarded the conventional punch and kick buttons in favor of a direction-oriented attacking system similar to the original Technos beat-em-up Renegade.

The NES version offered new stages, new moves and illustrated cut-scenes, as well as a new final boss and a new ending. Unlike the first NES game, it offered 2-Player Co-Op gameplay with the option to turn off the friendly fire.

The Game Boy version of "Double Dragon II" is an English localization of a "Kunio-kun" game (the Japanese franchise which inspired "Renegade" and "River City Ransom" and has nothing to do with the arcade and NES versions. </desc>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>PAL Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Double Dragon II - The Revenge (Japan) (En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Double Dragon II - The Revenge (Japan) (En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Double Dragon II - The Revenge (Japan) (En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="124960" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dragon Ball - Final Bout (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Ball - Final Bout</name>
    <desc>Dragon Ball: Final Bout is a unlicensed port of the Sony Playstation game Dragon Ball Z: Ultimate Battle 22, made for the Sega Mega Drive and Super Nintendo by an unknown developer. The name and several of the splash screens are taken from the next Sony Playstation game Dragon Ball: Final Bout,(which is a 3D fighting game) but the sprites are ripped from Ultimate Battle 22.</desc>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <image>./mixart/Dragon Ball - Final Bout (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dragon Ball - Final Bout (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dragon Ball - Final Bout (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="21" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dragon Ball Z - Buyuu Retsuden (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Ball Z - Buyuu Retsuden</name>
    <desc>Dragon Ball Z: L'Appel Du Destin is a fighting game that maintains the dual screen mode previously seen in the DBZ Super Butouden series of the SNES, which allowed you to be far from the opponent yet still be able to see him by having the screen split between the two characters. This is important to note, as the most damaging attack of the game could be just executed from far away of your opponent, the energy fireball projectiles. These special attacks also need that you have your KI bar (which unlike energy one, is rechargeable) to a considerable level and the only way to block them is by means of a long button combination.

The constitution of the characters is based strictly on the Freezer and Cell sagas (Son Goku SSJ, Son Gohan SSJ2, Piccolo, Vegeta SSJ, Future Trunks SSJ, Krilin, Recoome, Ginyu, Freezer, A-18 and Perfect Cell), with special mention to Krilin, Ginyu and Recoome, who made here their first appearance in a fighting game. There are also 9 scenarios available, all of them corresponding to recognizable areas of the anime itself, some also appearing for 2 times but in different status (ie, "normal" Namek and Namek "in flames"). </desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bandai</developer>
    <publisher>Bandai</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dragon Ball Z - Buyuu Retsuden (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dragon Ball Z - Buyuu Retsuden (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dragon Ball Z - Buyuu Retsuden (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="21" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dragon Ball Z - L'Appel du Destin (France) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Ball Z - L'Appel du Destin</name>
    <desc>Dragon Ball Z: L'Appel Du Destin is a fighting game that maintains the dual screen mode previously seen in the DBZ Super Butouden series of the SNES, which allowed you to be far from the opponent yet still be able to see him by having the screen split between the two characters. This is important to note, as the most damaging attack of the game could be just executed from far away of your opponent, the energy fireball projectiles. These special attacks also need that you have your KI bar (which unlike energy one, is rechargeable) to a considerable level and the only way to block them is by means of a long button combination.

The constitution of the characters is based strictly on the Freezer and Cell sagas (Son Goku SSJ, Son Gohan SSJ2, Piccolo, Vegeta SSJ, Future Trunks SSJ, Krilin, Recoome, Ginyu, Freezer, A-18 and Perfect Cell), with special mention to Krilin, Ginyu and Recoome, who made here their first appearance in a fighting game. There are also 9 scenarios available, all of them corresponding to recognizable areas of the anime itself, some also appearing for 2 times but in different status (ie, "normal" Namek and Namek "in flames"). </desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bandai</developer>
    <publisher>Bandai</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dragon Ball Z - L'Appel du Destin (France) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dragon Ball Z - L'Appel du Destin (France) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dragon Ball Z - L'Appel du Destin (France) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18380" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu</name>
    <desc>"Dragon Slayer" tells the story of a young prince named Selios. One day his old teacher Raiyas sends him to a nearby cave to retrieve a magic weapon. When the prince returns, he finds the house attacked by monsters. Raiyas tells him to seek help in the castle of a baron, whose country has always been allies with theirs for a long time. However, the baron betrays Selios' trust and imprisons him. The young prince manages to escape, but without the possibility to return he has no choice but to wander through the land, trying to find trustworthy companions who would help him to save his country.

This is a traditional medieval-themed Japanese RPG with turn-based combat viewed from first-person perspective (like in  Dragon Warrior games). The enemies are semi-random: they do appear out of nowhere and attack suddenly, but they are visible on the screen, and if you flee from a battle they will still be there to pursue you.

The Genesis release has updated graphics; gameplay-wise it is identical to the SNES version.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19940916T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="641" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu II (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu II</name>
    <desc>Years have passed since prince Selios, the hero of the first game, defeated the demon god Agunija in the ultimate battle. Peace returned to the land of Iseruhasa. Selios married his sweetheart Dina, and they had a child, whom they gave the name Atlas. At the age of fifteen, Atlas was already a strong warrior, thanks to the lessons of his teacher Lowel. Everything seemed peaceful in the country, until two warriors spotted strange creatures near the capital city. Those were... men in space suits! Of course, the warriors could not have known this and believed them to be monsters. Do the mysterious strangers have peaceful intentions, or are they a new threat to the kingdom?

The second "Dragon Slayer" is very similar to the first game, graphically and gameplay-wise. The only major difference is the fact that the enemies are now completely visible on screen before battles, so that the player can avoid fighting them if he wants to. Otherwise, it is a traditional Japanese RPG with turn-based combat viewed from first-person perspective. The Genesis version has once again updated graphics. </desc>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <releasedate>19950120T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu II (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu II (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dragon Slayer - Eiyuu Densetsu II (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="23" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Duke Nukem 3D (Brazil).zip</path>
    <name>Duke Nukem 3D</name>
    <desc>Duke Nukem 3D is a port of the PC's Duke Nukem 3D, for the Mega Drive, created by SEGA's official Brazilian distributor Tec Toy and released exclusively in Brazil.

The gameplay is fundamentally the same and has the player blasting invading aliens from Duke's point of view. This version has nine levels based off the PC's Lunar Apocalypse episode, and a range of enemies and weapons from the original game. The difficulty has been raised significantly, and the framerate is noticeably reduced. The port also makes heavy use of scanlines and a smaller window size to reduce the overall render load.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tec Toy</developer>
    <publisher>3D Realms</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter-Shooter / 1st person-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Duke Nukem 3D (Brazil).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Duke Nukem 3D (Brazil).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Duke Nukem 3D (Brazil).mp4</video>
    <genreid>259</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="38958" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dyna Brothers (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dyna Brothers</name>
    <desc>Dyna Brothers is a real-time strategy title developed by CRI for the Sega Mega Drive. The player must guide an army of dinosaurs to victory against their opponents, who are aliens that have invaded Earth. The player's main base and source of life is "The Egg", from which other life forms are spawned. The enemy's base is represented by a UFO. Players have the choice of creating over five different types of dinosaurs: a stegosaurus, triceratops, tyrannosaurus rex, allosaurus, and lastly, an oviraptor. The player uses each dinosaur's unique ability to gather power points to spend in executing commands. This includes sending rain showers to grow vegetation, causing disasters, giving specific directions, and so on.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19920724T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>CRI</developer>
    <publisher>CRI</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dyna Brothers (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dyna Brothers (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dyna Brothers (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18381" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dyna Brothers 2 (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Dyna Brothers 2</name>
    <desc>Planet Jura is a green and beautiful place where dinosaurs have lived for longer than anyone can remember. One day, however, a giant black ship appears in the sky, and aliens come down to the surface and start attacking the dinosaurs. Feeling their suffering, the dinosaurs' creator, The Egg, awakens. To protect their race and their planet, the dinosaurs must fight the invading aliens, and force them to leave Planet Jura.

Dyna Brothers 2 is a real-time strategy game comparable to Populous. The player controls their small army of dinosaurs against the invading enemy alien army. There are six types of units, each of which has different skills and proficiencies. The player can order their dinosaurs to move or attack, and can also hatch new dinosaurs from The Egg. There are also environmental commands like earthquakes and lightning strikes.

The game features a practice mode, story mode, and free mode, as well as a 2-player versus mode where the second player takes the role of the alien invaders.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931203T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>CSK Research Institute Corp.</developer>
    <publisher>CRI</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dyna Brothers 2 (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dyna Brothers 2 (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dyna Brothers 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="157" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Dynamite Headdy (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Dynamite Headdy</name>
    <desc>Dynamite Headdy is a platformer... with a difference. You control a little character whose main attack comes from his disembodied head. Yes, years before Rayman appeared, we already had a hero who used detachable appendages to attack his enemies.

Rather than the traditional power-ups, Dynamite Headdy enables you to swap your head for different kinds – such as heads that heal you or heads that stick on to walls. You use your head in order to climb up on platforms as well, as you can grab hold of things with it, and on certain stages of the Mega Drive/Genesis version it is used to turn the game into a side-scrolling shooter, as you gain a propeller, jet, or bird head. Basically, Dynamite Headdy is just a traditional platformer at heart.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Dynamite Headdy (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Dynamite Headdy (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Dynamite Headdy (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="98" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Eliminate Down (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Eliminate Down</name>
    <desc>Eliminate Down is a horizontally-scrolling shooter similar in style to Thunder Force. The player has several weapons that can be freely switched (forward shot, back shot, and missile), and can also change the speed of the ship. Enemies come from all directions, and certain waves will drop powerups, including shields and weapon upgrades. The player needs to collect five upgrades in order to improve their weaponry, but the upgrade affects all three weapons.

The game includes eight stages, most of which include both a midboss and a boss at the end, and three difficulty settings. There is also a minigame similar to Whack-a-Mole where there is a grid of ship icons, and the player must hit the rotating ships.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19930625T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Aprinet</developer>
    <publisher>Soft Vision</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Eliminate Down (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Eliminate Down (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Eliminate Down (Japan).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1059" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Fastest 1 (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Fastest 1</name>
    <desc>Fastest 1 is a Formula One racing game. The game doesn't have an official FIA license, but much like Human's Fire Pro Wrestling series, includes a number of recognizable fictionalized drivers, such as Ayrton Sesna and Satoru Inakajima. The game includes a world championship mode, where the player must start from the lowest rankings and win races to become the F1 world champion. There is also a battle mode where one or two players can race each other or against computer opponents, as well as a test run mode where the player can learn each course and try to set course records. There are a total of 16 different courses, which can be played in either dry, wet, or half-wet conditions, as well as a wide variety of vehicle settings that can be tweaked.</desc>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Human</developer>
    <publisher>Human</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Fastest 1 (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Fastest 1 (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Fastest 1 (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="38959" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Feng Kuang Tao Hua Yuan (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Feng Kuang Tao Hua Yuan</name>
    <desc>Feng Kuang Tao Hua Yuan (literally Crazy Utopia) is an unlicensed game developed by Creaton Softech Inc. for the Sega Mega Drive and released in some unknown year.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Creaton Softech</developer>
    <publisher>Creaton Softech</publisher>
    <image>./mixart/Feng Kuang Tao Hua Yuan (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Feng Kuang Tao Hua Yuan (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Feng Kuang Tao Hua Yuan (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="1061" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ferias Frustradas do Pica Pau (Brazil).zip</path>
    <name>Ferias Frustradas do Pica Pau</name>
    <desc>FÃ©rias Frustradas do Pica-Pau (roughly translated as Woody Woodpecker's Frustrated Vacations) is a platform game developed and published by Tectoy and released exclusively in Brazil for the Sega Mega Drive and Sega Master System. It stars cartoon character Woody Woodpecker on a quest to save his friends. 
 
FÃ©rias Frustradas do Pica-Pau is unusual in that it keeps a non-shaded cartoon style throughout the entire game.</desc>
    <rating>0.45</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tec Toy</developer>
    <publisher>Tec Toy</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Ferias Frustradas do Pica Pau (Brazil).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ferias Frustradas do Pica Pau (Brazil).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ferias Frustradas do Pica Pau (Brazil).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="630" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Fire Mustang (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Fire Mustang</name>
    <desc>Fire Mustang is a fast side-scrolling shooter set during World War II. The player controls a P-51D Mustang plane through different missions, with many enemies on the screen at the same time and a large aircraft as a boss at the end of every mission. The Mustang has an unlimited amount of bullets, but one hit is sufficient to lose a life. There are different power-ups to collect, providing additional fire power and new firing patterns. Regardless of the power-ups, the Mustang shoots forward and drops bombs to the ground at the same time, targeting ground troops. There is a limited amount of forgers, large blasts damaging many enemies at once.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19910531T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Fire Mustang (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Fire Mustang (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Fire Mustang (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1063" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Flash Point (Japan) (En) (Proto).zip</path>
    <name>Flash Point</name>
    <desc>Flash Point (ãƒ•ãƒ©ãƒƒã‚·ãƒ¥ãƒ ã‚¤ãƒ³ãƒˆ) is an arcade puzzle game by Sega that is based on Tetris. The player is given a pre-designed Tetris puzzle where the goal is to clear a set of specified, highlighted blocks off the screen. The game ends if the player's blocks reach the top of the screen, similar to traditional Tetris rules. 
 
It was later re-released in the Sega Ages 2500 Series Vol.28: Tetris Collection in its original form. Also included in this collection is a previously-unreleased Sega Mega Drive version of Flash Pointâ€”the ROM of which has since been ripped and circulates on the internet today. It is unknown whether Flash Point suffered a similar fate to Sega's Tetris.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Zemina</developer>
    <publisher>Zemina</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Flash Point (Japan) (En) (Proto).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Flash Point (Japan) (En) (Proto).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Flash Point (Japan) (En) (Proto).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1064" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./From TV Animation Slam Dunk - Kyougou Makkou Taiketsu! (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>From TV Animation Slam Dunk - Kyougou Makkou Taiketsu!</name>
    <desc>Hanamichi Sakuragi is your average high school delinquent; sporting a bright red pompadour and continually being shot down by every girl he approaches, he jumps at the chance to impress a cute girl named Haruko by joining his school's basketball team. While at first not knowing the difference between a slam dunk and a Sherman tank, he slowly becomes an important part of the Shohoku High School team, which fights against the odds on the road towards the regional championships.

Slam Dunk: Kyogo Makko Taiketsu! (Champion Front Showdown!) is a five-on-five basketball game based on the anime and manga created by Takehiko Inoue. Following the story, starting from the first exhibition matches, the player can take control of either a single player or the whole Shohoku team in an arcade-style basketball game. The game uses a side-view for the center court, and zooms in for a head-on view when near the basket. There is also an exhibition mode for up to five players, where six different school teams from the series are available for play. </desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Bandai</developer>
    <publisher>Bandai</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/From TV Animation Slam Dunk - Kyougou Makkou Taiketsu! (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/From TV Animation Slam Dunk - Kyougou Makkou Taiketsu! (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/From TV Animation Slam Dunk - Kyougou Makkou Taiketsu! (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1067" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Fushigi no Umi no Nadia (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Fushigi no Umi no Nadia</name>
    <desc>This is one of the several games based on the animé series The Secret of Blue Water. The series (and the game) are loosely based on the stories by the famous French science fiction author Jules Verne. The game is set in 1889, a time of great inventions and technology progress unseen before. You play as Jean, a young genius scientist. In Paris he meets Nadia, an African circus performer. Nadia wears a pendant that contains magical powers, and that is why the evil Gargoyle is after her - this pendant is just the item she needs to build the ultimate weapon, the Tower of Babel. Jean will do anything to protect Nadia, and hope that his love to her, his adventurer spirit, and the power of science will eventually defeat Gargoyle!

Unlike most Japanese adventures, "Fushigi no Umi no Nadia" is a top-down, third-person perspective game, in which you actually move your character around. Nadia and other friends join Jean in a RPG-like fashion (although there is no combat in the game, different characters have their own item-based abilities you should use at certain points). There are no real puzzles in the game, but you'll often have to use your inventory items to make the game progress.

Not to confuse with other Fushigi no Umi no Nadia games (for NES, Turbo CD, etc.)!</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Fushigi no Umi no Nadia (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Fushigi no Umi no Nadia (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Fushigi no Umi no Nadia (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="38962" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Game no Kanzume Otokuyou (Japan) (Sega Channel).zip</path>
    <name>Game no Kanzume Otokuyou</name>
    <desc>Game no Kanzume Otokuyou is a compilation of Sega Game Toshokan games released for the Sega Mega Drive, a "digest" version of the Mega-CD collections Game no Kanzume Vol.1 and Game no Kanzume Vol.2. It was released exclusively through the Japanese Sega Channel at some unknown time, and the current ROM we know of was presumably found on the disc containing a certain version of the Dreamcast Web Browser; this has yet to be confirmed (TODO). 
 
Games included : 
- 16t 
- Flicky 
- Putter Golf 
- Hyper Marbles 
- Shi no Meikyuu 
- Medal City 
- Paddle Fighter 
- Ikazuse! Koi no Doki Doki Penguin Land MD 
- Pyramid Magic 
- Robot Battler 
- Teddy Boy Blues 
- Aworg</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Compilation</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Game no Kanzume Otokuyou (Japan) (Sega Channel).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Game no Kanzume Otokuyou (Japan) (Sega Channel).png</marquee>
    <genreid>3840</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="198768" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Gensou Senki Kokou no Ryuu - Crying Dragon (Japan) (Proto).zip</path>
    <name>Gensou Senki Kokou no Ryuu - Crying Dragon</name>
    <desc>Gensou Senki Kokou no Ryuu: Crying Dragon is an unreleased action RPG originally announced by Sega as part of a line-up of early Sega Mega-CD games given to Famitsu and listed in the 28 June 1991 issue, on page 14. It was cancelled for unknown reasons. 
 
On November 20th, 2019, a very early prototype of the game was acquired by Andlabs and subsequently dumped. As a sign that the prototype is from very early in development, it is a Sega Mega Drive on a standard Sega development cartridge. 
 
The game itself is a side-scrolling action RPG. When you start the game, you'll be thrown into a town. You can move around and press Up to enter a building. Each building has a primiitve looking shop which after a brief period of time unceremoniously presents a menu where you can do shop-type things with.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <genre>Role playing games-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Gensou Senki Kokou no Ryuu - Crying Dragon (Japan) (Proto).png</image>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1070" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Gouketsuji Ichizoku (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Gouketsuji Ichizoku</name>
    <desc>Gouketsuji Ichizoku , called Power Instinct outside Japan, is a 1993 arcade fighting game by Atlus and the first in the long-running series of the same name. Atlus ported it to the Sega Mega Drive in 1994, releasing it exclusively in Japan. Plans were made to port the game to the US under the name Power Instinct, but were scrapped (however a US SNES version was released under this name).

The game is a conventional fighter. A, B, and C each perform a different variation of each character's base attack, with various combinations possible with the D-pad.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Atlus</developer>
    <publisher>Atlus</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Gouketsuji Ichizoku (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Gouketsuji Ichizoku (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Gouketsuji Ichizoku (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="78348" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Gunfight 3 in 1 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Gunfight 3 in 1</name>
    <desc>Developed and edited by Sega in 1994 for the Mega Drive, Gunfight 3 in 1 is a shooting game only compatible with the Justifier, Konami's optical gun. This cartridge is a compilation that includes 3 games: Mischievous Gopher, Terminator, Falling Star.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Gunfight 3 in 1 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Gunfight 3 in 1 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Gunfight 3 in 1 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>261</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1075" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Heavy Unit - Mega Drive Special (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Heavy Unit - Mega Drive Special</name>
    <desc>Heavy Unit is a typical side-scrolling shooter in which you have to fly through several levels filled with enemies, mid and end bosses. Apart from the usual power ups that increase your speed and weapons, there is also one that transforms your spaceship into a large robot that has a different weapon system.

This is the same game as Heavy Unit for Turbografx-16 but with improved graphics (more colours, bigger enemies) and sound. Levels layout is the same. </desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kaneko</developer>
    <publisher>Toho Company</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Heavy Unit - Mega Drive Special (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Heavy Unit - Mega Drive Special (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Heavy Unit - Mega Drive Special (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125064" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hercules 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Hercules 2</name>
    <desc>The game is composed of four stages based off of the original PlayStation game. All of the graphics try to copy the original game, though are downgraded with lots of detail missing such as the whole forest atmosphere of the first level. Also, a few enemies use sprites from either Aladdin for the SNES, or the Mega Drive pirate of the same game. 
 
The first three stages are platform based, while the final fourth stage is more like a shooter where you ride Pegasus. Each stage ends with a boss that must be defeated in order to advance.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>IGS</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Hercules 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Hercules 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18392" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Honoo no Toukyuuji - Dodge Danpei (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Honoo no Toukyuuji - Dodge Danpei</name>
    <desc>Danpei Ichigeki is a young boy who loves dodgeball. Danpei's father was a famous dodgeball player when he was still alive, and he joins the Dodgeball Club at his elementary school. However, these kids are very serious about their dodgeball, and the road ahead isn't going to be easy for Danpei.

Dodge Danpei is a team dodgeball game, one of several based on the anime and manga created by Tetsuhiro Koshita, which plays strikingly similar to the well-known Super Dodge Ball. Each team has four main players and three support players, and attempts to knock out the opposing team's main members by throwing the ball at them in various ways. Apart from normal throws, the player can also pass to teammates, and execute special power throws which are harder to dodge or catch.

The game includes several different game modes, including the main story mode which follows the story of the anime, as well as one- and two-player exhibition matches. There is also a "league" mode which allows for a tournament of up to six teams, as well as a training mode where the game teaches the basics of how to play the game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920710T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Dodgeball-Sports</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Honoo no Toukyuuji - Dodge Danpei (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Honoo no Toukyuuji - Dodge Danpei (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Honoo no Toukyuuji - Dodge Danpei (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="38977" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hybrid Front, The (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Hybrid Front, The</name>
    <desc>The Hybrid Front is a turn-based strategy video game, released in Japan (exclusively) for the Mega Drive. 
 
The introduction begins with someone logging into a computer. Then, it shows a revolution that occurred sometime in the 2080s leading into a series of wars and conflict that lead up to the video game's main setting of the 26th century. Since the second half of the 21st century, the depletion of fossil fuel resources have helped to deepen the conflict on Earth... 
During the 24th century, the Earth was bombarded from orbit with massive optical weapons called the Metal Hammer by an Italian consortium; major cities around the world were burned to toast. The resistance would eventually be put down by CoCoON (abbreviation for COoperation COmmunity of Orbital Negotiation). Not only they would gain the corporate hegemony of humanity, CoCoON would develop a reputation as a hostile group of corporate war hawks; constantly revolting against the peaceful coalition of the PETO (abbreviation for Pan Earth Treaty Organization). 
Let the fight begins ! 
</desc>
    <releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Hybrid Front, The (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Hybrid Front, The (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Hybrid Front, The (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18393" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hyokkori Hyoutan-jima - Daitouryou wo Mezase! (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Hyokkori Hyoutan-jima - Daitouryou wo Mezase!</name>
    <desc>Hyokkori Hyotanjima: Daitoryo o Mezase! ("Aim for the Presidency!") is a sugoroku-style board game for up to four players based on the popular NHK children's show Hyokkori Hyotanjima. Four characters from the show all decide they want to be the island's president, and so they set off to start campaigning.

The goal of each round is to collect the most points; points can be earned or lost based on the spaces the player lands on. The round ends when a player reaches the destination set at the start of the round, which gives a points bonus. The player with the most points after a set number of rounds is the winner. </desc>
    <releasedate>19920807T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>JSH</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Hyokkori Hyoutan-jima - Daitouryou wo Mezase! (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Hyokkori Hyoutan-jima - Daitouryou wo Mezase! (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Hyokkori Hyoutan-jima - Daitouryou wo Mezase! (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1081" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Hyper Marbles (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Hyper Marbles</name>
    <desc>In the future, even the simple kids game of marbles is high-tech and extreme. Hyper Marbles takes the basic concept of the classic kids game -- to knock the opponent's marbles out of the playfield -- and gives it a futuristic sci-fi twist. The player directs their robotic marble around the field, attempting to push their opponents into the deadly electrified walls lining the arena. Aiding in this is a jet booster, which can cause opponents to bounce quite far, but if overused will overheat and must cool down before being used again. There are ten different arenas, each with different hazards like oil slicks and moving barriers. There is a single player mode, where the goal is to destroy all enemies to move on, as well as a two-player versus mode where the goal is to destroy the other player.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Various</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Hyper Marbles (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Hyper Marbles (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Hyper Marbles (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1082" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ikasuze! Koi no Doki Doki Penguin Land MD (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Ikasuze! Koi no Doki Doki Penguin Land MD</name>
    <desc>Doki Doki Penguin Land MD is a 16-bit remake of the classic Master System puzzle game Penguin Land. The player controls a penguin who must get an egg from the top of each stage to the bottom, where his girlfriend is waiting for him. The player must break ice blocks to open a path, but if the egg falls too far, it will break. There are numerous hazards that the player must watch out for, including moving platforms, solid iron blocks, blocks that will break as soon as the egg touches them, moving spikes, and tubes through which only the penguin or the egg can pass.

The player can also find special items to help out; hearts will increase the bonus score, wings let the penguin jump higher, and iron eggs let the egg fall further without breaking. There are a total of 30 puzzles to solve, with a password given every five stages. The game also lets you pause the game to view the entire map, as well as set a waypoint to return to should the egg break. </desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Ikasuze! Koi no Doki Doki Penguin Land MD (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ikasuze! Koi no Doki Doki Penguin Land MD (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ikasuze! Koi no Doki Doki Penguin Land MD (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1095" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - 98-Shiki Kidou Seyo! (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - 98-Shiki Kidou Seyo!</name>
    <desc>Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor is the adaptation on Megadrive of the Japanese animated series of the same name and broadcast in France in the early 90s. In this futuristic universe, big machines like cranes have been replaced by giant robots. To ensure that these robots are not used for harmful purposes, Patlabor was created. You play as the two main heroes of the series, at the controls of their robots.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Ma-Ba</developer>
    <publisher>Ma-Ba</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - 98-Shiki Kidou Seyo! (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - 98-Shiki Kidou Seyo! (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Kidou Keisatsu Patlabor - 98-Shiki Kidou Seyo! (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125102" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./King of Fighters '99, The (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>King of Fighters '99, The</name>
    <desc>The King of Fighters '99 is an unlicensed fighting game published for the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis console by X Boy as a follow up to King of Fighters '98. 
A sequel, The King of Fighters 2000, was released the next year. 
 
The game consists of 3-on-3 matches as the previous version did. Each character has their own special moves and one super move. New backgrounds exist and a few of the ones used previously have been altered significantly. There are reused and new music tracks along with songs reused from other unlicensed Mega Drive games that use the same sound driver. 
The controls are the same as '98. The A button blocks, B &amp; C punch and kick respectively. A super move can be done whenever the MAX icon flashes below your lifebar or if "Maximu" is set on the options menu. Throws are not implimented. 
 
The endings are minimal, with a simple "Congratulation" screen with the character select portraits scrolling beneath it.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <genre>Fight-Fight / 2D</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/King of Fighters '99, The (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/King of Fighters '99, The (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/King of Fighters '99, The (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39002" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Kishi Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Kishi Densetsu</name>
    <desc>Kishi Densetsu (é¨Žå£«ä¼ èª¬) is a 1993 war simulation game for the Sega Mega Drive by Kodansha Research Institute released exclusively in Japan.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930730T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kodansha</developer>
    <publisher>Kodansha</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Kishi Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Kishi Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Kishi Densetsu (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="479" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Klax (Japan) (Namco).zip</path>
    <name>Klax</name>
    <desc>An action/puzzle game, the object is to catch assorted color falling tiles and create rows, columns, or diagonals of a single color. Each level requires a different pattern to be made, and the tiles fall faster, more at a time, and in an increasing number of colors as the game progresses.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19900907T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tengen</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Klax (Japan) (Namco).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Klax (Japan) (Namco).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Klax (Japan) (Namco).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="173" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Langrisser II</name>
    <desc>"Langrisser II" is a sequel to  Warsong (whose original title is Langrisser). The events of the game take place several years after those described in "Warsong". Gone is the benevolent kingdom of Baltia, and a new power has risen - the Rayguard Empire, led by Emperor Bernhart and his four generals. Recently, Bernhart ordered his army to attack the neighboring countries, obviously searching for something. This "something" might be none else but a legendary evil sword, that makes the one who wields undefeated. It is up to the noble knight Elwin and his friends to stop the Emperor!

"Langrisser II" is a strategy RPG. The army is divided into soldier units and generals, who fight alone and who are usually stronger than a whole unit. Before the scenario begins, you must hire soldiers, buy weapons and items, etc. During the battle, if you come into contact with an enemy unit, an automatic battle sequence occurs. You can also cast healing spells on your units or offensive spells to hurt the enemy.

The major difference between "Langrisser II" and its "remake",  Der Langrisser for SNES, is the absence of branching storyline in Genesis release.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19941226T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Masaya Games</developer>
    <publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Langrisser II (Japan) (Rev B) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1054" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ling Huan Daoshi - Super Magican (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Ling Huan Daoshi - Super Magican</name>
    <desc>Ling Huan Daoshi is an unlicensed Sega Mega Drive game developed by Gamtec and released in Taiwan. Its name is disputable - while the title screen and packaging use chinese lettering, it is subtitled with an English name of Super Magician. Furthermore the ROM header lists the game's name as Elf Wor, and it has also been referred to as Reigen Doushi and Revenge of Fu Manchu. 
 
The game is strikingly similar to Zombies Ate My Neighbors, though has a more eastern setting.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>GameTek</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Ling Huan Daoshi - Super Magican (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ling Huan Daoshi - Super Magican (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ling Huan Daoshi - Super Magican (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="150771" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Link Dragon (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Link Dragon</name>
    <desc>Link Dragon (Long) (é¾ ) is an unlicensed Blockade clone for the Sega Mega Drive by the Taiwanese companies Songtly and Jumbo Team released in 1993. The game is divided into several levels; after collecting a certain amount of pieces (fire?) a door opens (which you must go to without dying). Dying starts you at the beginning of the stage.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Jumbo Team</developer>
    <publisher>Jumbo Team</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Link Dragon (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Link Dragon (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Link Dragon (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="107183" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Lion King 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lion King 3</name>
    <desc>Lion King 3 is a platform game released for the Sega Mega Drive based, not the Disney film of the same name, but the original film itself, as a follow-up to The Lion King II. It was developed by an unknown company likely connected to Chuanpu &amp; Gamtec and published by X Boy. 
A second release does not credit X Boy but it is unknown if it was published by another company or by X Boy without their logo. 
 
In this game, players get the choice of playing as either Simba or Mufasa, although they play identically to one another, through several levels, each with a boss at the end, all while having to contend with various platforming hazards such as floating platforms, swings and all sorts of enemies that obstruct their path. 
Both lions possess the ability to attack with their claws using the B button and can fire a special attack, a energy wave that shoots straight forward, with the A button. Extra special attacks can be found throughout every level. 
 
Health can be restored in game by picking up hearts and lives can be gained by picking up a 1-up. Atop of this, a life is earnt by picking up 100 Sun Emblems with the counter resetting afterwards. Throughout each level, progress can be saved by leaping at an unlit torch, which will light and act as a Checkpoint. 
 
There is no story in-game and the ending screen is simply a shot of the player's lion gazing out across a lake as the word "FIN" appears overhead. 
 
Trivia 
Strangely enough, Simba's in-game sprite is coloured a pale pink. Atop of this, while his idle graphics are taken from The Lion King, every other sprite seems to be an original. 
On the same note, Mufasa' sprite is simply Adult Simba's from the same game. 
Even more so then with Mulan, this game takes almost every resource from other games, such as enemies from Donkey Kong Country and the background on the Stage Screen screen is from the Transylvania stage in QuackShot. 
Most bizarrely of all, this game contains many sound samples taken from games like The Lion King and Disney's Aladdin often distorted immensely and employed in appropriate places. For example, a bug will sound like a monkey and the sound effect played when you pause the game is a portion of Mufasa's sound bite from The Lion King, slowed down incredibly and cut off. It merely says: "Everything the".</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>X BOY</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Lion King 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Lion King 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Lion King 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="107182" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Lion King II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Lion King II</name>
    <desc>The Lion King II is an unlicensed platformer for the Sega Mega Drive. It is based on the 1994 film The Lion King (as opposed to its 1998 sequel which shares the Lion King II title). It was developed by Gamtec at an unknown date, and uses sound effects from other unlicensed Mega Drive games. For example, the sound for Simba slashing enemies is the select sound from Rockman X3, and the sound when picking up an item is from Squirrel King. 
 
There are two playable characters: Simba and Mufasa, the latter can be played by collecting a golden star. Simba can be reaccessed when touching an enemy, and torches act as checkpoints; the player's lion can activate them by jumping up when next to a torch.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>X BOY</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Lion King II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Lion King II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1103" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Lord Monarch - Tokoton Sentou Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Lord Monarch - Tokoton Sentou Densetsu</name>
    <desc>You are prince Alfred, the son of the great king of Monarch. Since you have been a rather fresh and lazy boy, the king decides to strengthen you by sending you to battle. You are now sixteen, and you must prove you are worthy of being the prince of Monarch!

This is a strategy war game. You command an army and can perform various actions, such as sending troops, fortifying your position, allying with another ruler, etc. There are time limits to your strategic operations during which you'll have to defeat the enemy. The Genesis version features animé-style graphics, slightly different interface, and an elaborated storyline that was absent in the original SNES version. </desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
    <publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Lord Monarch - Tokoton Sentou Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Lord Monarch - Tokoton Sentou Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Lord Monarch - Tokoton Sentou Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="656" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Madou Monogatari I (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Madou Monogatari I</name>
    <desc>In this game, you play a young apprentice sorceress named Arle. She studies at a magic school, and is about to take her most important examination: go to the Tower of Satan, defeat the enemies and overcome all the obstacles on the way using her magic power!

Mado Monogatari I is a puzzle/RPG mixture. Featuring characters and puzzles from Puyo Puyo games, it is set in a 3D dungeon which you explore from first-person perspective. Combat takes place on a platform, and is a mixture of turn-based and real time styles. Enemies attack you even if you wait, but you have time to perform your moves. You should hold down buttons and press direction arrows to execute various magic spells. </desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19960322T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Compile</developer>
    <publisher>Compile</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Madou Monogatari I (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Madou Monogatari I (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Madou Monogatari I (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125624" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Magic Bubble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Magic Bubble</name>
    <desc>Magic Bubble is an unlicensed 1993 puzzle game developed by C&amp;E for the Sega Mega Drive. It was the only game produced by C&amp;E (a Taiwanese company) where the packaging, instructions and in-game text is all in English. The game involves matching like-coloured bubbles which float to the top of the screen. 
 
In the 2000s, publishing rights to the game were purchased by Super Fighter Team, who also published a translation of another of C&amp;E's games, Beggar Prince.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>C&amp;E</developer>
    <publisher>C&amp;E</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Magic Bubble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Magic Bubble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Magic Bubble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="508" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Magical Hat no Buttobi Turbo! Daibouken (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Magical Hat no Buttobi Turbo! Daibouken</name>
    <desc>An ancient evil has resurfaced after being sealed underground for thousands of years. The peaceful island, Usonto, has been split into seven pieces, and it's up to our hero, Hat, and his friends to restore the island and defeat the evil king!

Based on the 1989 TV anime Magical Hat, produced by Studio Pierrot and based on the original manga by Yoji Katakura, Magical Hat no Buttobi Turbo! Daiboken (Magical Hat's Flying Turbo! Adventure) is an action platform game not unlike the Master System classic Psycho Fox. You play as the titular Hat, jumping on and punching enemies, grabbing items from statues, and fighting a boss at the end of each world. In each stage, you can find your robot-egg friend Robegg hidden somewhere, who will help you out by acting as a projectile and a shield.

There are a wide range of different power-up items that can be obtained in the game, which will do things like give you temporary invincibility, freeze all the enemies for a short time, give you an extra-high jump, or even call in air support from a helicopter. At the end of each stage, you can play a game of chance to win extra items and lives.

A heavily modified version of the game was released outside of Japan as DEcapAttack. The graphics, sound, story, and many of the stages were changed. </desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19901215T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Tokai Engineering</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Magical Hat no Buttobi Turbo! Daibouken (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Magical Hat no Buttobi Turbo! Daibouken (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Magical Hat no Buttobi Turbo! Daibouken (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1104" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Magical Taruruuto-kun (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Magical Taruruuto-kun</name>
    <desc>Based on a popular manga comedy published in Shonen Jump, Magical Taruruuto-kun is about a boy named Edojou Honmaru who is constantly being bullied at school until he calls the titular hero Taruruuto from another world to help him. It is a cutesy platform game that plays similarly to most other games of its genre. There are many hazards to jump over and end of level boss fights, Taruruuto can hit enemies with his wand or pick up items and throw them.</desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19920424T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Freak, Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Magical Taruruuto-kun (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Magical Taruruuto-kun (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Magical Taruruuto-kun (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="674" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mamono Hunter Youko - Dai 7 no Keishou (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Mamono Hunter Youko - Dai 7 no Keishou</name>
    <desc>From NCS (the makers of Assault Suit Leynos, Assault Suit Valken, Gynoug, and Shubibinman) comes Mamono Hunter Yoko: Dai 7 no Keisho (or Devil Hunter Yoko: The Seven Bells), one of the only games based on the anime/manga devil slayer of the same name. Devil Hunter Yoko is about Yoko Mano, who was a regular girl making her way through high school--until she learned that she is the 108th successor to a line of warriors charged with defending the earth against demons. 

Every woman born into the Mano family has taken up the role of the legendary Devil Hunters, warriors who battle demons and other forces of darkness who threaten Earth. The realm of the demons (which is parallel to our world) is in cross-dimensional alignment with our own, which could cause a portal to open, allowing the demons to cross over, and launch an all-out attack. The demons are trying to destroy Yoko before she can take her rightful place as the 108th generation Devil Hunter. She must stop the demons before they can perform the ritual that will mean the end of the human race.

Mamono Hunter Yoko: Dai 7 no Keisho is a side scrolling action/platformer game along the lines of Valis. You control Yoko who is equipped with a sword, which you use to slash your enemies. Also if you hold the attack button you can create a shield which will block weak attacks. The shield can also then be thrown to attack enemies. You play through various different worlds, such as a plant type stage, a water stage, a cave stage, a snow stage, etc. </desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19910322T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>NCsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Mamono Hunter Youko - Dai 7 no Keishou (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Mamono Hunter Youko - Dai 7 no Keishou (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Mamono Hunter Youko - Dai 7 no Keishou (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="428" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Marble Madness (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Marble Madness</name>
    <desc>A port of the arcade game. The idea is deceptively simple: Guide a marble down a path without hitting any obstacles or straying off the course. The game is viewed from an isometric perspective, which makes it harder to stay focused on the direction the ball is to follow. There are tight corridors to follow and enemies to avoid. There is a 2-player mode in which players must race to the finish; otherwise you're racing against the clock.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19930813T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Atari</developer>
    <publisher>Atari</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Marble Madness (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Marble Madness (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Marble Madness (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="697" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Master of Weapon (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Master of Weapon</name>
    <desc>The "7-Day War" -- seven days of nuclear winter -- have caused massive ecological shifts on Earth. The ground splits open, the oceans boil, and all living things on the planet begin to change...including humanity. Scientists create a computer to leave a seed and restore humanity, a computer known simply as "N", which is part of the top-secret Project Yukiwo. What is Project Yukiwo? None who know remain...

Master of Weapon is a vertically-scrolling shooter based on the 1990 Taito arcade game. The player controls the fighter ship "N", shooting various biological enemies. Powerups are sparse, with only a handful of upgrades available from item pods. The player can fire in the air, as well as towards the ground to hit land-based enemies. There is also a special weapon which can be changed with powerups, but also takes time to recharge back to full stock. There are a total of nine "acts", and three difficulty settings.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910927T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Master of Weapon (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Master of Weapon (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Master of Weapon (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1106" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Maten no Soumetsu (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Maten no Soumetsu</name>
    <desc>Maten no Sometsu tells the story of a young boy (you can name him as you like) who was found in the forest by a warrior named Zafan. Zafan takes the boy into his home, where he grows up, unaware of this story. When he reaches the age of sixteen, Zafan dies, attacked by monsters. He sends his adoptive son to visit the king of the country, to follow the way of the warrior - and perhaps to discover his true origins...

This is a traditional Japanese RPG set in a medieval environment, with randomly appearing enemies whom you fight in turn-based style, viewing the battle field from first-person perspective. During your journey through the country you'll meet other characters who will join your party. There is a night/day cycle in the game.

Not to be confused with the post-apocalyptic RPG Maten Densetsu for SNES. </desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kodansha</developer>
    <publisher>Kodansha</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Maten no Soumetsu (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Maten no Soumetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Maten no Soumetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18407" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./MegaMind (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>MegaMind</name>
    <desc>MegaMind is a computer version of the classic code-breaking board game Mastermind for one player. The player must guess a four-digit sequence of pieces within a set number of turns; the only feedback given is an indication of how many correct pieces are present and how many correct pieces are both present and in the correct place. There are four difficulty levels, with higher difficulties increasing the number of pieces to choose from as well as allowing the computer to outright lie once during the game. There are four different themed sets of pieces to play with.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/MegaMind (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/MegaMind (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/MegaMind (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1113" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./MegaPanel (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>MegaPanel</name>
    <desc>Megapanel is a tile-based puzzle game that plays like a mixture of Tetris Attack and a traditional sliding tile puzzle. Blocks rise from the bottom of a well, and the player must slide them around in order to create a row or column of three same-color blocks. This causes the group to clear, and potentially create chains from the blocks above falling. As the game continues, the number of blocks that must be cleared to continue as well as the speed at which the stack rises will both increase.

The game includes three modes. First is training mode which explains the basics of the game. In this mode, a certain number of blocks must be cleared to complete the stage. Second is a "pin-up" mode for one player, where clearing blocks reveals parts of an image of a cute anime girl, the goal being to uncover the entire picture. Last is a two-player versus mode, where players compete to clear their blocks the fastest, and can send garbage blocks to their opponent and fill up their field. The game includes two difficulty settings, two versus modes, a sound test, and a unique mode that displays the entire game in sepia tone.</desc>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Namco</developer>
    <publisher>Namco</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/MegaPanel (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/MegaPanel (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/MegaPanel (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39014" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Meng Huan Shui Guo Pan - 777 Casino (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Meng Huan Shui Guo Pan - 777 Casino</name>
    <desc>Meng Huan Shui Guo Pan: 777 Casino is a casino style game in the style of Pachinko Kuunyan: you play as a boy or girl walking in a city filled with casinos. To play a game, you must pass behind the building and talk to the girl in disguise in rabbit who will give you chips to play. The game contains blackjack and slot machines.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>City Man Technology</publisher>
    <genre>Casino</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Meng Huan Shui Guo Pan - 777 Casino (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Meng Huan Shui Guo Pan - 777 Casino (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Meng Huan Shui Guo Pan - 777 Casino (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>3584</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="739" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Metal Fangs (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Metal Fangs</name>
    <desc>Metal Fangs is a unique futuristic battle driving game, where the player controls a team of racers and must attempt to destroy the competing team. Each "race" is made up of two heats of two parts each, and hits or kills on the other team earns points. During each heat, each team takes one turn attacking (four vehicles on the course) and one turn defending (three vehicles on the course). The team with the most points at the end of the last heat wins a reward and moves on to the next match.

However, your team won't get very far with just its basic equipment. After choosing your team's colors and members, you must then purchase upgrades for each person: engines, fuel, AI, armor, and of course weapons. During the game, you can switch freely between each member of your team. Your vehicle automatically moves forward around the track, but you can turn, throttle, and brake in order to move closer to or escape from the other team.

After each successful match there is a game of chance where winnings can be increased. There is also a two-player simultaneous battle mode.</desc>
    <releasedate>19931217T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Victor Interactive</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Race, Driving</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Metal Fangs (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Metal Fangs (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Metal Fangs (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1537</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="155441" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Fighting Edition (Russia) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Fighting Edition</name>
    <desc>Fighting Edition follows the same rules and format of most 2D fighting games released at the time: the player's objective is to defeat their opponent in a best two-out-of-three match using their character's standard and special moves. The player has four basic attack buttons (two punch buttons and two weapon buttons) and a set of command-based special moves unique to each character. The player can grab and throw their opponent like other fighting games, but if two characters attempt to do this at the same time, they will wrestle each other until one overpowers the other. Below each character's vitality gauge is a power gauge that automatically fills up and resets during battle. If the player performs a special move at the exact moment the gauge is filled, their power level will increase by one level, allowing the player to perform stronger attacks. If the player manages to increase their power level a third time, the gauge will be temporarily replaced by a thunderbolt symbol, allowing the player to perform a super move during this period. 
 
There are three game modes in Fighting Edition: a Story Mode where the player fights against the computer in a series of story-based matches; a Fighting Mode, where the player against another player or the computer (or have two computer opponents fight each other); and a Trial Mode where a single player must defeat as many opponents as possible without losing.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <genre>Fight-Fight / 2D</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Fighting Edition (Russia) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Fighting Edition (Russia) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125675" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./MK5 - Mortal Kombat Mythologies - Sub-Zero (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>MK5 - Mortal Kombat Mythologies - Sub-Zero</name>
    <desc>MK5 - Mortal Combat - Sub Zero is a pirated port of Mortal Kombat Mythologies: Sub-Zero for PlayStation and Nintendo 64. 
 
This game uses the system of Mortal Kombat Mythologies in that it's a cross between fighting and side-scrolling. The controls are somewhat awkward; during fights, Sub-Zero won't automatically turn around when behind an opponent, forcing the player to use the A button to turn around. The fighting engine isn't taken from the official Mortal Kombat games and instead uses an engine similar to one used in some other pirated Mega Drive fighting games. All of the opponents in this game are clones of major Mortal Kombat characters. There are four levels, each with a different set of clones to fight.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <genre>Platform-Plateform / Fighter Scrolling-Fight</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/MK5 - Mortal Kombat Mythologies - Sub-Zero (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/MK5 - Mortal Kombat Mythologies - Sub-Zero (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/MK5 - Mortal Kombat Mythologies - Sub-Zero (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="139" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Monster World IV (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Monster World IV</name>
    <desc>This is a sequel to Wonder Boy 5: Monster World 3. You control Asha, the green-haired girlfriend of Shion, the hero of the previous game. One day, Asha was standing on a cliff near her home village, and suddenly heard a mysterious voice calling for help. She decided to leave the village and to embark on an adventure to discover the identity of this mysterious person.

Monster World 4 is essentially a platform game, with slight RPG/adventure elements (puzzles, treasure, equipment, etc.) Asha can jump, run, attack or defend (by pressing the "down" button). She can also use items and equip weapons and armor, talk to people, and open treasure chests. Later in the game, she will also be able to use magic, and a little blue pet animal will assist and help her on her journey. The combat system is very similar to the classical Zelda style. Health and mana points are measured in little hearts, and the more you progress in the game, the more hit points you gain.

The game was released only in Japan. It is sometimes erroneously called "Wonder Boy 6".</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Westone</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Monster World IV (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Monster World IV (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Monster World IV (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1078" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Mulan (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Mulan</name>
    <desc>Mulan is an unlicensed action game by some unknown developer for the Sega Mega Drive made some unknown year. It is based on either the Chinese legend of Hua Mulan or the 1998 Disney film of the same name - which it steals art from, giving us a potential earliest release date. Some of its music is stolen from another unlicensed game, Chuanpu's 1996 Ya Se Chuan Shuo; whether or not the rest is also stolen has yet to be determined. 
 
Interestingly enough, the game has a story screen... in Chinese, English, Spanish, Portugese, and Arabic. The stories appear to be identical: during the Tang Dynasty, the Hun warlord Tan-Yu led his soldiers to seize the dynasty, and Tang conscripts all men to fight the oncoming forces. Hua Mulan, not wanting to see her old father fight, goes in to fight for him. 
 
The game is a typical platformer. B attacks and C jumps.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Mulan (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Mulan (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Mulan (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="59387" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Nekketsu Koukou Dodgeball-bu - Soccer Hen MD (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Nekketsu Koukou Dodgeball-bu - Soccer Hen MD</name>
    <desc>Nekketsu FC is referred to as a weak team, but now we were finally supposed to play the national tournament. To celebrate the national competition, the team went to eat sushi. However, a series of unfortunate incidents began to happen. Wow, who would have thought the whole team would come down with food poisoning from eating sushi!? 
 
At this rate it looked like we would have to give up our dream of entering the nationals, but just then our coach Misako had a bright idea! 
 
Of all our sport clubs, dodge ball seems to be the strongest, so why don't we ask them to help us out? The dodge ball team is led by Kunio, and let's hope he lives up to the expectations of Misako!</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
    <publisher>PALSOFT</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Soccer-Sports</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Nekketsu Koukou Dodgeball-bu - Soccer Hen MD (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Nekketsu Koukou Dodgeball-bu - Soccer Hen MD (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Nekketsu Koukou Dodgeball-bu - Soccer Hen MD (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="520" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NewZealand Story, The (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>NewZealand Story, The</name>
    <desc>One day, a kiwi tribe was having fun and games outside the zoo, only to be kidnapped by the evil-minded Leopard Seal, who plans to sell them at the black market. Fortunately, during the kidnapping process, Tiki, leader of the tribe, managed to escape the sack, and her job is to rescue Phee-Phee and the other kiwis scattered around New Zealand, and are held in cages in various locations that include Auckland, Rotorua, Waitomo Caves, Strait Cook, and Mt. Cook. 

If Tiki doesn't rescue a kiwi in a limited amount of time, the devil will appear and try to kill her. When Tiki reaches the outskirts of each city, except Strait Cook, there is a boss waiting to meet Tiki, and kill her by using their own choice of weapons. Also making the rescue mission difficult are several nasties that attempt to throw their own weapons, like bombs and arrows, at her. To defeat these enemies, Tiki shoots at them using her crossbow and arrows. More often than not, when Tiki shoots at enemies, they will leave behind pieces of fruit that she can pick up for points. However, it is likely that Tiki may get other weapons or the letters E, X, T, E, N, and D. Collecting all these letters will result in an extra life, and as for the weapons, they include laser shots, bombs, and fireballs. 

In some levels, a few areas are located further up than just left or right, and the only way that Tiki can go up is by snatching something off the enemy that gives her the ability to fly up. Other areas are underwater, and when Tiki goes underwater, her oxygen  meter decreases, so she has to rise up to the surface again to restore her oxygen levels. Apart from her own weapons, Tiki is able to squirt water at enemies if she gets to the top of the water.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19900303T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/NewZealand Story, The (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/NewZealand Story, The (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/NewZealand Story, The (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39839" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./NHK Taiga Drama - Taiheiki (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>NHK Taiga Drama - Taiheiki</name>
    <desc>NHK Taiga Drama: Taiheiki is a 1991 strategy game for the Sega Mega Drive by Sega tying into NHK's Taiga Drama adaptation of the Japanese epic Taiheiki which aired that year.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911213T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>NHK</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/NHK Taiga Drama - Taiheiki (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/NHK Taiga Drama - Taiheiki (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/NHK Taiga Drama - Taiheiki (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1134" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Nightmare Circus (Brazil).zip</path>
    <name>Nightmare Circus</name>
    <desc>Nightmare Circus is a beat'em-up mixed with elements from platform games and fighting games, made for Sega Genesis/Mega Drive.  The hero, Raven, is trying to put an end to the nightmarish circus that only appears on stormy nights.  He has to fight twisted and warped circus denizens through a variation of deadly circus levels.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Funcom</developer>
    <publisher>Tec Toy</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Nightmare Circus (Brazil).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Nightmare Circus (Brazil).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Nightmare Circus (Brazil).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39840" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ninja Burai Densetsu (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Ninja Burai Densetsu</name>
    <desc>Ninja Burai Densetsu  is a 1991 strategy game by Sega for the Sega Mega Drive released exclusively in Japan.

The game plays similarly to other strategy games such as SystemSoft's Daisenryaku games and Sega's own Shining games. You are in control of a team of ninjas fighting another team. C selects a ninja/confirms an action. B cancels an action, or if no action is in progress, selects the next ninja. A opens the battle menu, which allows you to end your turn. Battles are fully automatic. Unique to Ninja Burai Densetsu are side-scrolling special stages: should you move a ninja onto a special space, they will go into a town where they can get various helpful items from townsfolk.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911205T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Ninja Burai Densetsu (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ninja Burai Densetsu (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ninja Burai Densetsu (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="403" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ninja Gaiden (Japan) (En) (Proto).zip</path>
    <name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
    <desc>Sega even had a third project running, this time for the Mega Drive. Once again, the development was done by a third party. This time it seems to have been the mostly unknown developer called Opus, as in-game art and the sound engine used indicate. This game was never released, probably due to quality issues, but a beta copy was leaked and can be played on emulators nowadays. The game would have tried to build on the concept of the original arcade game, but feels to some degree more like a very bad approach to the Streets of Rage school of beat-em-ups. It is obvious that it either was in a rather early development stage, or Sega did right to pull the plug on this botched mess.

The game features a lot of cut scenes, all of them in the finest Engrish. The chapter titles are in Japanese, though. The story doesn't make any sense, at least not in its presented state. Later in the game, you meet people you should know but don't, and about halfway through the game you get to know that your goal from the beginning was to rescue Ryu's kidnapped lady friend.</desc>
    <releasedate>19921212T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Ninja Gaiden (Japan) (En) (Proto).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ninja Gaiden (Japan) (En) (Proto).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ninja Gaiden (Japan) (En) (Proto).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="120709" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Nobunaga no Yabou - Bushou Fuuunroku (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Nobunaga no Yabou - Bushou Fuuunroku</name>
    <desc>Nobunaga no Yabou: Bushou Fuuunroku (ä¿¡é•·ã ®é‡Žæœ› æ­¦å°†é¢¨é›²éŒ²) is a simulation game by Koei as part of a series of games based on the life of Nobunaga which itself is part of their Historical Simulation Series. It was first released in 1990 on the NEC PC-88 and then was ported to several other platforms released in Japan, including a port to the Sega Mega Drive in 1991 which was not released outside Japan.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Koei</developer>
    <publisher>Koei</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Nobunaga no Yabou - Bushou Fuuunroku (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Nobunaga no Yabou - Bushou Fuuunroku (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Nobunaga no Yabou - Bushou Fuuunroku (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="120710" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Nobunaga no Yabou - Haouden (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Nobunaga no Yabou - Haouden</name>
    <desc>Nobunaga no Yabou: Haouden ("Nobunaga's Ambition: Tale of the Conquerer") is a strategy-sim from Koei and the fifth in their flagship Nobunaga's Ambition series of Sengoku-era feudal sims. Once again, the player assumes one of a number of daimyos, including Oda Nobunaga himself, and tries to take over the rest of Japan. It was originally released in 1992 for the PC-9801 home computer and ported to various other computers and consoles of the period. 
 
Among the tweaks to the gameplay was the addition of castles, which are now the locations that players must conquer in order to take over new territory. Haouden was also the first game in the series to be given an expansion pack, though this pack would not be available to all versions of the game. 
 
The game was the first flagship Nobunaga's Ambition game to never receive a US localization. It sits between the fourth game, Nobunaga's Ambition: Lord of Darkness (Nobunaga no Yabou: Bushou Fuuunroku) from 1990, and the sixth game, Nobunaga no Yabou: Tenshouki from 1994.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940225T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Koei</developer>
    <publisher>Koei</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Nobunaga no Yabou - Haouden (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Nobunaga no Yabou - Haouden (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Nobunaga no Yabou - Haouden (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1138" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Osomatsu-kun Hachamecha Gekijou (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Osomatsu-kun Hachamecha Gekijou</name>
    <desc>One day, Osomatsu's five brothers went missing. The mischievous Iyami, of course, must be behind this! With great haste, Osomatsu grabs his slingshot, and sets out to rescue his brothers and give Iyami a taste of his own medicine.

Osomatsu-kun: Hachamecha Gekijo (Nonsense Theater) is a side-scrolling action platformer based on the manga and anime created by Fujio Akatsuka, which plays similarly to Alex Kidd. The player controls the titular Osomatsu through outlandishly Japanese environments, fighting bizarre enemies, collecting ribbons to buy various items from hidden shops, and searching for his missing brothers. Each stage is made up of multiple areas; falling into holes in the ground leads to underground passages, and jumping onto flying shells leads up into the clouds. A boss waits at the end of each stage, usually just Iyami in some sort of strange disguise. </desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Osomatsu-kun Hachamecha Gekijou (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Osomatsu-kun Hachamecha Gekijou (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Osomatsu-kun Hachamecha Gekijou (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1141" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Paddle Fighter (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Paddle Fighter</name>
    <desc>Paddle Fighter is a digital version of the popular game of air hockey. Two players each control a round paddle, and must attempt to hit a puck into the opposing player's goal, with the winner being the first to seven goals. Each player has a number of special moves available to them, which include defensive moves like blocking the goal for a short period of time, as well as offensive moves like splitting the puck into five "phantom pucks" which can distract the opposing player. There is a single-player mode where a series of increasingly difficult opponents must be defeated, as well as a two-player mode where any of the eight different characters can be played as.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Sports</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Paddle Fighter (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Paddle Fighter (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Paddle Fighter (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1536</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1142" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Panorama Cotton (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Panorama Cotton</name>
    <desc>The fairy kingdom has long been threatened by the dark witch Wool, the leader of the Dark Undulation. The queen Velvet sent the cute little fairy Silk to seek aid by the red-haired witch Cotton, the only one who could defeat Wool. Cotton agrees under one condition: she will receive some willows as a reward, since willows are her favorite food. Finally, after defeating Wool, Cotton realized that someone poisoned the promised willows, and swears revenge. Accompanied by Silk, she begins to chase the mysterious enemy.

"Panorama Cotton" is a pseudo-3D scrolling shooter reminiscent of  Space Harrier, set in an animé-style fantasy world. Various levels scroll "into the screen", vertically, horizontally, or diagonally. You can move Cotton over the screen, shooting at oncoming enemies and avoiding obstacles on her way. Cotton can upgrade her weapon to higher levels as you advance in the game, and can also cast magical spells by collecting special items.</desc>
    <rating>0.9</rating>
    <releasedate>19940812T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Success</developer>
    <publisher>Success</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Panorama Cotton (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Panorama Cotton (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Panorama Cotton (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1146" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pepenga Pengo (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Pepenga Pengo</name>
    <desc>The Sno-Bees are back! One day in Antarctica, an asteroid crashes into the crystal that protects the penguins, shattering it into many pieces and freeing the Sno-Bees who had been frozen in ice. In order to rescue his people, the blue penguin (along with a pink penguin in two-player mode) goes after the Sno-Bees and to recover the missing pieces of the crystal. The game takes the basic template of the 1982 original and expands on it, offering a greater variety of enemies, various environmental hazards, and power-ups, along with of course updated 16-bit graphics and sound. The goal is still to push blocks and crush enemies. Enemies now appear from generators, which must be destroyed to stop new enemies from appearing, and all enemies must then be eliminated to complete each stage.

In addition to the main story mode, the game also features a competitive battle mode for up to four players, as well as a conversion of the original arcade game. </desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19951222T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>JSH</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pepenga Pengo (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pepenga Pengo (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pepenga Pengo (Japan).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="190893" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star Fukkokuban (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star Fukkokuban</name>
    <desc>In 1994, Sega released a version for the Sega Mega Drive, Phantasy Star Fukkokuban. This version is merely the Master System version on a Mega Drive cartridge PCB with the appropriate connector pin to signal Master System mode changed accordingly (which is how passthrough devices like the Power Base Converter work). The situation behind this release is unknown; the most prominent rumor is that it was a contest giveaway.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star Fukkokuban (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star Fukkokuban (Japan).png</marquee>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="143221" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Amia's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Amia's Adventure</name>
    <desc>This game is one of the eight text adventures that chronicles the lives of characters before their story continues in Phantasy Star II. This particular game covers Anna Zirski, a counter-hunter. A counter-hunter hunts down and arrests hunters who have become criminals. Anna is tasked with capturing criminals holed up in a Motavian town. These criminals are accused of illegally accessing Mother Brain in order to disrupt the food production of that region. Anna must put a stop to these hackers.nnnnGameplay consists of exploring various locations, looking around them to find other characters to converse with in order to gain clues, and searching for items to take in order to use them to solve problems which helps further the plot. nnnnSome items that can be picked up can be used for weapons during combat. When in combat, the players weapon's attack power is multiplied by a random dice roll to figure out the strength of the attack. The same rule applies to the enemy combatant's attack. The goal of combat is to drain all the enemy's HP.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Amia's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Amia's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Amia's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1147" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Anne's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Anne's Adventure</name>
    <desc>This game is one of the eight text adventures that chronicles the lives of characters before their story continues in Phantasy Star II. This particular game covers Amy Sage, a doctor who is tasked with getting medicine to an elementary school that has been recently attacked by biomonsters. 

Gameplay consists of exploring various locations, looking around them to find other characters to converse with in order to gain clues, and searching for items to take in order to use them to solve problems which helps further the plot. 

Some items that can be picked up can be used for weapons during combat. When in combat, the players weapon's attack power is multiplied by a random dice roll to figure out the strength of the attack. The same rule applies to the enemy combatant's attack. The goal of combat is to drain all the enemy's HP. </desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Anne's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Anne's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Anne's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="143214" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Huey's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Huey's Adventure</name>
    <desc>The game takes place in the summer of AW 1284, shortly before the events of Phantasy Star II. 
 
Hugh Thompson (or Huey Reane)) is a scholar in biology at Motavia University. He's called in by the University president to investigate an incident involving an energy-sapping plant creature roaming the campus, feeding itself on electricity and steadily growing larger in the process. After the creature spreads itself through the college's reactor over to the main energy center, threatening to deprive the entire town of Kvarts of its electricity, Hugh sets out to try and stop it. This adventure is what eventually drives Hugh to adapt his knowledge of anatomy to combat biomonsters, in the aid of Rolf in Phantasy Star II.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Huey's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Huey's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Huey's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1148" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Kinds's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Kinds's Adventure</name>
    <desc>Phantasy Star II Text Adventures were a series of eight text adventure videogames available to users of Sega Meganet, a modem for the Sega Mega Drive in Japan, and later released as part of two compilations on the Sega Mega-CD. Each of the games takes place shortly before Phantasy Star II, documenting the backgrounds of its characters, and explaining what brings them to the town Paseo where they eventually team up to investigate the pervasive troubles of the Algol Solar System. 
 
Kinds's Adventure: Kind (Josh on the American and European versions), aged 18, is an aspiring engineer. He has always loved machines and knows perfectly how robots work. He built many small devices and knows how to hack computers. However, being head in the air, it often destroys things, but tries nevertheless to repair them. Finally, after being a "repairer" with little talent, he decided instead to put his talent to the destruction of machines, but for good reasons. He began to join a gang of rebels to destroy Mother Brain, the great electronic brain of the Algol solar system. And finally, he ends up teaming up with Rolf in Phantasy Star II.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Kinds's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Kinds's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Kinds's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1149" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Nei's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Nei's Adventure</name>
    <desc>Phantasy Star II Text Adventures were a series of eight text adventure videogames available to users of Sega Meganet, a modem for the Sega Mega Drive in Japan, and later released as part of two compilations on the Sega Mega-CD. Each of the games takes place shortly before Phantasy Star II, documenting the backgrounds of its characters, and explaining what brings them to the town Paseo where they eventually team up to investigate the pervasive troubles of the Algol Solar System. 
 
Nei's Adventure : This chapter features Nei - a Numan created through an experiment to breed humans with biomonsters. After her escape from Neifirst, she is rescued by Rolf and adopted as his little sister.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Nei's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Nei's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Nei's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1150" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Rudger's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Rudger's Adventure</name>
    <desc>Phantasy Star II Text Adventures were a series of eight text adventure videogames available to users of Sega Meganet, a modem for the Sega Mega Drive in Japan, and later released as part of two compilations on the Sega Mega-CD. Each of the games takes place shortly before Phantasy Star II, documenting the backgrounds of its characters, and explaining what brings them to the town Paseo where they eventually team up to investigate the pervasive troubles of the Algol Solar System. 
 
Rudger's Adventure : This chapter features Rudolf "Rudo" Steiner, who after the loss of his wife and child in a Biomonster attack, becomes a hunter dedicated to their extermination.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Rudger's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Rudger's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Rudger's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1151" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Shilka's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Shilka's Adventure</name>
    <desc>Phantasy Star II Text Adventures were a series of eight text adventure videogames available to users of Sega Meganet, a modem for the Sega Mega Drive in Japan, and later released as part of two compilations on the Sega Mega-CD. Each of the games takes place shortly before Phantasy Star II, documenting the backgrounds of its characters, and explaining what brings them to the town Paseo where they eventually team up to investigate the pervasive troubles of the Algol Solar System. 
 
Shilka's Adventure: Shilka or Shir on American and European versions. She is the only heiress of a rich family in Paseo, the capital of the planet Motavia. Instead of spending her time doing nothing and remedying the monotony of everyday life, she became an expert thief. She likes to take the air, the freshness of the night breeze and often rests on the roofs. It is called "Shir of the Wind". His adventure takes place in autumn of the interstellar year 1282, about two years before the events that take place in Phantasy Star II. She plans to steal a painting entitled "Opa-Opa", which is on display in an exhibition hotel.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Shilka's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Shilka's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Shilka's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1152" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Phantasy Star II - Yushis's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Phantasy Star II - Yushis's Adventure</name>
    <desc>Phantasy Star II Text Adventures were a series of eight text adventure videogames available to users of Sega Meganet, a modem for the Sega Mega Drive in Japan, and later released as part of two compilations on the Sega Mega-CD. Each of the games takes place shortly before Phantasy Star II, documenting the backgrounds of its characters, and explaining what brings them to the town Paseo where they eventually team up to investigate the pervasive troubles of the Algol Solar System.  
 
Yushis's Adventure: His name is Rolf on the American and European versions. He is a government's agent of Moltavia planet Capital, Paseo. He is the main character of Phantasy Star II. On mission, he rescues a young Newman: Nei.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Phantasy Star II - Yushis's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Phantasy Star II - Yushis's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Phantasy Star II - Yushis's Adventure (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125700" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pocket Monsters (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Pocket Monsters</name>
    <desc>Like the Famicom pirate, the player controls Pikachu through numerous sidescrolling levels. There are 5 levels in total, with a boss at the end of each, as well a mini-boss in the first level of the Mega Drive version. Pikachu can jump on enemies and use a special move which clears all of the enemies on the screen, although the latter can only be done when the charge meter is full (indicated by a power bar at the top of the screen of the SNES version, or a numeric counter in the Mega Drive version, which is full when it hits 20.) The player can start either 3 and 5 lives and continues each, and there's a difficulty setting in the options menu.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>DVS Electronic Co</developer>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pocket Monsters (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pocket Monsters (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125701" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pocket Monsters 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Pocket Monsters 2</name>
    <desc>Pocket Monster II is a platform game for the Sega Mega Drive and it's the direct sequel to Pocket Monster, both probably developed by ex-workers from Chuanpu Technology and perhaps published by X Boy. Unlike the first game, no SNES port has yet been discovered. 
 
This game shows a significant improvement over the original, as both the artwork and audio has been improved since the first game, though the former is still mostly stolen from other games and it still shows all the previous glitches, in addition to a new one. The music is mostly remade from the Japanese Pokémon TV series, with songs including the original Japanese opening theme (Stage 1 and Stage 4) and the ending theme of the pilot. (Boss theme.)</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>DVS Electronic Co</developer>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pocket Monsters 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pocket Monsters 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125756" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pokemon Stadium (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Pokemon Stadium</name>
    <desc>Pokemon Stadium is an unlicensed game loosely based on the Nintendo 64 game of the same name, made for the Sega Genesis &amp; SNES by an unknown developer. 
 
The game has two modes: Arcade and VS, with twelve playable Pokémon.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pokemon Stadium (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pokemon Stadium (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
  </game>
  <game id="1159" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pro Yakyuu Super League '91 (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Pro Yakyuu Super League '91</name>
    <desc>Pro Yakyuu Super League '91 is a baseball game developed by Sega that was released in 1991. The game was localized in the west almost a year later as Sports Talk Baseball, which featured an official MLBPA license. 
 
Instead of a running commentary, Super League '91 uses a constant soundtrack of Japanese drums during the game and a remix of the umpire voices to a techno tune at the main menu. There is no way to view any advanced statistics other than at the end of the game in the Japanese version (i.e., errors and hits). All the players names are written in hiragana, with English letters being used only to show field position and the status of the player.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Pro Yakyuu Super League '91 (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pro Yakyuu Super League '91 (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pro Yakyuu Super League '91 (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1160" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Psy-O-Blade (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Psy-O-Blade</name>
    <desc>In 21th century, there are three main powers on the Earth. The free world and the communist block carried over from the 20th century; the third power is the New Communist Federation. Since a program of denuclearizing was supported by all those powers, the New Communist Federation developed a devastating non-nuclear weapon: the satellite "Raiden". The two other powers competed with the New Communist Federation, developing their own killer satellites, and the danger of total annihilation became once again an issue. Seeing no future for the Earth, humans started to colonize other planets. In 22th century, they sent an experimental ship "Septemius 1" to a star six light years far away from the Solar System. The ship's main computer, "Racoon", sent a strange message before stopping any communication. You are Keith McDonnell, a seventeen-year-old crew member of the ship "Septemius 2" that was sent to investigate the strange disappearance. Will you be able to uncover the mystery?

This is a Japanese adventure in animé style. You interact with the game world by moving a cursor and clicking on objects to examine or use them, and people to talk to them, or by choosing options ("Move" and "Scroll") from a menu. There are no puzzles to solve; you advance in the game by talking to characters, visiting different locations, and examining and using objects.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>T&amp;E Soft</developer>
    <publisher>Sigma Enterprises</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Psy-O-Blade (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Psy-O-Blade (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Psy-O-Blade (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="210" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pulseman (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Pulseman</name>
    <desc>Pulseman is an electric hero who was created to fight cyber crime. Combat the galaxy gang throughout 7 stages with around 50 levels. Pulseman is best described as a fusion between the gameplay of Sonic the Hedgehog and Mega Man in ways of gameplay.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Game Freak</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pulseman (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pulseman (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pulseman (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1161" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Putter Golf (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Putter Golf</name>
    <desc>Putter Golf is a simple, fast-paced miniature golf game for one player. The player's only control over the ball is choosing the direction and power of the shot, and they must get the ball into the cup within par. Each of the 18 holes contains bizarre hazards like bumpers, lava pits, moving walls, and ice. For each stroke over par, the player loses one ball; if all balls are lost, the game is over. However, the player can regain balls by shooting under par.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19901103T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Sports / Golf-Sports</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Putter Golf (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Putter Golf (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Putter Golf (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1538</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="243" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Puyo Puyo (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Puyo Puyo</name>
    <desc>This is a falling pieces puzzle, Puyo Puyo originated on the MSX system and was later turned into an arcade hall version. Get four same-colored puyos touching each other to make them disappear. If more puyos of the same color are connected then they will disappear too. This game can be played simultaneously by two players for a competitive gameplay. Hinder your opponent by making multiple puyo combinations.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Compile</developer>
    <publisher>Compile</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Puyo Puyo (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Puyo Puyo (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Puyo Puyo (Japan).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18418" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Puzzle &amp; Action - Ichidanto-R (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Puzzle &amp; Action - Ichidanto-R</name>
    <desc>Ichidant-R is the second game in the Puzzle &amp; Action series, and the sequel to Tant-R. Twenty new minigames are present, including rocketship assembly, a batting contest, and hitting the brakes on a speeding car.

The game once again includes an arcade mode for one or two players. This time, the player is questing to rescue a kidnapped princess from an evil knight. There is also a quest mode which plays like a simple RPG, where battles are fought via minigames. Of course, the four-player competition and free modes also make a return, rounding out the package.</desc>
    <releasedate>19950113T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game-Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Puzzle &amp; Action - Ichidanto-R (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Puzzle &amp; Action - Ichidanto-R (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Puzzle &amp; Action - Ichidanto-R (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1162" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Puzzle &amp; Action - Tanto-R (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Puzzle &amp; Action - Tanto-R</name>
    <desc>Tant-R is the first entry in Sega's long-running Puzzle &amp; Action series of variety games. The game is a collection of small minigames for one to four players, such as navigating a maze, stopping a timer at the right time, or remembering a sequence of animal noises. There are a total of 20 different minigames.

The game includes the original arcade mode for one or two players, where the player must successfully complete minigames in order to track down a pair of fugitives in full prison garb. There is also a competition mode for 2-4 players where each player's wins are counted, as well as a free play mode where any of the games can be practiced. </desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Puzzle &amp; Action - Tanto-R (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Puzzle &amp; Action - Tanto-R (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Puzzle &amp; Action - Tanto-R (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1163" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pyramid Magic (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Pyramid Magic</name>
    <desc>Pyramid Magic is a platform puzzle game that casts the player as a young explorer seeking a treasure hidden deep within a pyramid. Each stage contains blocks, treasure boxes, and an exit which is blocked by a ghost. The explorer can kick and destroy the blocks as well as carry them, and can also move through small openings by carrying blocks into them. However, if he falls even one square downward, the block will crush him and the stage must be restarted. He must collect the contents of each box in order -- the last contains an item which will dispel the ghost -- and reach the exit without either trapping or crushing himself with the blocks.

After clearing each stage, a time bonus is awarded, and an extra life is earned for every 3000 points. Every five stages, the player receives a password with which to resume play, and is also allowed to skip two stages. There are a total of 35 puzzles to solve.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pyramid Magic (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pyramid Magic (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pyramid Magic (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1164" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pyramid Magic II (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Pyramid Magic II</name>
    <desc>Pyramid Magic II is a direct continuation of the first game. In the final room of the first title, the intrepid young explorer finds a stone tablet, which directs him to another part of the pyramid. He must now make his way back through the pyramid, once more in search of the treasure. The gameplay elements are identical to the first game: collect the keys and reach the exit of each room without crushing or trapping the explorer. The ability to skip two stages returns, and there are 35 new puzzles to solve.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pyramid Magic II (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pyramid Magic II (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pyramid Magic II (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1165" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pyramid Magic III (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Pyramid Magic III</name>
    <desc>Pyramid Magic III is the final title in the Pyramid Magic series of puzzle adventure games, and picks up right where the second game left off. Our hero is still inside of the same pyramid, but is finally nearing the treasure he seeks! Unfortunately, it would appear that the final step requires a large, heavy, fragile jug filled with some kind of liquid. He must now find a way to take this jug to where his treasure awaits.

While the basic concept remains the same, the game is made more difficult by the addition of the jug. The jug is fragile: if it is kicked or dropped any distance, it will break and the stage must be restarted. However, it is also dangerous: much like the stone blocks, if the explorer falls even one square while carrying it, he will be crushed by its weight. In each puzzle, the player must collect all of the keys to open the door, but he must also reach the door while carrying the jug with him in order to proceed. There are a total of 30 puzzles to solve, and once again the player is allowed to "pass" twice.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pyramid Magic III (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pyramid Magic III (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pyramid Magic III (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1166" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Pyramid Magic Special (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Pyramid Magic Special</name>
    <desc>Want more Pyramid Magic? Pyramid Magic Special eschews the rather thin story of the series and simply offers more puzzles to solve. Just like always, the player is cast as an explorer seeking a hidden treasure, who must make his way through each room, collecting all the keys, without either trapping or crushing himself in the process. This installment offers another 35 puzzles to solve. These new puzzles are exceptionally challenging, designed for those who found the other titles too easy, and the player is even given three passes instead of the usual two.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Pyramid Magic Special (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Pyramid Magic Special (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Pyramid Magic Special (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="497" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Rainbow Islands Extra (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Rainbow Islands Extra</name>
    <desc>Rainbow Islands Extra is a conversion of the classic Taito coin-op Rainbow Islands. Included on the cartridge are conversions of both the original game and the reworked "Extra Version", in which the stages and bosses have been rearranged to be more challenging. As with the other versions, the game is set in the titular Rainbow Islands, where the two boys Bub and Bob (no longer small dragons as in Bubble Bobble) must free the islands from the evil monsters who have overrun them, by using the magical power of rainbows! In addition to both the Original and Extra modes, the game also includes three difficulty levels.</desc>
    <releasedate>19901005T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Taito</developer>
    <publisher>Taito</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Rainbow Islands Extra (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Rainbow Islands Extra (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Rainbow Islands Extra (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39841" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ransei no Hasha (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Ransei no Hasha</name>
    <desc>Ransei no Hasha  is a 1991 strategy game by SystemSoft for the NEC PC-98 and the second game in their Tenka Touitsu series of strategy games, whose first entry was released in 1989. Asmik ported it to the Sega Mega Drive in 1991. No version has left Japan.</desc>
    <releasedate>19911129T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Asmik</developer>
    <publisher>Asmik</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Ransei no Hasha (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ransei no Hasha (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ransei no Hasha (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="633" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Rent a Hero (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Rent a Hero</name>
    <desc>Taro Yamada lives in the town of Corja in Japan with his mother, eccentric father and younger sister Alyssa; the family moved there after his father changed jobs. He received his Combat Armor by accident during their house-warming party, when he ordered pizza from 'Sensational Cafeteria' and instead received the suit. After realizing the suit gave him incredible strength and that he is required to pay for the armor, Taro decides to become Rent a Hero, a hero for hire, performing various heroic tasks and odd-jobs for the townspeople of Corja.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19910920T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Rent a Hero (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Rent a Hero (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Rent a Hero (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18421" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Riddle Wired (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Riddle Wired</name>
    <desc>A terrorist group has taken control of an armed satellite and is attacking all the nations of the Earth. Your mission: infiltrate and recapture the satellite...by answering trivia questions. Riddle Wired is a Japanese-style quiz game, and despite the scenario, the entirety of the game consists of answering general knowledge questions. The player will face a series of different opponents during the mission, and each one will ask the player a series of questions in a so-called "Quiz Battle". If the player answers correctly, the enemy will lose HP; if not, then the player will lose HP. If the enemy's HP is drained, the player moves on to the next stage, but if all HP is lost then the game is over. One or two players can play simultaneously.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910828T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Riddle Wired (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Riddle Wired (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1168" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Robot Battler (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Robot Battler</name>
    <desc>Robot Battler is an action game for the Sega Mega Drive, released exclusively in Japan via the Sega Game Toshokan service. Players build and equip robots to fight each other from a top-down perspective.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Robot Battler (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Robot Battler (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Robot Battler (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125703" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Rockman X3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Rockman X3</name>
    <desc>Rockman X3 is a pirated port of the game of the same name, made for the Mega Drive by an unknown company.  There are two versions of this of this on the internet with slight differences between them, mostly due to stage music.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Rockman X3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Rockman X3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Rockman X3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125210" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Samurai Spirits II (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Samurai Spirits II</name>
    <desc>Samurai Spirits II is a pirate for the Sega Genesis, made by an unknown company in 1998. It is partially based on Samurai Shodown 2: Haohmaru Jigouku Hen for the Neo Geo, with the music being remade from that game. The character select and in-game portraits are taken from the game as well, except for Heishiro, whose portrait is from the Soul Edge Genesis pirate. 
 
A total of eight characters are playable: Haohmaru, Nicotine, Genjuro, Hanzo, Ukyo, Jubei, Cham-Cham as well as Heishiro from Soul Edge, who is referred as "Hei" in-game.</desc>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Samurai Spirits II (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Samurai Spirits II (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Samurai Spirits II (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125792" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./San Guo Yan Yi - Huo Shao Chi Bi (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>San Guo Yan Yi - Huo Shao Chi Bi</name>
    <desc>San Guo Yan Yi: Huo Shao Chi Bi, also known as The Battle of Red Cliffs, is an unlicensed beat-'em-up game. The game is an unofficial port of the Sega Saturn title Tenchi wo Kurau II: Sekiheki no Tatakai.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <image>./mixart/San Guo Yan Yi - Huo Shao Chi Bi (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/San Guo Yan Yi - Huo Shao Chi Bi (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/San Guo Yan Yi - Huo Shao Chi Bi (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39850" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sangokushi Retsuden - Ransei no Eiyuutachi (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Sangokushi Retsuden - Ransei no Eiyuutachi</name>
    <desc>Sangokushi Retsuden: Ransei no Eiyuutachi is a 1991 simulation game by Sega released in Japan â€” and China, where it was called San Guo Zhi Lie Zhuan: Luan Shi Qun Ying. Whether or not the game has any connections to Koei, who makes the most popular games based around China's Three Kingdoms time periods, is unknown.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910429T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <players>1-3</players>
    <image>./mixart/Sangokushi Retsuden - Ransei no Eiyuutachi (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Sangokushi Retsuden - Ransei no Eiyuutachi (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Sangokushi Retsuden - Ransei no Eiyuutachi (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125793" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sangokushi V (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Sangokushi V</name>
    <desc>San Guo Zhi V is a strategy game, without official Sega license. It is a direct portage of Sangokushi V.</desc>
    <releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SKOB</developer>
    <publisher>SKOB</publisher>
    <genre>Simulation</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Sangokushi V (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Sangokushi V (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Sangokushi V (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1024</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="151394" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shui Hu Zhuan (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Shui Hu Zhuan</name>
    <desc>It is a strategic RPG based on the events of the famous classic Chinese novel "Shuihuzhuan" ("Margin in the Water", also known as "Marsh Law Forces", "Marsh Tale", "Marsh Men" and "Mount Liang Marsh"), which tells the story of 108 heroes who fought against the corrupt regime of the Song Dynasty (12th century). You take control of a group led by Song Jiang, a famous thief and hero leader, who begins as the young Zhao He. His city was attacked by imperial soldiers and his long quest for freedom began with this battle...</desc>
    <releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chuanpu</developer>
    <publisher>Chuanpu</publisher>
    <image>./mixart/Shui Hu Zhuan (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Shui Hu Zhuan (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Shui Hu Zhuan (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="18432" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Shura no Mon (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Shura no Mon</name>
    <desc>Tsukumo Mutsu, a young student of Karate, has come to the city seeking the Jinmukan dojo, looking for a challenge to prove himself. He's gotten lost, but a young girl helps him out. She happens to be the granddaughter of the head of the dojo, and doesn't want him to get involved with the place, but Tsukumo insists on continuing regardless. He walks right in, and takes on the first guy in a karate gi he comes across...

Shura no Mon is a so-called "command action" game based on the manga by Masatoshi Kawahara. The player controls Tsukumo by selecting commands from a list, using different attacks and defensive maneuvers at the appropriate time, with the results shown via brief animated sequences. Between bouts, lightly-animated visual scenes progress the story. The plot closely follows the first arc from the manga, starting with Tsukumo's arrival at the legendary Jinmukan dojo.</desc>
    <releasedate>19920807T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Shura no Mon (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Shura no Mon (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Shura no Mon (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1177" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Slap Fight MD (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Slap Fight MD</name>
    <desc>At first glance, Slap Fight MD is a direct conversion of the 1986 arcade classic Slap Fight from Toaplan and Taito, featuring a faithful conversion of the original title with several difficulty settings, as well as both original and arranged soundtracks. However, also included on the cartridge is a completely new sequel with all-new stages, bosses, graphics, and music. The basic gameplay is identical: a vertically-scrolling shooter where power-ups cycle through a list to choose from, and it is possible to construct massively-wide ships with incredible firepower. Slap Fight MD also adds the ability to jettison your ship's power-ups causing a massive screen-filling explosion that can potentially save your life.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Toaplan</developer>
    <publisher>Toaplan</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Slap Fight MD (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Slap Fight MD (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Slap Fight MD (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="583" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Snow Bros. - Nick &amp; Tom (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Snow Bros. - Nick &amp; Tom</name>
    <desc>Nick and Tom are two Princes living the dream with two beautiful princesses. When suddenly the evil King Scorch freezes Prince Nick and Tom and kidnaps the Princesses. Now Nick and Tom find themselves with abilities dealing with snow and ice. These two Snow Brothers will need to hunt down the evil King Scorch and rescue the princesses.

Snow Bros. is a fixed-screen platform game where players must defeat all enemies on each level (screen), 50 altogether. The Snow Bros use  snow as their weapon, throwing it at the enemies to stun them. When lots of snow is thrown at an enemy, it becomes covered in a flurry and unable to move. These can be rolled into  giant snowballs and pushed or kicked into other enemies. If left alone, enemies will eventually  defrost and become angry at the player. The enemy filled snowballs are a much stronger weapon then the regular handful of snow and are the only effective weapon Nick and Tom have against the bosses.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Toaplan</developer>
    <publisher>Tengen</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Snow Bros. - Nick &amp; Tom (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Snow Bros. - Nick &amp; Tom (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Snow Bros. - Nick &amp; Tom (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1186" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sonic Crackers (Japan) (Proto) (1994-07-xx).zip</path>
    <name>Sonic Crackers</name>
    <desc>"Sonic Crackers, also called Sonic Studium, was a video game developer developed by the Sonic Team and published by Sega, a platform game from the Sonic series on Mega Drive1. Scene Sonic and his friend Miles "" Tails "" Prower, this prototype was the basis for Knuckles' Chaotix, released on 32X in 1995. "</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Sonic Crackers (Japan) (Proto) (1994-07-xx).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Sonic Crackers (Japan) (Proto) (1994-07-xx).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Sonic Crackers (Japan) (Proto) (1994-07-xx).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="291" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sonic Eraser (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Sonic Eraser</name>
    <desc>Sonic Eraser is a puzzle game very similar to Columns that features Sega mascot Sonic the Hedgehog. Pieces in different arrangements drop into a well; if two or more matching pieces touch, they disappear and the above pieces fall to take their place. There are four different single-player game modes:

1. Round: Each stage starts with pieces in the well already. There are several spinning green pieces, which must all be destroyed to finish the stage.

2. Normal: A standard endless mode in which the game speed continually rises as matches are made.

3. Doubt: No white-colored blocks will appear in the drop formations, but often a random block in the formation will change to a white block after it is placed.

4. Block: Similar to Normal mode, but blocks will not fall out of formation until a match is made, allowing for impressive clear combos.

These modes can be played either single player or two-player simultaneous on separate fields. There is also a versus mode for one or two players, in which creating a combo of three or more clears will attack the opposing player, which causes them to lose control of their pieces for a short time.</desc>
    <rating>0.15</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Sonic Eraser (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Sonic Eraser (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Sonic Eraser (Japan) (SegaNet) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="507" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Sorcerian (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Sorcerian</name>
    <desc>Sorcerian is the fifth game in the Dragon Slayer series. It is set in the fantasy land known as Pentawa, whose inhabitants are in constant need of protection from ferocious creatures roaming the wilderness. The king of Pentawa hires a party of adventurers, and their first assignment is to retrieve a precious sceptre from a dungeon, where it is guarded by the evil demonic lord Ouks.

The game is an RPG with an unusual side-scrolling perspective and action-based combat, somewhat of a cross between  Wizardry and platform games. Despite being a Japanese game, Sorcerian resembles Western RPGs of its time, focusing more on character development than story. In the beginning, the player creates a party of four characters, choosing between fighter, wizard, elf, and dwarf (races and classes are not distinguished). Beside the usual inns and shops, there are many things that can be done in the towns of the game, including complex development of magical spells (up to 120 spells of different disciplines), training to raise personal skills (strength, intelligence, etc.), enchanting weapons with elemental magic, as well as looking for part-time jobs.

The view switches to side-scrolling when the party ventures into a hostile area. Combat is performed in real time, with the player controlling the entire party at once. The lead character can be changed at any time, and battle actions will be carried out by whoever is in front. Melee attacks and magic spells are unleashed by pressing corresponding buttons. The characters can also jump and interact with objects by bumping into them. Dungeons are usually maze-like, and some contain simple puzzles such as finding and activating hidden switches to open doors.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19900224T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
    <publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Sorcerian (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Sorcerian (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Sorcerian (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125482" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Soul Blade (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Soul Blade</name>
    <desc>Soul Blade is an unlicensed Sega Mega Drive game featuring characters from Namco's Soul franchise (specifically Soul Edge/Soul Blade). Little is known about the origin of this game, though a similar game exists for the SNES and Game Boy Color. 
 
The game is a standard one-on-one fighter.</desc>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Soul Blade (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Soul Blade (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Soul Blade (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125483" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Soul Edge VS Samurai Spirits (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Soul Edge VS Samurai Spirits</name>
    <desc>Soul Edge VS Samurai Spirits is an unlicensed fighting game released on the Sega Mega Drive/Genesis as a follow up to both Soul Calibur and Samurai Spirits II. It which was presumably developed by the same company as they use the same exact fighting engine. The game features characters from the Samurai Shodown and Soul Blade series. The theme song of the game is lifted from the Mega Drive RPG Barver Battle Saga: Tai Kong Zhan Shi.</desc>
    <releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Fight</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Soul Edge VS Samurai Spirits (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Soul Edge VS Samurai Spirits (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Soul Edge VS Samurai Spirits (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1189" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Squirrel King (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Squirrel King</name>
    <desc>Squirrel King is an unlicensed platform game developed for the Sega Mega Drive. It was published and developed by Gamtec, and therefore its origin is Taiwan. 
 
Squirrel King is extremely similar to Capcom's Chip 'N Dale: Rescue Rangers and it sequel, Chip 'N Dale: Rescue Rangers 2 for the NES, to the point where the player actually plays as two characters named "Chip" and "Dale" (though they look slightly different to their Disney counterparts). C jumps, B picks up and throws crates, and A allows Chip or Dale to throw fireballs, assuming they have some in their inventory. 
 
Squirrel King is the basis for another unlicensed title, Super Mario World, also for the Mega Drive,but developed by Chuanpu and possibly published by Ming Super Chip Electronic.</desc>
    <rating>0.5</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>GameTek</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Squirrel King (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Squirrel King (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Squirrel King (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1190" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Star Cruiser (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Star Cruiser</name>
    <desc>Star Cruiser is a 1990 adventure game for the Sega Mega Drive by Arsys Software, published by NCS. It combines two prior games by Arsys, Star Cruiser and Star Cruiser II, both released on various Japanese home computers. No version has been released outside Japan.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Arsys</developer>
    <publisher>Masaya</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Star Cruiser (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Star Cruiser (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Star Cruiser (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1196" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Bubble Bobble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Super Bubble Bobble</name>
    <desc>Super Bubble Bobble® is a Sega Mega Drive game unlikely to be developed by Gamtec. As the name suggests, this is a pirate attempt to emulate the formula of Bubble Bobble Taito games. 
 
The game allows the user to play as Bub and Cororon, as well as anime characters Shin-Chan Pencil and Doraemon.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>GameTek</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Super Bubble Bobble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Super Bubble Bobble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Super Bubble Bobble (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18442" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Daisenryaku (Japan) (Rev A).zip</path>
    <name>Super Daisenryaku</name>
    <desc>Super Daisenryaku is one of the many titles in SystemSoft's long-running war strategy series. The game mechanics are based on Daisenryaku II, but many of the 35 included maps are unique to this release, including several based on Phantasy Star. There is no scenario mode, and any of the included maps can be played. Some maps are for two players, some for four, and any map can be played with any combination of human and computer players.

The game is played on a large map made up of hexagonal spaces, each of which is a specific type of terrain. Each player controls a number of units, which each take up one space on the grid. Different units have different strengths and weaknesses toward other units, which are also affected by the terrain. Each player controls a capital, and the goal is to capture the other players' capitals.</desc>
    <releasedate>19890429T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Systemsoft</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy-Simulation</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Super Daisenryaku (Japan) (Rev A).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Super Daisenryaku (Japan) (Rev A).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Super Daisenryaku (Japan) (Rev A).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125602" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Donkey Kong 99 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Super Donkey Kong 99</name>
    <desc>Super Donkey Kong 99, sometimes known as Super King Kong 99, is an unlicensed Sega Mega Drive game created by a currently unknown developer. It is an attempt to bring the likes of SNES game, Donkey Kong Country (Super Donkey Kong in Japan) to Sega's system, though is very different to any of the SNES games. 
Players control Donkey Kong through a variety of levels whose graphics are taken from Donkey Kong Country and Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!. There are also several enemies taken from Donkey Kong Country 2: Diddy's Kong Quest. A picks up barrels, B runs and C jumps, and a boss will appear every couple of levels. The final boss is unbeatable without using a cheat.</desc>
    <releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Platform-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Super Donkey Kong 99 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Super Donkey Kong 99 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="109052" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Mario 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario 2</name>
    <desc>Super Mario 2 1998 or Super 1998 Mario 2 is an unlicensed clone of the original Super Mario Bros. made by some unknown developers presumably in 1998. It was later hacked into another unlicensed game, Sonic Jam 6 released in 2000 by the same company, Gamtec.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Super Mario 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Super Mario 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="155461" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Mario World 64 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Super Mario World 64</name>
    <desc>Super Mario World 64 is a pirated port of the SNES Super Mario World, made for the Mega Drive/Genesis by an unknown developer, at an unknown date (but presumably some time after the original release of Super Mario 64, in 1996). Super Mario World 64 was probably created by the same people who created Super Donkey Kong 99.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <image>./mixart/Super Mario World 64 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Super Mario World 64 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Super Mario World 64 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="155445" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Super Tank War (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Super Tank War</name>
    <desc>Here is Super Tank War, a pretty rare unlicensed Mega Drive (or Genesis if you're American) game by Gamtec. It's pretty much a Battle City clone, which is not an entirely surprising thing for them to have made, considering the popularity of Battle City and its hacks in Taiwan and other Famiclone-heavy markets, not to mention the fact that Gamtec had already made such a clone for the NES, variously known as either "King Tank" or "Super City Tank"</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <image>./mixart/Super Tank War (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Super Tank War (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
  </game>
  <game id="1200" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Surging Aura (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Surging Aura</name>
    <desc>In "Surging Aura", you play the role of the young prince Muu, son of the king of the country Pasfelda. One day, during a major ceremony, the kingdom is attacked by an army of monsters. The royal wizard has no choice but to use cursed magic. As a result, the mighty demon Rufid appears and challenges the prince to battle. Defeated by the demon, the prince is saved by a mysterious force, and is teleported out of the town, to a remote village, where his adventure truly begins.

"Surging Aura" is Japanese RPG in animé style. Regular enemies are random, and the battles are fought from first person view. The combat is is a mixture between turn based and real time styles, like in contemporary  Final Fantasy games. Enemies will attack even if you don't perform any action during the battle. The game features full screen animé-style pictures as cut scenes</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Japan Media Programming Inc.</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Surging Aura (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Surging Aura (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Surging Aura (Japan).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="39842" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Taikou Risshiden (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Taikou Risshiden</name>
    <desc>Taikou Risshiden  is a simulation game by Koei in their Rékoeition series. It was first released in 1992 on various Japanese computers before being ported to a variety of platforms, including a 1993 port to the Sega Mega Drive that was not released outside Japan.</desc>
    <releasedate>19930528T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Koei</developer>
    <publisher>Koei</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Taikou Risshiden (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Taikou Risshiden (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Taikou Risshiden (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125800" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Taiwan Daheng (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Taiwan Daheng</name>
    <desc>Jeu de stratégie. Intégralement en chinois.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>C&amp;E</developer>
    <publisher>C&amp;E</publisher>
    <image>./mixart/Taiwan Daheng (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Taiwan Daheng (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Taiwan Daheng (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="1206" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Teddy Boy Blues (Japan) (SegaNet).zip</path>
    <name>Teddy Boy Blues</name>
    <desc>Teddy Boy Blues is an updated conversion of the 1985 Sega coin-op action platformer. While the basic premise is similar to the Master System version -- each stage contains a number of enemy generators, and enemies must be shot and collected before they take a portion of the time meter -- this version of the game has several differences. The graphics have been redrawn to take advantage of the more powerful hardware and the Yohko Ishino tie-in has been removed. There are also several new stages throughout the game, though many of the original game's stages are also present.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Teddy Boy Blues (Japan) (SegaNet).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Teddy Boy Blues (Japan) (SegaNet).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Teddy Boy Blues (Japan) (SegaNet).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="144005" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Legend Returns (Russia) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Legend Returns</name>
    <desc>We all love those shelled-up Pizza addicts... as do the Russians apparently. An all new and somewhat original Mega Drive title starring the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles has been in circulation recently, flooding the Russian after-market of 16-bit software. Luckily for gamers elsewhere around the world, the game's ROM file has been preserved and since shared online. 
 
As excited as we were reading about another 16-bit adventure for our anthropomorphic turtles, the reality of what we have here is somewhat disappointing, although interesting. Similar to the many other Russian releases on the Sega Mega Drive, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Legend Returns takes elements from other titles without permission - this time from Ubisoft's flash game to promote Smash Up, Double Damage. 
 
Making use of the assets taken from other sources, the Russians have created their very own Street of Rage clone (or should we say Hyperstone Heist clone), albeit a lacklustre attempt. Gameplay, the repeating scenery and poor enemy AI aside, during our initial play-through we encountered an unbeatable Mouser who began walking in a bizarre fashion, blocking any further progress. 
 
Regardless of how well this title handles and whether or not level two can be beaten, Mega Drive fans should check out this unofficial offering, whilst looking towards the many other original titles Russia has produced for the 16-bit system over the years.</desc>
    <releasedate>20130101T000000</releasedate>
    <genre>Beat'em Up-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Legend Returns (Russia) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Legend Returns (Russia) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - The Legend Returns (Russia) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>263</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125806" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tekken Special (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Tekken Special</name>
    <desc>Tekken 3 Special is a pirated fighting game based off Tekken 2, created for the Mega Drive by an unknown company. 
 
The graphics are taken from the original game and simplified, with the characters being original hand drawn 2D sprites made to roughly resemble a the 3D models used in the original arcade board. The backgrounds are simple and not animated, often being mirrored horizontally like many other pirates on the Mega Drive in order to conserve ROM space. Many of the backgrounds appear to utilize poorly digitized elements. The music appears to be original. The ending is a simple "Congratulations" screen. 
 
The title screen and character icons are taken from the original Tekken 2 and reduced in color. These seem to be the only elements lifted directly from the arcade source.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Tekken Special (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tekken Special (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tekken Special (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125807" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tenchi o Kurau III - Sangoku Gaiden (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Tenchi o Kurau III - Sangoku Gaiden</name>
    <desc>Also known as Tun Shi Tian Di 3: San Guo Wai Chuan or Chinese Fighter, is an unlicensed fighting game. Its origins are largely unknown.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <image>./mixart/Tenchi o Kurau III - Sangoku Gaiden (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tenchi o Kurau III - Sangoku Gaiden (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tenchi o Kurau III - Sangoku Gaiden (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="68" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tetris (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Tetris</name>
    <desc>Tetris is one of many conversions of the famous block-stacking game, this one is based on the 1988 coin-op version produced by Sega. The goal is to place pieces made up of four tiles in a ten-by-twenty well, organizing them into complete rows, which then disappear. As rows are cleared, the pace of the game increases and the background changes, and the game ends if the stack reaches the top of the well.

In addition to a standard endless mode for one or two players, the game also includes a "time trial" mode for one or two players, where the goal is to get as many points as possible in three minutes. There is also a "doubles" mode, where two players work together to fill lines in an extra-wide well, each controlling their own pieces simultaneously.

The game offers a number of standard options: setting the starting level, how much "garbage" is at the bottom of the well when the game starts, and whether the next piece is visible. There are also optional "item blocks," which are special flashing pieces that give an extra bonus if they are used to clear a line.</desc>
    <rating>0.65</rating>
    <releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Tetris (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tetris (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tetris (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="665" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Thunder Pro Wrestling Retsuden (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Thunder Pro Wrestling Retsuden</name>
    <desc>Thunder Pro Wrestling Retsuden is a spinoff of Human's popular Fire Pro Wrestling series, and the only title in the series to appear on the Mega Drive. Like the other Fire Pro games, it is an arcade-style wrestling game featuring a roster of fictional wrestlers. The game includes a standard World Championship mode where the player picks a wrestler and fights his way to win the title. There is also an "Exciting" mode in which one or two players can play an exhibition singles or tag match against the computer or each other, an Elimination mode where each player picks a team of five wrestlers, and a "Handicap" mode where one fighter must alone take on a tag team. </desc>
    <releasedate>19920327T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Human</developer>
    <publisher>Human</publisher>
    <genre>Sports-Action</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Thunder Pro Wrestling Retsuden (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Thunder Pro Wrestling Retsuden (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Thunder Pro Wrestling Retsuden (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1536</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="143831" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Thunderbolt II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Thunderbolt II</name>
    <desc>Thunderbolt II, which also refers to itself as Lei Dian Chuan Shuo II or just Lei Dian II  is an unlicensed vertical scrolling shoot-'em-up released for the Sega Mega Drive in 1995. There is not thought to have been a Thunderbolt I - more likely it is borrowing its name from Raiden II, a 1993 arcade shooter by Seibu Kaihatsu that is a sequel to Raiden. 
</desc>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <publisher>Ming Super Chip</publisher>
    <genre>Shooter</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Thunderbolt II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Thunderbolt II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Thunderbolt II (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="125820" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tiny Toon Adventures 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Tiny Toon Adventures 3</name>
    <desc>The game consists of five stages, each usually composed of four screens each and then a boss. Following with the story, you free different types of animals each stage, trapped in what appear to be either little cages or trash bins, jumping on the cages will release them and will destroy all enemies currently as well as adding to your score. In the game, the graphics in stages three and four are based off those from Super Mario World. Stage three appears to outright lift level graphics straight from the SNES game, while stage four uses what appear to be original graphics based on the Super Mario World style. Unlike stage three though, stage four also has enemy sprites that are based off of Super Mario World enemies, including Koopas and Chargin' Chuck, and pigs that fly with parachutes, much like Para-bombs.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>Gamtec</developer>
    <publisher>Gamtec</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Tiny Toon Adventures 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tiny Toon Adventures 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tiny Toon Adventures 3 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="155466" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tom Clown (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Tom Clown</name>
    <desc>Tom Clown is an unlicensed game for the Sega Mega Drive developed by AV artisan and published by Realtec in 1993. 
The game is a re-imagining of the Atari 2600 game Circus ? move the teeter-board back and forth to bounce the clowns upwards and pop balloons. Power-ups will pass by overhead and give the player extra chances or clear certain colored balloons. After clearing the stage, the player moves onto the next round.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>AV Artisan</developer>
    <publisher>Realtec</publisher>
    <image>./mixart/Tom Clown (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tom Clown (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tom Clown (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
  </game>
  <game id="64845" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Top Fighter 2000 MK VIII (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Top Fighter 2000 MK VIII</name>
    <desc>Top Fighter 2000 MK VIII is a fighting game created for the Mega Drive, presumably in the year 2000 by an unknown company. It features 8 characters from many different places and sources, including real-life personalities such as Michael Jordan and Muhammad Ali. 
 
This is a fighting game with 8 opponents and no repeats between them. Each character has their own special moves and one super move, along with 8 backgrounds that are not character specific. The backgrounds are cobbled together using elements of backgrounds found in several different games, including World Heroes, Street Fighter II, The King of Fighters '95, and Fatal Fury 2. The controls appear to be somewhat better than other Mega Drive pirated fighting games, such as Tekken 3 Special. However, the A button is unused, leaving B and C to be used for all attacks, similar to a NES fighting pirate. 
 
Each fight lasts until one fighter wins 1 or 3 rounds and each round can last for up to 30, 60 or 99 seconds, depending on the settings. The hit detection is poor, with many attacks that miss the opponent when they're supposed to hit them. The endings are minimal, with a portrait of your character on a simple "YOU ARE BEST. GAME OVER" (sic) screen.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <developer>X BOY</developer>
    <publisher>X BOY</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight-Fight / 2D</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Top Fighter 2000 MK VIII (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Top Fighter 2000 MK VIII (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Top Fighter 2000 MK VIII (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1212" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tougiou King Colossus (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Tougiou King Colossus</name>
    <desc>The story of "King Colossus" is simple: you are a young fighter who lives in a small house somewhere on a fantasy continent and who was raised by the local wise man. Now, when he became skilled at sword fighting, the wise man sends him to the dangerous South Cave, to defeat the monsters populating it. By visiting different places, the hero will battle even more fearsome monsters, until he finally challenges the ultimate evil.

"King Colossus" is a top-down adventure with action combat and light RPG elements. You fight monsters by equipping weapons and swinging them in real time. There is a variety of accessories and items to find in the game, as well as different obstacles to overcome in the dungeons. </desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19920626T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Tougiou King Colossus (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tougiou King Colossus (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tougiou King Colossus (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1215" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Tun Shi Tian Di III (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Tun Shi Tian Di III</name>
    <desc>The game's story is based on "Romance of the Three Kingdoms" and "Tenchi o Kurau series (But unrelated of story)". The game evidently is based on the same engine as that of Ya-se Chuan Shuo and Barver Battle Saga: Tai Kong Zhan Shi, with the exceptions of a different battle view.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>20030101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>SKOB</developer>
    <publisher>SKOB</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Tun Shi Tian Di III (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Tun Shi Tian Di III (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Tun Shi Tian Di III (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="553" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Twinkle Tale (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Twinkle Tale</name>
    <desc>An overhead scrolling fantasy shoot 'em up, Twinkle Tale casts the player in the role of the young witch Saria, in a quest to rid her magical floating island of the evil creatures that have invaded it.

The game is played from an overhead perspective, with Saria having complete freedom of movement in all directions and with the objective being to clear out all enemies in all 9 stages, looting whatever treasure you can find and defeating each stage's boss.

Saria's offensive weapons come pre-defined as three different spells, which you can freely switch to at any time and level-up by collecting power stars, as well as screen-clearing bombs.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19920724T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Zap</developer>
    <publisher>Wonder Amusement Studio</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Twinkle Tale (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Twinkle Tale (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Twinkle Tale (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1217" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Uchuu Senkan Gomora (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Uchuu Senkan Gomora</name>
    <desc>Atlantal, a peaceful planet, has been attacked by an invading alien fleet known only as The Aggressors, leaving the capital city Delila in ruins. In order to sop The Aggressors, the people of Atlantal send the most powerful fighter ship on the planet, the bio-ship Gomorrah.

Uchu Senkan Gomorrah (Space Battle Ship Gomorrah) is a horizontally-scrolling shooter based on the 1990 coin-op of the same title. The player controls the titular ship, Gomorrah, which can shoot both straight forward as in most shooting games, as well as freely in any direction via an aiming cursor, which is controlled independently of the ship itself. Additionally, there are several power-ups that can be found, including speed-ups, additional mounted guns, and the life-up, which will not only increase the ship's armor, but also cause it to grow in size as well.

The game features 9 stages, each with a boss at the end, as well as one or two-player simultaneous play. The game difficulty has been rebalanced from the arcade to compensate for the lack of a trackball to control the aiming cursor; the player must stop their ship in order to move the cursor. </desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Aisystem Tokyo</developer>
    <publisher>UPL</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Uchuu Senkan Gomora (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Uchuu Senkan Gomora (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Uchuu Senkan Gomora (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1218" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ultraman (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Ultraman</name>
    <desc>In the future, Earth must protect itself from alien invaders, a task handled by the Science Special Search Party. However, they are not alone in this endeavor. After crashing his ship on Earth while in pursuit of the evil alien Bemular, the super-being Ultraman is here to help whenever the attacking aliens prove too much for humanity alone to handle. Standing hundreds of feet tall with incredible strength and amazing abilities, he can only remain on Earth for a few minutes, and so must defeat his foes before his power drains completely.

Based on the popular television show from 1967, Ultraman directly follows the story of its source material. Cast in the role of the titular Ultraman, the player must defeat many of the same monsters that appeared in the original series. Taking the appearance of a 1-on-1 fighting game, Ultraman can punch, kick, and grapple his opponent, as well as use a variety of various special moves that must be charged. However, in order to actually defeat his opponent, Ultraman must deplete their continually-recharging life bar, and at that moment hit with his most powerful special attack: the Specium Beam. As the game continues, different enemies may even find ways to avoid this most formidable attack, and Ultraman must adapt... Each stage has a time limit of only three minutes, and there are three lives and no continues.</desc>
    <rating>0.4</rating>
    <releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>BEC</developer>
    <publisher>Human</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Fight</genre>
    <players>1-8</players>
    <image>./mixart/Ultraman (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ultraman (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ultraman (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1219" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Undead Line (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Undead Line</name>
    <desc>Undead Line is a top-down arcade shooter with scrolling screens, like Commando and other games. The player controls a character (from a selection of three on the MSX 2 version) that shoots projectiles at enemy monsters.

The six levels available are presented in a menu and can be selected and played in any order. There is a boss battle at the end of each one.

Chests with power-ups are scattered throughout the levels. They open when shot, and in the Genesis version it is possible to cycle through the available power-ups by keeping firing at them. The power-ups include armor and speed boosts, and several types of projectiles.</desc>
    <rating>0.7</rating>
    <releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>T&amp;E Soft</developer>
    <publisher>PALSOFT</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Undead Line (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Undead Line (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Undead Line (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1220" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Uzu Keobukseon (Korea).zip</path>
    <name>Uzu Keobukseon</name>
    <desc>Uzu Keobukseon is a 1992 shoot-'em-up by Samsung released exclusively in Korea for the Sega Mega Drive. It is the only first-party Mega Drive title produced by Samsung, who was Sega's hardware distributor and software translator in Korea.</desc>
    <rating>0.8</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Samsung</developer>
    <publisher>Samsung</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Uzu Keobukseon (Korea).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Uzu Keobukseon (Korea).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Uzu Keobukseon (Korea).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="625" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Verytex (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Verytex</name>
    <desc>Humanity has long since advanced into space, and colonies have been established on many planets, but humanity has yet to contact any alien life. However, an emergency signal has come from the planet Shirakusa. During a colonization survey, contact was lost with the battleship Aphrodite. As a member of the elite Verytex squad, you are sent to investigate.

Verytex is a vertically scrolling space shooter with vague organic themes. There are six stages and three different weapon types: Normal Shot, a standard multidirectional cannon; Beam Laser, a powerful forward-shooting weapon; and Boomerang Laser, a wide-range forward shot. Each weapon type can be upgraded to three increasing levels of power. Also available are homing missiles, which are also upgradeable, as well as smart bombs and shield pickups.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19910405T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Asmik</developer>
    <publisher>Asmik</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Verytex (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Verytex (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Verytex (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="64849" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Virtua Fighter 2 VS Tekken 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Virtua Fighter 2 VS Tekken 2</name>
    <desc>Virtua Fighter 2 vs. Tekken 2 is an unlicensed Sega Mega Drive fighting game. The name has been taken from box and cartridge designs - in game it refers to itself as V.R Fighter VS Taken2. Its creator is currently unknown. 
As the name suggests, it is a crossover between characters from Sega AM2's Virtua Fighter 2 and Namco's Tekken 2, though for unknown reasons Bahn and Honey from Fighting Vipers are also playable. As expected, it is heavily influenced by Virtua Fighter 2 and Tekken 2, mimicking many of the stages and borrowing many sounds and music tracks. It does not, however, pull content from the Mega Drive port of Virtua Fighter 2 - only the Sega Saturn/Sega Model 2 version.</desc>
    <releasedate />
    <genre>Fight-Fight / 2D</genre>
    <image>./mixart/Virtua Fighter 2 VS Tekken 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Virtua Fighter 2 VS Tekken 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Virtua Fighter 2 VS Tekken 2 (Taiwan) (En) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>262</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="705" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Vixen 357 (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Vixen 357</name>
    <desc>In 2384 AD, a great interstellar war took place. The Earth emerged victorious, thanks to a secretly developed robot weapon called "Serd". After the war, the usage of Serds was not a secret any more, and various nations started using them for military purposes. Several years, a more powerful weapon named Vector was developed. The usage of such highly destructive weapons led to wars between the nations of the world. You control Takuya Murasawa and his comrades, member of a special military force called Slash. Everything begins with an attack of unidentified Vectors on their base...

"Vixen 357" is an animé-style strategy/RPG game with mech combat. You control your robots by moving them over the battle map, and fighting enemies with long-ranged or melée attacks. An animated battle sequence is shown when you and enemy robots attack each other. You can switch pilots in the robots and repair them during battles. Your pilots level up by gaining experience points, and you'll be able to acquire new robots and weapons during the game.</desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19921023T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Masaya Games</developer>
    <publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games-Tactical RPG-Strategy</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Vixen 357 (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Vixen 357 (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Vixen 357 (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1224" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Wani Wani World (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Wani Wani World</name>
    <desc>Wani Wani World is a modified conversion of the 1991 Kaneko coin-op The Berlin Wall, itself based on the 1980 coin-op Space Panic. Two small dinosaurs with very large hammers, Charlie and Smiley, make their way through numerous screens of platforms and ladders filled with enemies. Their only method of attack is to bash a hole in the ground, wait for an enemy to fall into it, and then bash the enemy in the head, which causes the enemy to fall and transform into items and delicious food.

There are five worlds, each with several screens and large boss at the end, as well as a minigame between worlds where bonus items can be earned. The game can be played alone or two-player cooperatively.</desc>
    <rating>0.75</rating>
    <releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Kaneko</developer>
    <publisher>Kaneko</publisher>
    <genre>Action-Platform</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Wani Wani World (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Wani Wani World (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Wani Wani World (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>257</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1237" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./XDR - X-Dazedly-Ray (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>XDR - X-Dazedly-Ray</name>
    <desc>XDR is a horizontal scrolling shooter in the mold of Gradius, featuring upgradable weapons and six stages of shooting action. The game features a vague science fiction theme, and includes six stages with a boss at the end of each. There are three difficulty settings. </desc>
    <rating>0.55</rating>
    <releasedate>19900826T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Affect</developer>
    <publisher>UNIPACC</publisher>
    <genre>Shoot'em Up</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/XDR - X-Dazedly-Ray (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/XDR - X-Dazedly-Ray (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/XDR - X-Dazedly-Ray (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>260</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1239" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Ya Se Chuan Shuo (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Ya Se Chuan Shuo</name>
    <desc>A beautifull Chinese RPG. Also known as Di Guo Wang Zhao or The Story of Arthur</desc>
    <rating>0.35</rating>
    <releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Chuanpu</developer>
    <publisher>Chuanpu</publisher>
    <genre>Role playing games</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Ya Se Chuan Shuo (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Ya Se Chuan Shuo (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Ya Se Chuan Shuo (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>768</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="362" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Yu Yu Hakusho - Makyou Toitsusen (Japan) (Translated En).zip</path>
    <name>Yu Yu Hakusho - Makyou Toitsusen</name>
    <desc>Yusuke Urameshi and his friends are invited to a tournament by Makyou Toitsusen, a mysterious martial arts society. In this tournament they are gonna face again some demons who fought them in the past, and decide who are the strongest.</desc>
    <rating>0.85</rating>
    <releasedate>19940930T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Treasure</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Action</genre>
    <players>1-4</players>
    <image>./mixart/Yu Yu Hakusho - Makyou Toitsusen (Japan) (Translated En).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Yu Yu Hakusho - Makyou Toitsusen (Japan) (Translated En).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Yu Yu Hakusho - Makyou Toitsusen (Japan) (Translated En).mp4</video>
    <favorite>true</favorite>
    <genreid>256</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="490" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Yu Yu Hakusho Gaiden (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Yu Yu Hakusho Gaiden</name>
    <desc>Based on the manga/animé series Yu Yu Hakusho. This is a story of a teenager delinquent Yuusuke Urameshi, who was hit by a car while trying to save a child. However, there was no place found for him either in paradise or in hell, and Koenma, the son of the death god Enma, sends him back to our world, where he has to be an "occult detective" and to fight against demons. Several characters join him on his quest: Kazuma Kuwabara, his ex-rival and best friend; Kurama, a 1400-year-old demon fox; and Hiei, formerly a demon who tried to conquer the world and had to repent for his sins by helping Yuusuke.

You must play the individual chapters of the four playable characters (Yuusuke, Kuwabara, Kurama, and Hiei), until in the final chapter you control them all in the ultimate confrontation against evil forces. The game is a Japanese-style adventure (no puzzles, menu-driven interface) with the addition of battles. The battles are real time; similarly to fighting games, you can kick, punch, defend, and use special techniques. Unlike most Japanese adventures, you view the game world from platform-like third person perspective (although you cannot move physically in adventure mode). </desc>
    <rating>0.6</rating>
    <releasedate>19940128T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Sega</developer>
    <publisher>Sega</publisher>
    <genre>Adventure</genre>
    <players>1</players>
    <image>./mixart/Yu Yu Hakusho Gaiden (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Yu Yu Hakusho Gaiden (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Yu Yu Hakusho Gaiden (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>512</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="18455" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Zan Yasha Enbukyoku (Japan).zip</path>
    <name>Zan Yasha Enbukyoku</name>
    <desc>Zan: Yasha Enbukyoku is a turn-based strategy game set in feudal Japan.

The background for the game's events is the ongoing battle between noble warriors, known as yasha, and demons. Between the two stand the "middle people", i.e. other Japanese generals and rulers. The player can choose to play as either yasha, demonic, or "middle" army. 

The player has to manage his army, deploying units for protection and attack, as well as negotiating with other rulers. Events such as earthquakes, plagues, etc. occur randomly. Diplomacy doesn't always work, so battles against enemy armies occupy a large portion of the game. The battles are somewhat similar to those of turn-based RPGs (though the game has no RPG elements): the player chooses commands from a menu, such as attack, use magic, use special technique, use a battle formation, etc. There is no active movement during the battles. The outcome of the battle depends on the chosen commands as well as on the strength of the units.</desc>
    <releasedate>19910329T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Wolf Team</developer>
    <publisher>Wolf Team</publisher>
    <genre>Strategy</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Zan Yasha Enbukyoku (Japan).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Zan Yasha Enbukyoku (Japan).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Zan Yasha Enbukyoku (Japan).mp4</video>
    <genreid>1280</genreid>
  </game>
  <game id="1243" source="ScreenScraper.fr">
    <path>./Zhuo Gui Da Shi - Ghost Hunter (Taiwan) (Unl).zip</path>
    <name>Zhuo Gui Da Shi - Ghost Hunter</name>
    <desc>Zhuo Gui Da Shi is a plateform game where you can shoot bubble to destroy them. It's a clone from the Arcade game Pang.</desc>
    <releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
    <developer>Senchi Technology</developer>
    <publisher>Senchi Technology</publisher>
    <genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
    <players>1-2</players>
    <image>./mixart/Zhuo Gui Da Shi - Ghost Hunter (Taiwan) (Unl).png</image>
    <marquee>./wheel/Zhuo Gui Da Shi - Ghost Hunter (Taiwan) (Unl).png</marquee>
    <video>./snap/Zhuo Gui Da Shi - Ghost Hunter (Taiwan) (Unl).mp4</video>
    <genreid>2816</genreid>
  </game>
</gameList>